<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the table-level READ ACL that
    grants the scoped role `x_[scope]_case_manager` UNCONDITIONAL read access
    on records of the `x_[scope]_case_party` custom table inside the scoped
    application `x_[scope]`. This is the READ companion to the case_manager
    create / write / delete ACLs whose granting ACLs are materialized by the
    sibling files:
        - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_create_agent.xml
          (creation is granted to BOTH manager AND agent; the manager grant
           is folded into a multi-role ACL that lists case_manager alongside
           case_agent so a single ACL covers the union of both creation rights
           per AAP Section 0.5.6 case_manager Create=Yes and case_agent
           Create=Yes for the case_party table)
        - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_write_manager.xml
          (manager write-all on case_party - unconditional WRITE companion
           to this READ ACL; together they implement the manager row's
           Write=All and Read=All cells per AAP Section 0.5.6)
        - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_delete_manager.xml
          (manager delete on case_party - the only role permitted to
           delete party records per AAP Section 0.5.6)
    Together those four files materialize the AAP Section 0.5.6 manager row
    mirrored at the case_party table level per AAP Section 0.5.1 row
    "servicenow-case-management-poc/acl/x_[scope]_case_party_*.xml"
    ("Mirror ACL pattern at party level"):
        | Role                    | Create | Read | Write | Delete |
        | x_[scope]_case_manager  |  Yes   | All  |  All  |  Yes   |

    The case_manager role is the highest-tier scoped role for case-management
    operations; per AAP Section 0.5.6 the manager has UNRESTRICTED read
    privileges on every case_party row regardless of which case the party is
    associated with, regardless of who is currently assigned to that parent
    case, regardless of whether the party is a Person or an Organization,
    and regardless of any other operational predicate. Read is the foundation
    privilege on which every other manager privilege builds: a manager cannot
    triage, route, or resolve a case without first being able to see the
    parties associated with it (the "who is involved" facts), they cannot
    decide whether to add or remove a party association without first reading
    the existing party list, and they cannot drive the Resolved -> Closed
    transition (reserved to the manager role per AAP Section 0.5.5) without
    first reading the case AND its associated parties to confirm completeness
    of the record. This file is therefore the prerequisite ACL for every
    other manager-tier capability on the case_party domain.

    AAP cross-references:
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - case_manager row, mirrored at the
        case_party table level per AAP Section 0.5.1 row
        "servicenow-case-management-poc/acl/x_[scope]_case_party_*.xml"
        ("Mirror ACL pattern at party level"):
            | Role                    | Create | Read | Write | Delete |
            | x_[scope]_case_manager  |  Yes   | All  |  All  |  Yes   |
        This file authors the single "Read = All" cell of the manager row
        for the case_party table. The "Yes" Create cell is authored (in
        union form alongside agent create) by
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_create_agent.xml; the "All" Write cell
        by ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_write_manager.xml; the "Yes" Delete
        cell by ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_delete_manager.xml. Each row of
        the ACL matrix maps to exactly one or zero ACL XML files - this
        per-cell granularity is what lets the Update Set add or remove role
        privileges independently without entangling roles or operations.
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - all-roles read coverage on case_party:
            - case_manager: Read=All            -> THIS FILE
            - case_agent:   Read=Assigned only  -> ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_read_agent_assigned.xml
                                                   (carries the row-level filter that
                                                    dereferences current.case to apply
                                                    the parent-case "Assigned only"
                                                    predicate via parent case's
                                                    assigned_agent and assigned_group)
            - case_viewer:  Read=All            -> ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_read_viewer.xml
                                                   (also unconditional - viewer is the
                                                    audit / supervisor tier with org-wide
                                                    visibility into every case_party for
                                                    oversight purposes)
        Together these three facts implement the user prompt's contract: the
        manager and viewer both see every case_party unconditionally (manager
        for operational oversight and routing, viewer for audit / compliance
        review); the agent's read scope is narrowed to "Assigned only" so
        agents see only the parties associated with cases they are entitled
        to work on. The deny-by-default nature of ServiceNow record ACLs
        means a user with NO scoped role sees zero rows on the case_party
        table; the three read ACLs combined give each role exactly its
        prescribed visibility.
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - relationship between this table-level
        read ACL and the field-level write ACLs on the parent case table:
            - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_group_field_acl.xml restricts
              WRITE on the parent case's assigned_group column.
            - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml restricts
              WRITE on the parent case's assigned_agent column.
        Those field-level ACLs apply to the parent case table only and have
        NO case_party analog because the case_party table - by AAP design -
        carries no role-based field-level write restrictions; all five party
        fields (case, party_type, person, organization, role_label) are
        governed solely by the table-level ACLs. Per the AAP matrix every
        role with Read=All can see every column on every visible row,
        including the polymorphic person and organization reference columns
        and the parent case reference. This is intentional: managers must
        see the full party association graph to triage, re-route, and close
        cases; viewers must see the full party graph for compliance and
        oversight. Therefore this READ ACL is unconditional at both the
        table level (no row filter) and the field level (no per-column read
        restriction).
      - Section 0.5.5 (State-Machine Transition Map) - manager-driven
        transitions that depend on this ACL:
            - "Resolved -> Closed: Caller has x_[scope]_case_manager role;
               auto-set closed_date." Closing a case requires the manager to
               first read the parent case to confirm Resolved status, the
               child task list to confirm task closure, AND the party list
               to confirm the historical party association record is intact
               (the audit trail of "who was involved" must be observable at
               the moment of closure). Reading the party list is authorized
               by THIS ACL.
            - "Any forward transition" by the manager: every UI Action and
               flow-driven transition begins with the manager opening the
               case form, which auto-loads the case_party Related List per
               AAP Section 0.4.4 ("Related Lists on the case form for both
               case_task and case_party"). That auto-load is a READ
               operation against this table - without this ACL the related
               list would render empty even though parties exist, which
               would mislead the manager during transitions.
        The transition rules are validated by the two case-type Flow Designer
        flows ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml and
        ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml plus the supporting subflows
        under ../flows/sub_flows/; those flows fire AFTER the platform's
        ACL evaluator has authorized the underlying read, so this ACL is a
        prerequisite to the case-form related-list rendering that precedes
        any transition.
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 3 - ACLs):
            "Role-based access enforced - case_viewer cannot write;
             case_agent cannot access unassigned cases; case_manager has
             full access."
        The clause "case_manager has full access" requires the manager role
        to be able to perform every CRUD operation on every table in the
        scoped application, including the case_party table. This ACL
        satisfies that clause for the read operation on case_party; the
        parallel clauses about case_viewer (which also reads all per the
        matrix - the AAP only restricts case_viewer from WRITE / CREATE /
        DELETE) and case_agent (read-restricted to "Assigned only") are
        unaffected by this ACL and are enforced by separate sibling ACL
        files.
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 1 - Data model):
            "All 3 custom tables created with correct fields and types -
             Zero missing mandatory fields."
        This validation is performed in part by a logged-in test user
        opening the case form to inspect the field set on each related
        table. The validation plan in ../docs/validation-gates.md exercises
        the demo manager (../seed-data/users/sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_manager.xml)
        reading each demo case's party related-list to verify all five
        case_party fields render correctly (case, party_type, person,
        organization, role_label - per AAP Section 0.5.7). Every one of
        those reads is authorized by THIS ACL.
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 6 - Dashboards):
            "Both dashboards render with synthetic data - All widgets
             display data; no broken report references."
        Although neither the Agent Workspace dashboard nor the Manager View
        dashboard directly aggregates over case_party (the eight reports in
        ../reports/ all aggregate over x_[scope]_case or x_[scope]_case_task
        per AAP Section 0.4.4), the manager's ability to drill INTO any
        case from a dashboard widget and inspect its parties is part of the
        end-to-end dashboard usability story. The drill-through navigates
        from the case row to the case form whose case_party Related List
        loads under THIS ACL.
      - Section 0.4.3 (Design Pattern Applications - Scoped role-based
        access control): "Three named roles paired with table-level and
        field-level ACLs whose conditions are encoded as scripted ACL
        expressions, replacing ArkCase's ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig
        map." This ACL is the table-level READ binding for the highest-tier
        scoped role on the party domain and is one of the declarative facts
        the platform's sys_security_acl evaluator consumes when authorizing
        a row read at runtime against the case_party table.
      - Section 0.4.3 (Polymorphic association via single-table choice + UI
        Policy): the case_party table collapses ArkCase's two separate
        association tables (acm_person_assoc, acm_person_org_assoc) into a
        single polymorphic ServiceNow table with a `party_type` Choice
        discriminator (Person | Organization). Because both polymorphic
        sub-shapes are stored in a single physical table, a single ACL
        record (this one) governs read access for the manager role across
        BOTH variants - there is no need for separate Person / Organization
        manager-read ACLs. This is a deliberate simplification of the source
        ArkCase model and is consistent with the project-wide convention of
        one ACL per (role, operation) tuple per scoped table.
      - Section 0.1.2 (Technical Interpretation - Access-control
        transformation): "ApplicationRolesConfig + RolesPrivilegesService +
        URL-based privilege metadata -> scoped roles + ACLs." In ArkCase the
        equivalent of THIS file would have been TWO entries in the
        rolesToPrivileges map (because ArkCase modeled person-association
        and organization-association in TWO separate tables, acm_person_assoc
        and acm_person_org_assoc) binding the manager-equivalent role to
        read privilege identifiers such as `acm-person-association-read`
        and `acm-organization-association-read`, evaluated at HTTP request
        time by AcmPluginUrlPrivilege against the GET verb on the person
        plugin's REST endpoints. The ServiceNow target replaces both map
        bindings AND the URL-privilege evaluator with this single
        declarative ACL record - because the target's case_party table is
        polymorphic per AAP Section 0.4.3, one ACL governs read for both
        Person and Organization variants.

    Why advanced=false (no scripted condition for manager read):
      Per AAP Section 0.5.6, the case_manager role's privileges are
      unconditional ("All", "Full access") - there is no "Assigned only"
      or other row-level filter on the manager's read scope. The manager is
      intentionally NOT scoped to a subset of case_party records; they have
      org-wide read authority because their job function is exactly to
      oversee, route, and close cases across all assignment boundaries
      including the parties associated with those cases. Therefore:
        - <advanced>false</advanced>      - no scripted condition
        - <condition/>                    - empty encoded query (no row filter)
        - <script/>                       - empty server-side script
      With no condition and no script, the ACL evaluates to "permit" for
      any caller who carries the x_[scope]_case_manager role. This is the
      correct semantic for the AAP's "manager has full read" requirement.
      Setting advanced=true with an empty script would be functionally
      equivalent but stylistically incorrect - the ServiceNow convention
      is to reserve advanced=true for ACLs that actually carry a scripted
      body (see, for contrast,
      ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_read_agent_assigned.xml where
      advanced=true and the script encodes the disjunctive ownership check
      that dereferences current.case up to the parent case row to apply
      `current.case.assigned_agent == gs.getUserID() ||
      gs.getUser().isMemberOf(current.case.assigned_group)`).

    Why this ACL is INDEPENDENT of the parent case's read ACL:
      ServiceNow ACL evaluation is per-table, not transitively inherited.
      Even though x_[scope]_case_party carries a reference to a
      x_[scope]_case row via its "case" field, the platform does NOT
      automatically apply the parent case's ACLs to child party records.
      Each table requires its own role-bound ACLs to govern access.
      Therefore this file is REQUIRED in addition to
      ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml - both must apply for a
      manager to be able to (a) open a case and (b) see its associated
      parties on the related list. Removing this file would break
      Validation Gate 3 (ACLs) for the case_party table even if the
      case-level manager ACL is present, because the case form's
      case_party Related List would silently render empty under
      deny-by-default semantics.

    Why READ is granted to manager unconditionally (design rationale):
      - Operational oversight: managers must see every party association
        across every case to triage intake, identify mis-classified parties
        (e.g., a person mistakenly entered as an organization), reconcile
        duplicate associations across cases, and pull aggregate views of
        which external persons or organizations recur across the case load.
        Restricting manager read on case_party to "Assigned only" would
        defeat the entire purpose of having a manager tier - they would
        only see parties on cases someone else had already routed to them,
        and by definition they could not perform cross-case party reviews.
      - State-machine entry point: per AAP Section 0.5.5 the
        Resolved -> Closed transition is reserved to the manager role and
        requires the manager to inspect the case form before approving the
        close. The case form auto-loads the case_party Related List - that
        list-load is a READ authorized by this ACL. Without this ACL the
        Related List would render empty and the manager would be unable to
        confirm the audit trail before closure.
      - Audit and compliance support: managers may be called upon to
        produce a list of every external person or organization associated
        with a given case for legal, compliance, or executive review at
        any time. The unconditional read ensures they can answer those
        requests without privilege escalation requests to platform admins.
      - Reporting accuracy: although the AAP's eight reports in ../reports/
        do not aggregate over case_party directly, future ad-hoc reports
        (created at runtime by a manager on the PDI within scope) would
        require manager-tier read access to case_party. Granting Read=All
        here pre-authorizes any future manager-authored case_party report
        without needing additional ACL changes.
      - Demo-data lifecycle: the seed script ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js
        creates demo party rows under each demo case (a Person and an
        Organization variant per case per AAP Section 0.4.1). The smoke-
        test phase requires the demo manager
        (../seed-data/users/sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_manager.xml) to read
        all seeded parties to confirm seed completeness; that read is
        authorized by THIS ACL.
      - Polymorphic UI policy interaction: the UI Policy in
        ../ui_policy/x_[scope]_case_party_conditional_fields.xml
        conditionally shows the person field when party_type=Person and
        the organization field when party_type=Organization. The UI Policy
        evaluates AFTER the platform has authorized the row read; this ACL
        is therefore the prerequisite to the UI Policy ever firing for a
        manager-tier user.

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only context per AAP Section
    0.3.2; no code or configuration is byte-for-byte ported from these
    files):
      - acm-services/acm-service-users/src/main/java/com/armedia/acm/
        services/users/model/ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig.java
        ArkCase mapped roles to privileges through a single configuration
        map (`Map<String, List<Object>> rolesToPrivileges`) keyed by the
        property `application.rolesToPrivileges`. The class declares the
        constant `ROLES_TO_PRIVILEGES_PROP_KEY = "application.rolesToPrivileges"`
        and exposes the map via `@MapValue(value = "application.rolesToPrivileges")
        getRolesToPrivileges()`. In that model, a "manager-equivalent"
        role (e.g., ROLE_PERSON_MANAGER, ROLE_ORG_MANAGER) would have been
        associated with read privilege identifiers such as
        `acm-person-association-read` and `acm-organization-association-read`
        (one identifier per association table, since ArkCase used two
        separate tables). The ServiceNow target replaces this map-based
        privilege association with declarative, scoped record-level ACLs -
        this XML record is the direct equivalent of the union of those two
        ArkCase map cells: the (case_manager, READ) pairing on the
        polymorphic case_party domain that subsumes both Person and
        Organization variants.
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-admin-plugin/src/main/java/com/
        armedia/acm/plugins/admin/service/RolesPrivilegesService.java
        Encapsulated role-CRUD and privilege-paging behavior in ArkCase
        (`retrieveRoles()`, `retrievePrivileges()`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByAuthorization(...)`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByRole(...)`, `updateRolePrivileges(...)`,
        `addRolesPrivileges(...)`, `removeRolesPrivileges(...)`). The
        service held injected dependencies on `UserDao`,
        `ApplicationRolesConfig`, `ApplicationPrivilegesConfig`,
        `ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig`, `ConfigurationPropertyService`,
        `CollectionPropertiesConfigurationService`, and
        `FunctionalAccessService` - a complex Spring/JPA stack that managed
        the role <-> privilege relationship at runtime. All of this Java
        service surface is replaced in the ServiceNow target by the
        platform's built-in sys_security_acl evaluator; no scripted
        privilege resolver is needed. Notably, ArkCase's
        `retrievePrivilegesByRole(roleName)` method paginated through the
        rolesToPrivileges map to return a role's privileges - the
        ServiceNow analog is the platform's "Roles" related list on
        sys_security_acl, which is automatically derived from the <roles>
        field of every ACL record like THIS one; no explicit query service
        is needed.

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.7.1 and 0.7.2):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: every cross-reference resolves into
        the x_[scope] scope (sys_scope = x_[scope], sys_package source =
        x_[scope]). No global-scope ACLs are written. The <name> field
        references the scoped table x_[scope]_case_party (not any OOB
        global table such as `task` or `incident_task`), and <roles>
        references the scoped role x_[scope]_case_manager. There are zero
        global writes from this file.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_id literals: <name>, <roles>,
        <sys_scope>, and <sys_package> all resolve their targets by name /
        source attribute lookup at Update Set apply time. The <sys_id>
        below is THIS record's own deterministic primary key (32-char
        lowercase hex MD5 of the canonical string
        "x_[scope]_case_party.read.case_manager", a stable canonical
        identifier for this exact ACL) and is not a cross-reference to
        any other record. Computing the sys_id deterministically
        guarantees the ACL is re-applyable / idempotent across fresh PDIs
        and round-trip Update Set previews per AAP Section 0.7.3 Gate 7,
        and matches the sibling-ACL convention:
            - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml uses
              MD5("x_[scope]_case.read.case_manager") =
              113c23bfb587d172b83db7ac8961ade2
            - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_read_manager.xml uses
              MD5("x_[scope]_case_task.read.case_manager") =
              c97e1d074ba86bf16b3a10cb4851e562
            - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_read_viewer.xml uses
              MD5("x_[scope]_case_party.read.case_viewer") =
              4aee16ed8c8df82c455f073e92498c7a
            - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_write_manager.xml uses
              MD5("x_[scope]_case_party.write.case_manager") =
              fc7c07fba024d5b59b782d83d22156b4
            - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_delete_manager.xml uses
              MD5("x_[scope]_case_party.delete.case_manager") =
              1f8bdcb79b5060d68ca63d034186c83a
            - this file uses
              MD5("x_[scope]_case_party.read.case_manager") =
              eebbc1bbf1aeab598e7ba377e1e6604b
      - Table-level (not field-level): <name> is `x_[scope]_case_party`
        with NO dot. Field-level read restrictions are NOT specified by
        the AAP for the case_manager role on case_party; the manager
        reads the entire party row including party_type, person,
        organization, role_label, and the case reference. Unlike the
        parent case table (which carries field-level write ACLs on
        assigned_group and assigned_agent - see sibling files
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_group_field_acl.xml and
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml), the
        case_party table has no field-level ACLs at all by AAP design.
        The <type>record</type> field below confirms this is a row-level
        (table-level) ACL, not a UI/REST/SOAP-flavored ACL.
      - Operation = read: corresponds exactly to the "Read = All" cell in
        the AAP matrix for the case_manager role mirrored to the
        case_party table. This is the table-level read binding; there are
        deliberately NO field-level read restrictions on x_[scope]_case_party
        for any role.
      - admin_overrides = true: standard ServiceNow pattern that allows
        the platform `admin` role to bypass this ACL. This is required so
        platform administrators can troubleshoot, repair, or re-seed
        scoped party data (per AAP Section 0.7.4 the
        ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js script runs as admin to populate
        demo party rows with mixed Person and Organization variants per
        AAP Section 0.4.1 to exercise the polymorphic UI policy). It does
        NOT widen case_manager privileges - non-admin managers see
        exactly what this ACL permits, which is full table-level read.
      - active = true: ACL is in force the moment the Update Set commits.
      - advanced = false: see "Why advanced=false" rationale above. The
        platform skips the empty <script/> body entirely.
      - condition (empty): the <condition/> encoded-query field is empty;
        no row-level filter applies to manager reads (manager has "All"
        access, not "Assigned only").
      - script (empty): the <script/> field is empty; the platform skips
        it because advanced=false.

    Difference from sibling ACLs - quick reference:
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_create_agent.xml (manager+agent
      CREATE on case_party - the case_party create ACL is a multi-role
      union granting both manager and agent create privileges):
        - <operation>     read              vs create
        - <roles>         x_[scope]_case_manager
                                            vs x_[scope]_case_manager,x_[scope]_case_agent
                                            (the create ACL lists BOTH roles
                                             since both have Create=Yes per
                                             AAP Section 0.5.6; this READ
                                             ACL lists ONLY the manager
                                             because the agent's read scope
                                             is "Assigned only" and is
                                             therefore handled by a separate
                                             scripted ACL file, not by
                                             folding into this one)
        - <sys_id>        eebbc1bbf1aeab598e7ba377e1e6604b
                                            vs MD5("x_[scope]_case_party.create.case_manager.case_agent")
                                            (or whatever canonical key the
                                             create-union ACL uses)
        - <sys_update_name> *_read_manager  vs *_create_agent
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_write_manager.xml (manager WRITE on
      case_party):
        - <operation>     read              vs write
        - <sys_id>        eebbc1bbf1aeab598e7ba377e1e6604b
                                            vs fc7c07fba024d5b59b782d83d22156b4
        - <sys_update_name> *_read_manager  vs *_write_manager
        - <description>                     differs in operation wording
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_delete_manager.xml (manager DELETE
      on case_party):
        - <operation>     read              vs delete
        - <sys_id>        eebbc1bbf1aeab598e7ba377e1e6604b
                                            vs 1f8bdcb79b5060d68ca63d034186c83a
        - <sys_update_name> *_read_manager  vs *_delete_manager
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_read_viewer.xml (viewer READ on
      case_party - same operation, same table, different role):
        - <roles>         x_[scope]_case_manager
                                            vs x_[scope]_case_viewer
        - <sys_id>        eebbc1bbf1aeab598e7ba377e1e6604b
                                            vs 4aee16ed8c8df82c455f073e92498c7a
        - <sys_update_name> *_read_manager  vs *_read_viewer
        - <description>                     refers to manager           vs viewer
        Both files have advanced=false, empty condition, and empty script
        because both manager and viewer have unconditional read per the
        AAP matrix. The two files are functionally parallel and together
        give the manager and viewer roles identical row-level read scope
        on x_[scope]_case_party (every row); the AAP intentionally puts
        manager and viewer in the same Read=All bucket because both serve
        org-wide oversight functions, while the case_agent role is the
        operational worker tier whose read is narrowed.
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_read_agent_assigned.xml (agent READ
      assigned-only on case_party):
        - <roles>         x_[scope]_case_manager
                                            vs x_[scope]_case_agent
        - <advanced>      false             vs true (the agent ACL carries
                                              a scripted condition that
                                              dereferences current.case to
                                              apply the parent-case
                                              "Assigned only" predicate;
                                              the manager ACL is
                                              unconditional)
        - <condition>     empty             vs encoded query that asserts
                                              parent-case "Assigned only"
        - <script>        empty             vs server-side dereference of
                                              current.case followed by
                                              disjunction of parent-case
                                              assigned_agent / assigned_group
                                              checks
        - <sys_id>        eebbc1bbf1aeab598e7ba377e1e6604b
                                            vs MD5("x_[scope]_case_party.read.case_agent.assigned")
        - <sys_update_name> *_read_manager  vs *_read_agent_assigned
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml (manager READ on parent
      case table):
        - <name>          x_[scope]_case_party
                                            vs x_[scope]_case
        - <sys_id>        eebbc1bbf1aeab598e7ba377e1e6604b
                                            vs 113c23bfb587d172b83db7ac8961ade2
        - <sys_update_name> *_case_party_read_manager
                                            vs *_case_read_manager
        - <description>                     references case_party table
                                            vs case table
        Both ACLs have identical <operation>=read,
        <roles>=x_[scope]_case_manager, <advanced>=false,
        <condition/>=empty, <script/>=empty - the only differences are
        the table name (case_party vs case) and the deterministic sys_id
        derived from that table name. This parallelism is what
        materializes the AAP rule "case_manager has full access" across
        BOTH the parent case table and the child case_party table.
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_read_manager.xml (manager READ on
      sibling case_task table):
        - <name>          x_[scope]_case_party
                                            vs x_[scope]_case_task
        - <sys_id>        eebbc1bbf1aeab598e7ba377e1e6604b
                                            vs c97e1d074ba86bf16b3a10cb4851e562
        - <sys_update_name> *_case_party_read_manager
                                            vs *_case_task_read_manager
        - <description>                     references case_party table
                                            vs case_task table
        Both ACLs have identical <operation>=read,
        <roles>=x_[scope]_case_manager, <advanced>=false,
        <condition/>=empty, <script/>=empty - the only differences are
        the table name (case_party vs case_task) and the deterministic
        sys_id derived from that table name. This parallelism completes
        the "case_manager has full access" mirror across all three
        custom tables (case, case_task, case_party).
      All other XML elements are identical between the manager-tier ACLs;
      the deterministic sys_id, the table name, and the operation/role
      triplet are the defining differences.

    Cross-dependencies and Update-Set ordering (AAP Section 0.5.2):
      MUST be loaded AFTER:
        - ../app/sys_app/x_[scope]_case_management.xml (scoped app record)
        - ../app/sys_scope/x_[scope].xml (scope record - resolves
          sys_scope and sys_package source="x_[scope]")
        - ../tables/x_[scope]_case_party.xml (resolves
          <name>x_[scope]_case_party</name> by table name lookup at apply
          time)
        - ../roles/sys_user_role_x_[scope]_case_manager.xml (resolves
          <roles>x_[scope]_case_manager</roles> by role name lookup at
          apply time)
      MUST be loaded BEFORE:
        - ../seed-data/role_assignments/sys_user_has_role_x_[scope]_demo_manager.xml
          (the demo manager's case_party-read access during round-trip
          verification depends on this ACL being applied first)
        - ../seed-data/parties/x_[scope]_case_party_demo_*.xml (so the
          demo manager immediately sees the seeded synthetic parties -
          both Person and Organization variants - once the Update Set
          commits and the demo manager logs in)
        - ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml,
          ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml,
          ../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml (Flow
          Designer flows on the parent case fire on update; their inline
          GlideRecord lookups against x_[scope]_case_party - if added by
          a future agent for party-related transition guards - and any
          parent-case dereferences inside subflows depend on this ACL
          having authorized the read)
        - any cleanup or re-seed activity in
          ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js that may post-validate prior demo
          party rows; while seed_demo_data.js itself runs as admin and
          bypasses this ACL via admin_overrides, post-seed smoke tests
          against the demo dataset depend on this ACL being applied so a
          logged-in demo manager can validate end-to-end party-read
          capability.
      The deny-by-default sibling pair that this file works with:
        - There is NO equivalent "deny" ACL needed for any role;
          ServiceNow ACLs are deny-by-default. A user without the
          case_manager role (and without case_agent or case_viewer) sees
          zero rows on x_[scope]_case_party regardless of any per-role
          ACL state.

    The literal `[scope]` placeholder is preserved verbatim per AAP
    convention (Section 0.7.2 "Scoped-namespace-only constraint"); the
    Personal Developer Instance auto-assigns the actual concrete scope
    id at App Engine Studio creation time, and the Update-Set apply-time
    renaming propagates consistently across all bracketed placeholders
    in this artifact. The deterministic sys_id below is computed against
    the `[scope]` literal and remains stable across re-imports onto
    fresh PDIs.
-->
<record_update table="sys_security_acl">
    <sys_security_acl action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <admin_overrides>true</admin_overrides>
        <advanced>false</advanced>
        <condition/>
        <description>Allows users with the x_[scope]_case_manager role to read all case_party records (unconditional). Per AAP Section 0.5.6, manager Read=All on case_party. NO field-level ACLs exist on case_party; this table-level grant fully governs manager read authority on every column (case, party_type, person, organization, role_label) for both Person and Organization polymorphic variants.</description>
        <name>x_[scope]_case_party</name>
        <operation>read</operation>
        <roles>x_[scope]_case_manager</roles>
        <script/>
        <sys_class_name>sys_security_acl</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>eebbc1bbf1aeab598e7ba377e1e6604b</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>x_[scope]_case_party</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_[scope]">x_[scope]</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_[scope]</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_security_acl_x_[scope]_case_party_read_manager</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <type>record</type>
    </sys_security_acl>
</record_update>
