<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the FIELD-LEVEL WRITE ACL that
    governs who may update the `assigned_group` column on the `x_[scope]_case`
    custom table inside the scoped application `x_[scope]`. Per AAP Section
    0.5.1 (File-by-File Transformation Plan, row for
    `acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_group_field_acl.xml`):
        "Field-level ACL: write restricted to manager"
    Per AAP Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix), this ACL grants write access to
    EXACTLY ONE role and DENIES it to everyone else:
        x_[scope]_case_manager - the case-management tier's delegation
        authority. The manager freely re-routes cases between operational
        groups; this is by design a management-tier privilege.
    All other role populations - x_[scope]_case_agent, x_[scope]_case_viewer,
    anonymous portal traffic, and any future scoped roles - are denied
    write access to the `assigned_group` column. ServiceNow's ACL evaluator
    applies an implicit DENY when no matching role grant exists; the
    absence of `x_[scope]_case_agent` and `x_[scope]_case_viewer` from the
    <roles> field below is therefore a deliberate, sufficient denial. No
    explicit "deny" record is required (and indeed cannot be expressed in
    a single sys_security_acl row - ServiceNow ACLs grant; non-grants
    deny).

    AAP cross-references:
      - Section 0.5.1 (File-by-File Transformation Plan, row for THIS
        file): "Field-level ACL: write restricted to manager".
        This file is the single artifact that materializes that single
        line in the transformation plan. The whole-of-AAP wording
        ("manager"), without the "agent-assigned" qualifier that appears
        in the sibling `assigned_agent_field_acl.xml` row, is preserved
        verbatim in the description below and reflected in the <roles>
        field carrying ONLY `x_[scope]_case_manager`.
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix, full table reproduced verbatim from
        AAP):
            | Role                    | Create | Read           | Write          | Delete |
            | x_[scope]_case_manager  | Yes    | All            | All            | Yes    |
            | x_[scope]_case_agent    | Yes    | Assigned only  | Assigned only  | No     |
            | x_[scope]_case_viewer   | No     | All            | No             | No     |
        The matrix above is enforced at TWO layers:
            (a) Table-level ACLs (sibling files
                `../acl/x_[scope]_case_create_*.xml`,
                `../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_*.xml`,
                `../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_*.xml`,
                `../acl/x_[scope]_case_delete_*.xml`) carry the row-level
                "All" / "Assigned only" predicates per role.
            (b) Field-level ACLs (THIS file plus
                `../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml`)
                further narrow the WRITE scope on two specific columns
                (`assigned_group` and `assigned_agent`) so that even an
                agent who has passed the table-level write check still
                cannot route cases between groups (THIS file) and so that
                non-assigned agents still cannot poach assignments (the
                sibling).
        ServiceNow ACL evaluation requires BOTH the table-level write ACL
        AND the field-level write ACL to permit the operation for write
        to succeed; the most-restrictive ACL governs. Therefore an agent
        who can write to a case row (because they ARE assigned, satisfying
        the table-level `write_agent_assigned` ACL) still cannot change
        `assigned_group` because this field-level ACL does not include
        the `x_[scope]_case_agent` role in <roles>. The agent's write
        attempt to the column fails the field-level role filter; the
        platform returns the standard "Access not permitted" form-level
        error and the column value is unchanged.
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix, "Assigned only" definition):
            "Assigned only = cases where assigned_agent = current user OR
             assigned_group contains current user."
        That definition motivates this field-level ACL's manager-only
        restriction. The "Assigned only" predicate at the table level
        depends on `assigned_group` membership as one of two grant paths.
        If a `case_agent` could write `assigned_group` directly, they
        could add their own group (or remove a peer's group) and
        unilaterally manipulate which cases they have row-level access
        to - the canonical privilege-escalation vector. Locking the
        column to manager-only writes closes that vector at the column
        level, regardless of whether the agent has row-level write access
        through the table-level "Assigned only" grant.
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 3 - ACLs):
            "Role-based access enforced - case_viewer cannot write;
             case_agent cannot access unassigned cases; case_manager has
             full access."
        The middle clause ("case_agent cannot access unassigned cases")
        is the central correctness criterion of THIS field-level ACL: a
        case_agent MUST NOT be able to set `assigned_group` to a group
        they belong to, because doing so would let them gain row-level
        access to a case they had no assignment relationship with. The
        denial here is structural - the agent role is simply not in
        <roles> - so the platform's ACL evaluator returns false for the
        column-write attempt without any conditional logic firing.
      - Section 0.4.3 (Design Pattern Applications - Scoped role-based
        access control): "Three named roles paired with table-level and
        field-level ACLs whose conditions are encoded as scripted ACL
        expressions, replacing ArkCase's ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig
        map." This file is the FIRST of the two field-level ACLs called
        out in that pattern statement; the other is
        `../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml`. Together
        the two field-level ACLs encode the layered defense described in
        the AAP: table-level grants mediate ROW visibility, and
        field-level grants further constrain WRITE on the assignment
        columns.
      - Section 0.1.2 (Technical Interpretation - Access-control
        transformation): "ArkCase resolves privileges via
        ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig.getRolesToPrivileges() (a
        Map<String, List<Object>> bound from application.rolesToPrivileges
        configuration), enforced at URL/method level by
        AcmPluginUrlPrivilege. The target replaces this with three scoped
        roles ..., each governed by table-level ACLs (read, write, create,
        delete) and field-level ACLs on assigned_group / assigned_agent."
        This file is the FIRST of the two field-level ACLs referenced
        in that statement.
      - Section 0.5.5 (State-Machine Transition Map) - relationship to
        the Draft -> Open transition:
            | Draft | Open | assigned_group populated |
                                  Surface form-level error |
        The state-machine flows `../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml`
        and `../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml` (with subflow
        `../flows/sub_flows/validate_open_transition.xml`) require
        `assigned_group` to be populated before the Draft -> Open
        transition can succeed. Per this field-level ACL, ONLY a manager
        may make that population. Therefore the Draft -> Open transition
        is operationally a manager-driven step: a draft case sits in
        Draft until a manager triages it and routes it to a group. The
        agent is then able to take over once the manager additionally
        sets `assigned_agent` (governed by the sibling field-level ACL).
        This is the workflow corollary of the privilege-escalation
        prevention encoded in this ACL.
      - Section 0.7.1 (Refactoring-Specific Rules and Requirements):
            "Enforce the exact role x CRUD matrix. Three scoped roles ...
             ACLs MUST be authored at table level AND field level for
             assigned_group and assigned_agent."
        This file is the field-level ACL for `assigned_group`; the
        sibling file `../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml`
        is the field-level ACL for `assigned_agent`. Together with the
        eight table-level ACLs in this folder, they materialize the
        "table level AND field level" requirement.

    Why this ACL is manager-only (no agent self-write branch):
      The two field-level ACLs in this folder differ in exactly one
      design choice: should the assigned agent be able to change the
      field themselves?
        - For `assigned_group` (THIS FILE): NO. Group changes cross team
          boundaries, re-route cases between operational organizations,
          and have downstream implications for SLA, routing rules, and
          notification chains. These are fundamentally management
          decisions, not operational ones. An agent who is reassigning
          their own case to a different group is effectively making a
          routing decision that should require manager review. Hence
          this ACL restricts write to the manager role only - by listing
          ONLY `x_[scope]_case_manager` in the <roles> field.
        - For `assigned_agent`
          (../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml): YES, but
          ONLY when the agent is the currently-assigned agent. The
          handoff use case is core to day-to-day operations: an agent on
          PTO needs to hand off active cases; an agent reassigning a
          misrouted case to a colleague who is the SME; an agent
          declining an assignment that conflicts with prior commitments.
          These are ALL operational decisions that should not require
          manager involvement to execute.
      This file's <roles> field carries ONE role; the sibling's <roles>
      field carries TWO roles (manager + agent). This ACL's <advanced>
      is false (no script body, simple role grant); the sibling's
      <advanced> is true (script body narrows the agent grant to
      self-assigned cases only).

    Why <advanced>false</advanced> is the correct setting (CRITICAL):
      ServiceNow ACL evaluation: when <advanced> is false, the platform
      evaluates ONLY the <condition/> encoded query (which is empty in
      THIS file) and the <roles> field. With an empty condition and a
      single-role <roles> field, the evaluator's logic reduces to "user
      holds x_[scope]_case_manager => grant; otherwise => deny". This is
      EXACTLY the semantics required by AAP Section 0.5.1's "write
      restricted to manager" mandate. Setting <advanced>true</advanced>
      would require a non-empty <script> body to express the grant; an
      unnecessary script step here would (a) be more brittle (script
      parsing/runtime errors could silently disable the ACL),
      (b) introduce code surface that a future maintainer might
      mistakenly modify to add an agent branch, and (c) be inconsistent
      with the other manager-only table-level ACLs in this folder
      (sibling files like `../acl/x_[scope]_case_create_manager.xml`,
      `../acl/x_[scope]_case_delete_manager.xml`,
      `../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_manager.xml` all use
      <advanced>false</advanced> with a manager-only <roles> and an
      empty <script>). Following the same pattern keeps this ACL
      auditable and stylistically uniform.

    Why ONLY `x_[scope]_case_manager` in <roles> (CRITICAL):
      ServiceNow's ACL evaluator first filters candidate ACLs by role:
      only ACLs whose <roles> field contains a role the current user
      holds are considered for evaluation. Therefore listing ONLY
      `x_[scope]_case_manager` here means:
        - case_manager users: the ACL is a candidate; the empty
          condition + empty script + advanced=false default evaluates
          to GRANT for any matching role. Manager writes succeed.
        - case_agent users: the ACL is NOT a candidate (their role is
          not in <roles>); the platform finds no matching field-level
          write ACL on `assigned_group`; per ServiceNow's default-deny
          behavior on field-level ACLs, the column write is denied.
        - case_viewer users: same as case_agent - not a candidate -
          denied.
        - admin users: the admin_overrides=true setting on this ACL
          allows the platform admin role to bypass all checks. Admin
          retains the ability to override the column for troubleshooting
          or repair purposes (and for the seed-script
          `../scripts/seed_demo_data.js` which runs as admin to
          populate demo cases per AAP Section 0.7.4).
      Adding `x_[scope]_case_agent` to <roles> would be incorrect: it
      would cause the agent role to pass the role-filter step and the
      empty-condition + empty-script + advanced=false logic would then
      grant unconditionally, completely defeating the AAP-mandated
      "manager-only" restriction. THE WHOLE POINT of this ACL is the
      single-role <roles> list.
      Adding `x_[scope]_case_viewer` would be even more incorrect:
      viewers are AAP Section 0.5.6-mandated read-only and must not
      pass any write ACL anywhere.

    Edge cases handled by this ACL's structure:
      - current.assigned_group IS NULL (an unassigned case in Draft
        state): the manager attempts to populate it for the Draft -> Open
        transition. The role-filter passes (manager is in <roles>); the
        empty condition passes; advanced=false short-circuits to grant.
        The manager's write succeeds. THIS IS THE PRIMARY HAPPY-PATH the
        ACL supports.
      - current.assigned_group is a different group (manager
        re-routes a case from group A to group B): same path -
        manager-in-roles + empty-condition + advanced-false-grant - the
        write succeeds. Agents who happen to be members of group A or
        group B cannot make this re-routing change.
      - User holds both case_manager and case_agent roles (unusual but
        possible): the role-filter passes on case_manager; grant
        succeeds. The user effectively operates at the higher-privilege
        manager level when both roles are held - the desired outcome.
      - User is admin (out-of-the-box ServiceNow admin role): the
        admin_overrides=true setting allows admin to bypass ALL ACL
        checks, including this one.
      - Anonymous portal traffic: anonymous users hold no scoped roles;
        the role-filter excludes them; column write is denied. The
        portal's case-submission widget (`../portal/widgets/sp_widget_x_[scope]_case_submission_widget.xml`)
        does NOT submit `assigned_group` (per AAP Section 0.5.1 row for
        `portal/rest/sys_ws_definition_x_[scope]_case_submit.xml`
        "Whitelisted fields only" - assigned_group is not in the
        whitelist), so the portal flow never attempts the denied write.

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only context per AAP Section
    0.3.2; no code or configuration is byte-for-byte ported from these
    files):
      - acm-services/acm-service-users/src/main/java/com/armedia/acm/
        services/users/model/ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig.java
        ArkCase mapped roles to privileges through a single configuration
        map (`Map<String, List<Object>> rolesToPrivileges`) keyed by the
        property `application.rolesToPrivileges`. The class declares the
        constant `ROLES_TO_PRIVILEGES_PROP_KEY =
        "application.rolesToPrivileges"` and exposes the map via
        `@MapValue(value = "application.rolesToPrivileges")
        getRolesToPrivileges()`. In that model, FIELD-level write
        restrictions did not exist as a first-class concept; they had
        to be re-implemented per-field as imperative checks inside Spring
        service classes (e.g., a CaseFile.setQueue / setAssignedGroup
        setter would bracket the assignment with role-aware logic, or a
        Spring AOP aspect would intercept setter calls to enforce
        manager-only writes on `acm_case_file.queue_id`). The ServiceNow
        target replaces that scattered imperative model with a single
        declarative, scoped, field-level ACL whose role grant carries
        the "manager-only" restriction. This XML record is the direct
        equivalent of the (case_manager, WRITE, assigned_group column)
        cell in the conceptual ArkCase map - a cell that in ArkCase had
        no specialized configuration support and had to be enforced
        through application code.
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-admin-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/admin/service/RolesPrivilegesService.java
        Encapsulated role-CRUD and privilege-paging behavior in ArkCase
        (`retrieveRoles()`, `retrievePrivileges()`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByAuthorization(...)`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByRole(...)`, `updateRolePrivileges(...)`,
        `addRolesPrivileges(...)`, `removeRolesPrivileges(...)`). The
        service held injected dependencies on UserDao,
        ApplicationRolesConfig, ApplicationPrivilegesConfig,
        ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig,
        ConfigurationPropertyService,
        CollectionPropertiesConfigurationService, and
        FunctionalAccessService - a complex Spring/JPA stack that managed
        the role <-> privilege relationship at runtime. All of this Java
        service surface is replaced in the ServiceNow target by the
        platform's built-in sys_security_acl evaluator; no scripted
        privilege resolver is needed. Per-field write restrictions on
        sensitive columns (like `assigned_group`/`queue_id`) that
        ArkCase had to enforce through custom @PrePersist / @PreUpdate
        JPA listeners or aspect-oriented interceptors are replaced in
        the ServiceNow scoped equivalent by THIS field-level ACL XML
        record - declarative, centrally managed by the platform's ACL
        engine, and free of any custom interceptor code.

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.7.1 and 0.7.2):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: every cross-reference resolves into
        the x_[scope] scope (sys_scope = x_[scope], sys_package source =
        x_[scope]). No global-scope ACLs are written. The <name> field
        references the scoped table-and-column
        `x_[scope]_case.assigned_group` (not any OOB table or any global
        column), and <roles> references the scoped role
        `x_[scope]_case_manager`. Zero global writes from this file.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_id literals: <name>, <roles>,
        <sys_scope>, and <sys_package> all resolve their targets by name
        / source-attribute lookup at Update Set apply time. Role names
        inside <roles> are resolved by name lookup against the
        sys_user_role table at runtime. The <sys_id> below is THIS
        record's own deterministic primary key (32-char lowercase hex,
        MD5 of the canonical identifier
        "x_[scope]_case.assigned_group.write.case_manager", a stable
        canonical key for this exact ACL) and is not a cross-reference
        to any other record. Computing the sys_id deterministically
        guarantees the ACL is re-applyable / idempotent across fresh
        PDIs and round-trip Update Set previews per AAP Section 0.7.3
        Gate 7. The MD5 result is 04d4a9cdb62499be0a894d217c979202,
        computed once at authoring time and committed verbatim below;
        any reauthoring of this file must reproduce the same canonical
        key string and the same MD5 output to preserve idempotency.
      - Field-level (NOT table-level): <name> is
        `x_[scope]_case.assigned_group` WITH a literal dot separator
        between table and column. This is the ServiceNow convention for
        field-level ACLs and distinguishes this record from the eight
        sibling table-level ACLs whose <name> is just `x_[scope]_case`
        (no dot, no column). The single-character dot difference is
        what tells the platform's ACL evaluator that this rule governs
        writes to a SPECIFIC COLUMN rather than to the entire row.
      - Operation = write: corresponds exactly to the field-level write
        restriction described in AAP Section 0.5.1's row for this file.
        There are NO field-level read ACLs on x_[scope]_case for any
        role (per AAP Section 0.5.6 only assigned_group and
        assigned_agent have any field-level ACLs at all, and those are
        write-only restrictions). There are NO field-level create or
        delete ACLs because those operations target rows, not fields.
      - admin_overrides = true: standard ServiceNow pattern allowing
        the platform `admin` role to bypass this ACL for
        troubleshooting, repair, or seed-data operations. The seed
        script `../scripts/seed_demo_data.js` runs as admin to populate
        demo cases (per AAP Section 0.7.4); admin's ability to set
        assigned_group during that seed pass depends on this override.
        The admin override does NOT widen non-admin role privileges; it
        only allows the platform-level admin role to bypass the
        manager-role grant.
      - active = true: ACL is in force the moment the Update Set commits.
      - advanced = false: there is NO scripted predicate; the ACL grant
        is purely role-based with an empty condition. See "Why
        advanced=false is the correct setting" rationale above.
      - condition (empty): no encoded-query condition is set; with
        advanced=false, the empty condition + role membership is the
        complete grant logic.
      - script (empty): no scripted predicate. With advanced=false the
        script field is ignored even if populated; leaving it empty
        keeps the record minimal and unambiguous.
      - type = record: this is a row-level (record-level) field ACL,
        not a UI/REST/SOAP-flavored one. The platform's record evaluator
        invokes this ACL during any GlideRecord update path that touches
        the assigned_group column.

    Cross-dependencies and Update-Set ordering (AAP Section 0.5.2):
      MUST be loaded AFTER:
        - ../app/sys_app/x_[scope]_case_management.xml (scoped app
          record)
        - ../app/sys_scope/x_[scope].xml (scope record - resolves
          sys_scope and sys_package source="x_[scope]")
        - ../tables/x_[scope]_case.xml (resolves the table half of
          <name>x_[scope]_case.assigned_group</name>)
        - ../dictionary/x_[scope]_case_assigned_group.xml (resolves the
          column half of <name>x_[scope]_case.assigned_group</name>;
          the field-level ACL cannot be applied until the field exists
          in sys_dictionary)
        - ../roles/sys_user_role_x_[scope]_case_manager.xml (resolves
          the single entry in <roles> by role-name lookup at apply time)
      MUST be loaded BEFORE:
        - ../seed-data/role_assignments/sys_user_has_role_x_[scope]_demo_*.xml
          (the demo manager's write tests during round-trip verification
          depend on this ACL being applied first)
        - ../seed-data/cases/x_[scope]_case_demo_*.xml (demo cases are
          inserted by the seed pass; this ACL governs subsequent
          demo-time writes to the assigned_group column)
        - ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml,
          ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml,
          ../flows/sub_flows/validate_open_transition.xml (Flow Designer
          flows fire on update; their inline GlideRecord writes to
          assigned_group during state transitions are filtered through
          this ACL when run by a logged-in agent or manager - the flows
          must not execute before the ACL is applied or unauthorized
          assigned_group writes could leak through during update-set
          apply)

    Composition with the table-level WRITE ACLs:
      A write to the assigned_group field requires BOTH:
        (a) The table-level write ACL on x_[scope]_case to permit the
            row update (one of `../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_manager.xml`,
            `../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_agent_assigned.xml`, or admin
            override), AND
        (b) THIS field-level ACL to permit the column update.
      Concrete walk-throughs:
        * Manager writes assigned_group on any case (initial group
          routing during Draft -> Open transition, or re-routing
          mid-lifecycle): (a) write_manager ACL grants unconditionally;
          (b) this ACL grants because manager is in <roles> with
          empty condition and advanced=false. PERMITTED.
        * Currently-assigned agent attempts to change assigned_group to
          a peer's group (effective re-routing): (a)
          write_agent_assigned grants because assigned_agent ==
          current user; (b) THIS ACL DENIES because case_agent is NOT
          in <roles>. The platform returns "Access not permitted" on
          the column. DENIED.
          THIS IS THE PRIMARY DEFENSE the ACL provides over the
          table-level ACL alone.
        * Currently-assigned agent attempts to remove assigned_group
          (set to null): same path - table-level grants, field-level
          denies. DENIED.
        * Non-assigned agent who IS in the assigned_group attempts to
          change the group to remove themselves (or add themselves to
          a different case's group via this case's record path): the
          row-level write fails first because the agent isn't the
          assignee; even if they were, THIS ACL would deny at the
          field level. DENIED at multiple layers.
        * Viewer attempts to write assigned_group: (a) NO write ACL
          grants the viewer role; the row update fails at the table
          level and never reaches this ACL. DENIED.
      The above walk-throughs are reproduced step-by-step in the manual
      `../scripts/round_trip_verify.md` procedure.

    Difference from sibling field-level ACL (assigned_agent):
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml:
        - <name>          x_[scope]_case.assigned_group
                                            vs x_[scope]_case.assigned_agent
        - <roles>         x_[scope]_case_manager
                                            vs x_[scope]_case_manager,x_[scope]_case_agent
        - <advanced>      false             vs true
        - <script>        empty             vs manager-or-assigned-agent CDATA body
        - <sys_id>        04d4a9cdb62499be0a894d217c979202
                              (MD5 of "x_[scope]_case.assigned_group.write.case_manager")
                                            vs 3719a93101a32c5e06c9907fbcfa8d03
                              (MD5 of "x_[scope]_case.assigned_agent.write.manager_or_assigned")
        - <sys_update_name> *_assigned_group_field_acl
                                            vs *_assigned_agent_field_acl
      The two field-level ACLs share their column-targeting structure
      (<name> = table.column, <type>=record, <operation>=write,
      admin_overrides=true) but diverge in roles/advanced/script per the
      design choice described above ("Why this ACL is manager-only").

    The literal `[scope]` placeholder is preserved verbatim per AAP
    convention (Section 0.7.2 "Scoped-namespace-only constraint"); the
    Personal Developer Instance auto-assigns the actual concrete scope
    id at App Engine Studio creation time, and the Update-Set apply-time
    renaming propagates consistently across all bracketed placeholders
    in this artifact - including the role-name string in <roles>. The
    deterministic sys_id below is computed against the `[scope]` literal
    and remains stable across re-imports onto fresh PDIs.
-->
<record_update table="sys_security_acl">
    <sys_security_acl action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <admin_overrides>true</admin_overrides>
        <advanced>false</advanced>
        <condition/>
        <description>Field-level ACL: only x_[scope]_case_manager can write the assigned_group field on x_[scope]_case. case_agent and case_viewer are denied (privilege escalation prevention).</description>
        <name>x_[scope]_case.assigned_group</name>
        <operation>write</operation>
        <roles>x_[scope]_case_manager</roles>
        <script/>
        <sys_class_name>sys_security_acl</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>04d4a9cdb62499be0a894d217c979202</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>x_[scope]_case.assigned_group</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_[scope]">x_[scope]</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_[scope]</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_security_acl_x_[scope]_case_assigned_group_field_acl</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <type>record</type>
    </sys_security_acl>
</record_update>
