<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the table-level WRITE ACL that
    grants the scoped role `x_[scope]_case_manager` UNCONDITIONAL write access
    on records of the `x_[scope]_case` custom table inside the scoped
    application `x_[scope]`. This is the WRITE companion to the case_manager
    create / read / delete ACLs (../acl/x_[scope]_case_create_manager.xml,
    ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml, ../acl/x_[scope]_case_delete_manager.xml)
    and together those four files materialize the AAP Section 0.5.6 row:
    "x_[scope]_case_manager : Create=Yes, Read=All, Write=All, Delete=Yes."

    The case_manager role is the highest-tier scoped role for case-management
    operations; per AAP Section 0.5.6 the manager has UNRESTRICTED write
    privileges on every case row regardless of who originally opened the
    case, who is currently assigned to it, or which group owns it. This
    privilege is the keystone that lets managers re-route cases between
    groups (by editing assigned_group), reassign in-flight cases between
    agents (by editing assigned_agent), correct intake errors on subject /
    description / requester_name / requester_email, set priority and type,
    and drive cases through every state-machine transition that requires
    elevated authority - notably the Resolved -> Closed transition, which
    AAP Section 0.5.5 reserves to the manager role and which is enforced
    server-side by the validate_closed_transition subflow at
    ../flows/sub_flows/validate_closed_transition.xml.

    AAP cross-references:
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - case_manager row (verbatim from AAP):
            | Role                    | Create | Read | Write | Delete |
            | x_[scope]_case_manager  |  Yes   | All  |  All  |  Yes   |
        This file authors the single "Write = All" cell. The "Yes" Create
        cell is authored by ../acl/x_[scope]_case_create_manager.xml; the
        "All" Read cell by ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml; the
        "Yes" Delete cell by ../acl/x_[scope]_case_delete_manager.xml. Each
        row of the ACL matrix maps to exactly one or zero ACL XML files -
        this per-cell granularity is what lets the Update Set add or remove
        role privileges independently without entangling roles or operations.
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - all-roles write coverage on x_[scope]_case:
            - case_manager: Write=All           -> THIS FILE
            - case_agent:   Write=Assigned only -> ../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_agent_assigned.xml
                                                   (carries the row-level filter
                                                    "assigned_agent = current.sys_id
                                                     OR assigned_group IN
                                                     current.user_group_membership")
            - case_viewer:  Write=No            -> deliberate absence of any
                                                   x_[scope]_case_write_viewer.xml
                                                   (deny-by-default)
        Together these three facts implement the user prompt's contract:
        the manager is empowered to edit any case unconditionally; the
        agent is empowered to edit only the cases they own (where ownership
        is the disjunction of direct agent assignment and group membership);
        the viewer is denied write entirely so the audit / compliance /
        supervisor tier cannot mutate case data.
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - relationship between this table-level
        write ACL and the field-level ACLs on assigned_group / assigned_agent:
            - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_group_field_acl.xml restricts
              write on the assigned_group column to the case_manager role.
            - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml restricts
              write on the assigned_agent column to the case_manager role
              AND to a case_agent who satisfies the "Assigned only" condition.
        ServiceNow evaluates ALL applicable ACLs for a given operation - a
        write to a sensitive field must pass BOTH the table-level ACL (this
        file or the agent-assigned write ACL) AND any field-level ACL on
        the column being written. Because the case_manager role is in the
        roles-list of BOTH field-level ACLs, the manager passes both checks
        and can write those columns freely. The field-level ACLs do not
        restrict the manager - they restrict case_agent (who can only write
        assigned_agent on cases they are already assigned to, never
        reassigning to themselves "from outside") and case_viewer (who can
        write neither field). This file is therefore the necessary table-
        level grant that, combined with the field-level ACL roles-list
        membership, gives the manager full edit authority on every column.
      - Section 0.5.5 (State-Machine Transition Map) - manager-driven
        transitions that depend on this ACL:
            - "Resolved -> Closed: Caller has x_[scope]_case_manager role;
               auto-set closed_date." Closing a case requires writing the
               status column from `Resolved` to `Closed`; that write must
               pass this ACL (manager role permitted). The auto-population
               of closed_date is performed by the before-update business
               rule ../business_rules/x_[scope]_set_closed_date.xml as a
               server-side side-effect of the same write transaction - that
               business rule runs in the manager's session, so the write
               must already have been authorized by THIS ACL.
            - "Open / In Progress / Pending / Resolved transitions": although
               agents can drive most forward transitions on cases they are
               assigned to (via the agent-assigned write ACL), the manager
               can drive ANY transition on ANY case. This ACL is what makes
               manager-mediated escalations and re-routings possible -
               without it, managers would be reduced to read-only oversight.
        The transition rules are validated by the two case-type Flow
        Designer flows ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml and
        ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml plus the supporting subflows
        under ../flows/sub_flows/; those flows fire AFTER the platform's
        ACL evaluator has authorized the underlying write, so this ACL is
        a prerequisite to the flow ever running for a manager.
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 3 - ACLs):
            "Role-based access enforced - case_viewer cannot write;
             case_agent cannot access unassigned cases; case_manager has
             full access."
        The clause "case_manager has full access" requires that the manager
        role be able to perform every CRUD operation on the case table, of
        which write is the most-frequent. This ACL satisfies that clause
        for the write operation; the parallel clauses about case_viewer
        (no write) and case_agent (no unassigned-case access) are unaffected
        by this ACL and are enforced by separate sibling ACL files
        (case_viewer never appears in any write/create/delete ACL;
        case_agent write is conditioned on the "Assigned only" filter via
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_agent_assigned.xml).
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 1 - Data model) and
        Gate 2 (Workflow): both gates depend on a logged-in test user being
        able to mutate case fields and exercise transitions. The validation
        plan in ../docs/validation-gates.md exercises the full state machine
        as the demo manager (../seed-data/users/sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_manager.xml);
        every state-machine transition step in that validation requires
        this ACL to authorize the underlying status update.
      - Section 0.4.3 (Design Pattern Applications - Scoped role-based
        access control): "Three named roles paired with table-level and
        field-level ACLs whose conditions are encoded as scripted ACL
        expressions, replacing ArkCase's ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig
        map." This ACL is the table-level WRITE binding for the highest-tier
        scoped role and is one of the declarative facts the platform's
        sys_security_acl evaluator consumes when authorizing a row update
        at runtime.
      - Section 0.1.2 (Technical Interpretation - Access-control
        transformation): "ApplicationRolesConfig + RolesPrivilegesService +
        URL-based privilege metadata -> scoped roles + ACLs." In ArkCase
        the equivalent of THIS file would have been a single entry in the
        rolesToPrivileges map binding the manager-equivalent role to a
        privilege identifier such as `acm-case-edit` or `acm-case-update`,
        evaluated at HTTP request time by AcmPluginUrlPrivilege against the
        PUT verb on the casefile REST endpoint. The ServiceNow target
        replaces both the map binding and the URL-privilege evaluator with
        this single declarative ACL record; the platform's sys_security_acl
        engine handles the role-membership check, condition evaluation, and
        admin-override logic that ArkCase implemented through hand-written
        Java code (see acm-services/acm-service-users plus the admin-plugin
        Java REST controllers under acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/
        acm-admin-plugin/.../web/api/).

    Why advanced=false (no scripted condition for manager write):
      Per AAP Section 0.5.6, the case_manager role's privileges are
      unconditional ("All", "Full access") - there is no "Assigned only"
      or other row-level filter. The manager is intentionally NOT scoped
      to a subset of cases; they have org-wide write authority because
      their job function is exactly to oversee, route, and close cases
      across all assignment boundaries. Therefore:
        - <advanced>false</advanced>      - no scripted condition
        - <condition/>                    - empty encoded query (no row filter)
        - <script/>                       - empty server-side script
      With no condition and no script, the ACL evaluates to "permit" for
      any caller who carries the x_[scope]_case_manager role. This is the
      correct semantic for the AAP's "manager has full write" requirement.
      Setting advanced=true with an empty script would be functionally
      equivalent but stylistically incorrect - the ServiceNow convention
      is to reserve advanced=true for ACLs that actually carry a scripted
      body (see, for contrast, ../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_agent_assigned.xml
      where advanced=true and the script encodes the disjunctive ownership
      check `current.assigned_agent == gs.getUserID() ||
      gs.getUser().isMemberOf(current.assigned_group)`).

    Why WRITE is granted to manager unconditionally (design rationale):
      - Cross-team routing: when a case is misclassified or an assignee
        leaves the organization, only the manager can re-route it by
        writing assigned_group / assigned_agent. Restricting manager write
        to "Assigned only" would create a chicken-and-egg problem - a
        manager could not initially assign a case because they weren't yet
        the assigned agent on it.
      - Records-management oversight: cases under audit, compliance review,
        or escalation may need their priority bumped, their description
        amended for clarity, or their requester_email corrected to enable
        outbound communication. Only managers have this editorial authority
        across all cases.
      - State-machine driver: per AAP Section 0.5.5 the Resolved -> Closed
        transition is reserved to the case_manager role - that transition
        is implemented as a write to the status column from `Resolved` to
        `Closed`, which must pass this ACL. Without this ACL no case could
        ever reach the terminal Closed state.
      - Pending-reason management: per AAP Section 0.5.5 the In Progress ->
        Pending transition allows a manager to set the pending_reason
        choice (Awaiting Info / Awaiting Third Party / Other). The write
        to pending_reason is authorized by THIS ACL.
      - Demo-data lifecycle: the seed script ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js
        runs as the platform admin (which bypasses this ACL via
        admin_overrides=true) but post-seed re-runs in interactive mode
        from the demo manager (sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_manager.xml) depend
        on this ACL being applied so the manager can manually advance a
        seeded Open or In Progress demo case to Resolved during smoke
        testing without needing the admin login.

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only context per AAP Section
    0.3.2; no code or configuration is byte-for-byte ported from these
    files):
      - acm-services/acm-service-users/src/main/java/com/armedia/acm/services/
        users/model/ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig.java
        ArkCase mapped roles to privileges through a single configuration
        map (`Map<String, List<Object>> rolesToPrivileges`) keyed by the
        property `application.rolesToPrivileges`. The class declares the
        constant `ROLES_TO_PRIVILEGES_PROP_KEY = "application.rolesToPrivileges"`
        and exposes the map via `@MapValue(value = "application.rolesToPrivileges")
        getRolesToPrivileges()`. In that model, a "manager-equivalent"
        role (e.g., ROLE_CASE_MANAGER) would have been associated with a
        write privilege identifier such as `acm-case-update` or
        `acm-case-edit`. The ServiceNow target replaces this map-based
        privilege association with declarative, scoped record-level ACLs -
        this XML record is the direct equivalent of one cell in the map:
        the (case_manager, WRITE) pairing.
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-admin-plugin/src/main/java/com/
        armedia/acm/plugins/admin/service/RolesPrivilegesService.java
        Encapsulated role-CRUD and privilege-paging behavior in ArkCase
        (`retrieveRoles()`, `retrievePrivileges()`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByAuthorization(...)`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByRole(...)`, `updateRolePrivileges(...)`,
        `addRolesPrivileges(...)`, `removeRolesPrivileges(...)`). The
        service held injected dependencies on `UserDao`, `ApplicationRolesConfig`,
        `ApplicationPrivilegesConfig`, `ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig`,
        `ConfigurationPropertyService`, `CollectionPropertiesConfigurationService`,
        and `FunctionalAccessService` - a complex Spring/JPA stack that
        managed the role <-> privilege relationship at runtime. All of
        this Java service surface is replaced in the ServiceNow target by
        the platform's built-in sys_security_acl evaluator; no scripted
        privilege resolver is needed. Notably, ArkCase's
        `updateRolePrivileges(roleName, privileges)` would have rebuilt
        the role's privilege list and persisted it via
        `configurationPropertyService.updateProperties(...)` - that
        write-time bookkeeping is, in ServiceNow, accomplished by the
        admin author of THIS XML record committing the Update Set; no
        runtime mutation is required.

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.7.1 and 0.7.2):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: every cross-reference resolves into
        the x_[scope] scope (sys_scope = x_[scope], sys_package source =
        x_[scope]). No global-scope ACLs are written. The <name> field
        references the scoped table x_[scope]_case (not the OOB `task`
        table or any other global table), and <roles> references the
        scoped role x_[scope]_case_manager. There are zero global writes
        from this file.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_id literals: <name>, <roles>,
        <sys_scope>, and <sys_package> all resolve their targets by name /
        source attribute lookup at Update Set apply time. The <sys_id>
        below is THIS record's own deterministic primary key (32-char
        lowercase hex MD5 of the canonical string
        "x_[scope]_case.write.case_manager", a stable canonical identifier
        for this exact ACL) and is not a cross-reference to any other
        record. Computing the sys_id deterministically guarantees the ACL
        is re-applyable / idempotent across fresh PDIs and round-trip
        Update Set previews per AAP Section 0.7.3 Gate 7.
      - Table-level (not field-level): <name> is `x_[scope]_case` with NO
        dot. The two field-level ACL files in this folder
        (../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_group_field_acl.xml and
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml) restrict who
        can WRITE those specific columns; they layer on top of THIS ACL
        rather than replacing it. The <type>record</type> field below
        confirms this is a row-level (table-level) ACL, not a UI/REST/SOAP-
        flavored ACL.
      - Operation = write: corresponds exactly to the "Write = All" cell
        in the AAP matrix for the case_manager role. This is the table-
        level write binding; the field-level write restrictions on
        assigned_group / assigned_agent are authored as separate ACL
        records and DO NOT override the manager's table-level grant.
      - admin_overrides = true: standard ServiceNow pattern that allows
        the platform `admin` role to bypass this ACL. This is required so
        platform administrators can troubleshoot, repair, or re-seed
        scoped data (per AAP Section 0.7.4 the seed_demo_data.js script
        runs as admin to populate demo cases). It does NOT widen
        case_manager privileges - non-admin managers see exactly what this
        ACL permits, which is full table-level write.
      - active = true: ACL is in force the moment the Update Set commits.
      - advanced = false: see "Why advanced=false" rationale above. The
        platform skips the empty <script/> body entirely.
      - condition (empty): the <condition/> encoded-query field is empty;
        no row-level filter applies to manager writes (manager has "All"
        access, not "Assigned only").
      - script (empty): the <script/> field is empty; the platform skips
        it because advanced=false.

    Difference from sibling ACLs - quick reference:
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_create_manager.xml (manager CREATE):
        - <operation>     write             vs create
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_[scope]_case.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_[scope]_case.create.case_manager")
        - <sys_update_name> *_write_manager vs *_create_manager
        - <description>                     differs in operation wording
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml (manager READ):
        - <operation>     write             vs read
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_[scope]_case.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_[scope]_case.read.case_manager")
        - <sys_update_name> *_write_manager vs *_read_manager
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_delete_manager.xml (manager DELETE):
        - <operation>     write             vs delete
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_[scope]_case.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_[scope]_case.delete.case_manager")
        - <sys_update_name> *_write_manager vs *_delete_manager
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_agent_assigned.xml (agent WRITE assigned-only):
        - <roles>         x_[scope]_case_manager
                                            vs x_[scope]_case_agent
        - <advanced>      false             vs true (the agent ACL carries a
                                              scripted condition; the manager
                                              ACL is unconditional)
        - <condition>     empty             vs encoded query for "Assigned only"
        - <script>        empty             vs server-side disjunction of
                                              assigned_agent/assigned_group checks
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_[scope]_case.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_[scope]_case.write.case_agent.assigned")
        - <sys_update_name> *_write_manager vs *_write_agent_assigned
      All other XML elements are identical between the manager-tier ACLs;
      the deterministic sys_id and the operation/role triplet are the
      defining differences.

    Cross-dependencies and Update-Set ordering (AAP Section 0.5.2):
      MUST be loaded AFTER:
        - ../app/sys_app/x_[scope]_case_management.xml (scoped app record)
        - ../app/sys_scope/x_[scope].xml (scope record - resolves
          sys_scope and sys_package source="x_[scope]")
        - ../tables/x_[scope]_case.xml (resolves <name>x_[scope]_case</name>
          by table name lookup at apply time)
        - ../roles/sys_user_role_x_[scope]_case_manager.xml (resolves
          <roles>x_[scope]_case_manager</roles> by role name lookup at
          apply time)
      MUST be loaded BEFORE:
        - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_group_field_acl.xml and
          ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml (the field-
          level ACLs build on top of this table-level ACL; loading them
          before this file would leave the manager temporarily unable to
          write the case row at all and the field-level ACLs would have
          no effect since the table-level write would deny first)
        - ../seed-data/role_assignments/sys_user_has_role_x_[scope]_demo_manager.xml
          (the demo manager's write access during round-trip verification
          depends on this ACL being applied first)
        - ../business_rules/x_[scope]_set_closed_date.xml,
          ../business_rules/x_[scope]_block_terminal_closed.xml,
          ../business_rules/x_[scope]_block_draft_backtransition.xml,
          ../business_rules/x_[scope]_validate_assigned_agent_membership.xml,
          ../business_rules/x_[scope]_clear_pending_reason_on_inprogress.xml
          (these business rules fire in the manager's session as
          before-update server-side guards on case writes; the ACL must
          authorize the write first or the business rule never runs)
        - ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml,
          ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml (Flow Designer flows fire
          on update; they depend on this ACL having authorized the
          underlying write)
        - any UI Action under ../ui_action/x_[scope]_case_*.xml that
          performs a state-machine transition on behalf of the manager
        - any cleanup or re-seed activity in ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js
          that may update prior demo cases; while seed_demo_data.js itself
          runs as admin and bypasses this ACL via admin_overrides, post-
          seed smoke tests against the demo dataset depend on this ACL
          being applied so a logged-in demo manager can validate end-to-
          end write capability.
      The deny-by-default sibling pair that this file works with:
        - x_[scope]_case_write_viewer.xml (DOES NOT EXIST - by design;
          case_viewer Write=No is enforced structurally by the absence of
          a granting ACL)
      Adding x_[scope]_case_write_viewer.xml would VIOLATE the AAP
      Section 0.5.6 matrix and MUST NOT be done by any future agent.

    The literal `[scope]` placeholder is preserved verbatim per AAP
    convention (Section 0.7.2 "Scoped-namespace-only constraint"); the
    Personal Developer Instance auto-assigns the actual concrete scope
    id at App Engine Studio creation time, and the Update-Set apply-time
    renaming propagates consistently across all bracketed placeholders
    in this artifact. The deterministic sys_id below is computed against
    the `[scope]` literal and remains stable across re-imports onto
    fresh PDIs.
-->
<record_update table="sys_security_acl">
    <sys_security_acl action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <admin_overrides>true</admin_overrides>
        <advanced>false</advanced>
        <condition/>
        <description>Table-level ACL: x_[scope]_case_manager can write all x_[scope]_case records (full write access). NOTE: field-level ACLs on assigned_group and assigned_agent further restrict those specific fields.</description>
        <name>x_[scope]_case</name>
        <operation>write</operation>
        <roles>x_[scope]_case_manager</roles>
        <script/>
        <sys_class_name>sys_security_acl</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>4aaf9511524653d8819d7b10fa5cb207</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>x_[scope]_case</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_[scope]">x_[scope]</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_[scope]</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_security_acl_x_[scope]_case_write_manager</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <type>record</type>
    </sys_security_acl>
</record_update>
