<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the table-level DELETE ACL that
    grants the scoped role `x_[scope]_case_manager` UNCONDITIONAL delete access
    on records of the `x_[scope]_case_party` custom table inside the scoped
    application `x_[scope]`. This is the DELETE companion to the case_manager
    create / read / write ACLs whose granting ACLs are materialized by the
    sibling files:
        - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_create_agent.xml
          (creation is granted to BOTH manager AND agent because the AAP
          Section 0.5.6 row for case_manager has Create=Yes; the manager grant
          is folded into a multi-role ACL that lists case_manager alongside
          case_agent so a single ACL covers the union of both creation rights)
        - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_read_agent_assigned.xml
          (manager reads via the same broader ACL pattern: read-all is
          granted to manager, read-assigned to agent — the agent-assigned
          ACL also lists manager so the union grants manager unconditional
          read access)
        - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_write_agent_assigned.xml
          (similar union: manager + agent-assigned)
    Together those four files realize the AAP Section 0.5.6 manager row
    mirrored at the case_party table level per AAP Section 0.5.1 row
    "servicenow-case-management-poc/acl/x_[scope]_case_party_*.xml"
    ("Mirror ACL pattern at party level"):
        | Role                    | Create | Read | Write | Delete |
        | x_[scope]_case_manager  |  Yes   | All  |  All  |  Yes   |

    Of the four CRUD operations, DELETE is the most-restricted on the
    case_party table: only the case_manager role gets it. There is
    intentionally NO sibling x_[scope]_case_party_delete_agent.xml file and
    NO sibling x_[scope]_case_party_delete_viewer.xml file - those two roles
    are denied delete by the ABSENCE of a granting ACL (ServiceNow
    record-level ACLs are deny-by-default; a role with no granting ACL for
    an operation cannot perform that operation). The deny is therefore
    enforced structurally - no scripted "deny" rule is required, and no
    inverse condition is encoded.

    AAP cross-references:
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - case_manager row, mirrored at the
        case_party table level per AAP Section 0.5.1 row
        "servicenow-case-management-poc/acl/x_[scope]_case_party_*.xml"
        ("Mirror ACL pattern at party level"):
            | Role                    | Create | Read | Write | Delete |
            | x_[scope]_case_manager  |  Yes   | All  |  All  |  Yes   |
        This file authors the single "Delete = Yes" cell of the manager row
        for the case_party table. Each row of the ACL matrix maps to exactly
        one or zero ACL XML files - this per-cell granularity is what lets
        the Update Set add or remove role privileges independently without
        entangling roles or operations.
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - all-roles delete coverage on case_party:
            - case_manager: Delete=Yes -> THIS FILE
            - case_agent:   Delete=No  -> deliberate absence of any
                                          x_[scope]_case_party_delete_agent.xml
            - case_viewer:  Delete=No  -> deliberate absence of any
                                          x_[scope]_case_party_delete_viewer.xml
        Together these three facts implement the user prompt's contract that
        only managers - who own records-management discipline for the entire
        case lifecycle including its child party associations - may destroy
        party records. Agents (who associate parties to assigned cases per
        AAP Section 0.4.4 Internal user UI "Related Lists on the case form
        for both case_task and case_party") and viewers (audit / compliance
        / supervisor tier with read-only access) cannot delete. This protects
        the historical audit trail of who was associated to a case in what
        role - a forensic concern that matters for the AAP Section 0.7.4
        "synthetic only" data discipline and for any future audit of case
        lifecycle integrity.
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 3 - ACLs):
            "Role-based access enforced - case_viewer cannot write; case_agent
             cannot access unassigned cases; case_manager has full access."
        The clause "case_manager has full access" requires that the manager
        role be able to perform every CRUD operation on the case_party
        table, of which delete is the fourth and most-elevated. This ACL
        satisfies that clause for the delete operation on the party domain;
        the parallel clauses about case_viewer (no write) and case_agent
        (no unassigned access) are unaffected by this ACL and are enforced
        by separate sibling ACL files (case_viewer never appears in any
        case_party write/create/delete ACL; case_agent delete on case_party
        is enforced by the deliberate absence noted above).
      - Section 0.4.3 (Design Pattern Applications - Scoped role-based
        access control): "Three named roles paired with table-level and
        field-level ACLs whose conditions are encoded as scripted ACL
        expressions, replacing ArkCase's ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig
        map." This ACL is the table-level DELETE binding for the
        highest-tier scoped role on the party domain and is one of the
        declarative facts the platform's sys_security_acl evaluator
        consumes when authorizing a row deletion at runtime against the
        case_party table.
      - Section 0.1.2 (Technical Interpretation - Access-control
        transformation): "ApplicationRolesConfig + RolesPrivilegesService +
        URL-based privilege metadata -> scoped roles + ACLs." In ArkCase the
        equivalent of THIS file would have been TWO entries in the
        rolesToPrivileges map (because ArkCase modeled person-association
        and organization-association in TWO separate tables, acm_person_assoc
        and acm_person_org_assoc) binding the manager-equivalent role to
        delete privilege identifiers such as `acm-person-association-delete`
        and `acm-organization-association-delete`, evaluated at HTTP
        request time by AcmPluginUrlPrivilege against the DELETE verb on
        the person plugin's REST endpoints. The ServiceNow target replaces
        both map bindings AND the URL-privilege evaluator with this single
        declarative ACL record - because the target's case_party table is
        polymorphic (party_type Choice = Person | Organization with
        conditional person and organization reference fields per AAP
        Section 0.4.3 Polymorphic association via single-table choice + UI
        Policy), one ACL governs delete for both Person and Organization
        variants.
      - Section 0.4.3 (Polymorphic association via single-table choice +
        UI Policy): the case_party table collapses ArkCase's two separate
        association tables (acm_person_assoc, acm_person_org_assoc) into a
        single polymorphic ServiceNow table with a `party_type` Choice
        discriminator (Person | Organization). Because both polymorphic
        sub-shapes are stored in a single physical table, a single ACL
        record (this one) governs delete access for the manager role
        across BOTH variants - there is no need for separate Person /
        Organization manager-delete ACLs. This is a deliberate
        simplification of the source ArkCase model.

    Why advanced=false (no scripted condition for delete):
      Per AAP Section 0.5.6, the case_manager role's privileges are
      unconditional ("All", "Full access") - there is no "Assigned only"
      or other row-level filter. Therefore:
        - <advanced>false</advanced>      - no scripted condition
        - <condition/>                    - empty encoded query (no row filter)
        - <script/>                       - empty server-side script
      With no condition and no script, the ACL evaluates to "permit" for
      any caller who carries the x_[scope]_case_manager role. This is the
      correct semantic for the AAP's "manager has full delete" requirement.
      Setting advanced=true with an empty script would be functionally
      equivalent but stylistically incorrect - the ServiceNow convention
      is to reserve advanced=true for ACLs that actually carry a scripted
      body (e.g., the ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_read_agent_assigned.xml
      and ../acl/x_[scope]_case_party_write_agent_assigned.xml siblings,
      which DO carry "Assigned only" filter scripts that traverse the
      case_party.case reference up to the parent case row to evaluate the
      AAP Section 0.5.6 "Assigned only" rule).

    Why DELETE is granted to manager only (design rationale):
      - Records-management discipline: case_party records are the durable
        record of every external person and organization the system ever
        associated with a case. Deletion is irreversible and removes the
        association history. Agents associate parties; viewers observe
        parties; only managers - who own the case lifecycle from intake
        to closure and bear records-management responsibility - have
        authority to remove party association records.
      - Audit trail integrity for compliance: case_party records preserve
        the "who was involved" facts for each case. The ACL Matrix at AAP
        Section 0.5.6 lists case_viewer as the "audit / compliance /
        supervisor tier" role with read-all access; that audit role's value
        depends on party association history remaining intact. Allowing
        agents to delete party rows would let any one agent silently erase
        evidence of who was associated to which case - subverting both the
        viewer's audit role and the manager's reporting view.
      - Portal anonymity contract: the external Experience Portal
        (../portal/sp_portal_x_[scope]_case_portal.xml) accepts anonymous
        case submissions through
        ../portal/rest/sys_ws_definition_x_[scope]_case_submit.xml but
        DOES NOT expose any party-level capability and DOES NOT create
        case_party rows on submission (the scripted REST submit endpoint
        only writes the parent case row with status = Draft per AAP
        Section 0.4.4 "External Experience Portal UI - Page 1 - Case
        Submission"). Anonymous callers and unauthenticated portal users
        therefore have NO scoped role at all and NO delete capability via
        this ACL. The portal contract is preserved automatically, and
        party associations remain an internal-only concern handled by
        managers and agents on the internal case form's Related List.
      - State-machine cleanup: when a case enters the terminal `Closed`
        state, the before-update business rule
        ../business_rules/x_[scope]_block_terminal_closed.xml prohibits
        further updates to that record. Deletion of party rows is a
        separate operation from update of the parent case and is governed
        by THIS ACL - only managers can purge a party record from the
        system. Agents who attempt to delete a party will receive
        ServiceNow's standard "Operation against file 'x_[scope]_case_party'
        was aborted by Access Control Rule" deny response from the
        platform.
      - Polymorphic data integrity: because the case_party table is
        polymorphic (Person | Organization variants share one table per
        AAP Section 0.4.3), allowing non-manager roles to delete would
        let an agent selectively destroy either Person or Organization
        rows independently, which could leave a case with an apparent
        "missing requester" or "missing respondent" association that
        actually existed historically. Manager-only delete preserves the
        polymorphic contract and ensures any deletion is a deliberate
        records-management decision rather than a side effect of agent
        workflow.

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only context per AAP Section
    0.3.2; no code or configuration is byte-for-byte ported from these
    files):
      - acm-services/acm-service-users/src/main/java/com/armedia/acm/
        services/users/model/ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig.java
        ArkCase mapped roles to privileges through a single configuration
        map (`Map<String, List<Object>> rolesToPrivileges`) keyed by the
        property `application.rolesToPrivileges`. In that model, a
        "manager-equivalent" role (e.g., ROLE_PERSON_MANAGER /
        ROLE_ORG_MANAGER) would have been associated with delete
        privilege identifiers such as `acm-person-association-delete`
        and `acm-organization-association-delete` (one identifier per
        association table, since ArkCase used two separate tables). The
        ServiceNow target replaces this map-based privilege association
        with declarative, scoped record-level ACLs - this XML record is
        the direct equivalent of the union of those two ArkCase map cells:
        the (case_manager, DELETE) pairing on the polymorphic case_party
        domain that subsumes both Person and Organization variants.
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-admin-plugin/src/main/java/com/
        armedia/acm/plugins/admin/service/RolesPrivilegesService.java
        Encapsulated role-CRUD and privilege-paging behavior in ArkCase
        (`retrieveRoles()`, `retrievePrivileges()`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByAuthorization(...)`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByRole(...)`, `updateRolePrivileges(...)`,
        `removeRolesPrivileges(...)`). All of this Java service surface
        is replaced in the ServiceNow target by the platform's built-in
        sys_security_acl evaluator; no scripted privilege resolver is
        needed. Notably, ArkCase's `userDao.deleteAcmRole(roleName)` call
        removed an entire role definition - that operation has no analog
        in this file because role definitions in ServiceNow are themselves
        managed by the ../roles/sys_user_role_x_[scope]_*.xml records,
        not by ACLs. THIS ACL governs the deletion of CASE_PARTY RECORDS,
        not the deletion of the role itself, and not the deletion of CASE
        records (governed by ../acl/x_[scope]_case_delete_manager.xml) or
        CASE_TASK records (governed by
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_delete_manager.xml).

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.7.1 and 0.7.2):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: every cross-reference resolves into
        the x_[scope] scope (sys_scope = x_[scope], sys_package source =
        x_[scope]). No global-scope ACLs are written. The <name> field
        references the scoped table x_[scope]_case_party (not any OOB
        global table such as `task` or `incident_task`), and <roles>
        references the scoped role x_[scope]_case_manager. There are zero
        global writes from this file.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_id literals: <name>, <roles>,
        <sys_scope>, and <sys_package> all resolve their targets by
        name / source attribute lookup at Update Set apply time. The
        <sys_id> below is THIS record's own deterministic primary key
        (MD5 of "x_[scope]_case_party.delete.case_manager", a stable
        canonical identifier for this exact ACL) and is not a
        cross-reference to any other record. Computing the sys_id
        deterministically guarantees the ACL is re-applyable / idempotent
        across fresh PDIs and round-trip Update Set previews per AAP
        Section 0.7.3 Gate 7 ("Update Set loads without errors on a fresh
        PDI instance").
      - Table-level (not field-level): <name> is `x_[scope]_case_party`
        with NO dot. ServiceNow's delete operation has no concept of
        "delete this specific column" - field-level ACLs apply only to
        read/write/none. The <type>record</type> field below confirms
        this is a row-level (table-level) ACL, not a UI/REST/SOAP-flavored
        ACL. Note that the case_party table - unlike the parent case
        table - has no field-level ACLs at all by AAP design; the
        case-table field-level ACLs on assigned_group / assigned_agent
        (../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_group_field_acl.xml and
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml) have no
        case_party analog because case_party fields (party_type, person,
        organization, role_label, case) carry no role-based write
        restrictions per AAP Section 0.5.6.
      - Operation = delete: corresponds exactly to the "Delete = Yes"
        cell in the AAP matrix for the case_manager role mirrored to the
        case_party table.
      - admin_overrides = true: standard ServiceNow pattern that allows
        the platform `admin` role to bypass this ACL. This is required
        so platform administrators can troubleshoot, repair, or remove
        scoped seed party data (per AAP Section 0.7.4 the
        ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js script can re-seed a fresh PDI; if
        a prior partial run left stale demo party rows, the admin user -
        who does NOT need the scoped case_manager role - must still be
        able to clean up). It does NOT widen case_manager privileges -
        non-admin managers see exactly what this ACL permits.
      - active = true: ACL is in force the moment the Update Set commits.
      - advanced = false: see "Why advanced=false" rationale above. The
        platform skips the empty <script/> body entirely.
      - condition (empty): the <condition/> encoded-query field is empty;
        no row-level filter applies to manager deletes (manager has
        "full" access, not "Assigned only").
      - script (empty): the <script/> field is empty; the platform skips
        it because advanced=false.

    Cross-dependencies and Update-Set ordering (AAP Section 0.5.2):
      MUST be loaded AFTER:
        - ../app/sys_app/x_[scope]_case_management.xml (scoped app record)
        - ../app/sys_scope/x_[scope].xml (scope record - resolves
          sys_scope and sys_package source="x_[scope]")
        - ../tables/x_[scope]_case_party.xml (resolves
          <name>x_[scope]_case_party</name> by table name lookup at apply
          time)
        - ../roles/sys_user_role_x_[scope]_case_manager.xml (resolves
          <roles>x_[scope]_case_manager</roles> by role name lookup at
          apply time)
      MUST be loaded BEFORE:
        - ../seed-data/role_assignments/sys_user_has_role_x_[scope]_demo_manager.xml
          (the demo manager's delete access during round-trip
          verification depends on this ACL being applied first)
        - any cleanup or re-seed activity in
          ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js that may delete prior demo party
          rows; while seed_demo_data.js itself runs as admin and
          bypasses this ACL via admin_overrides, post-seed smoke tests
          against the demo dataset depend on this ACL being applied so
          a logged-in demo manager can validate end-to-end party-delete
          capability.
      The deny-by-default sibling pairs that this file works with:
        - x_[scope]_case_party_delete_agent.xml  (DOES NOT EXIST - by design)
        - x_[scope]_case_party_delete_viewer.xml (DOES NOT EXIST - by design)
      Adding either of those files would VIOLATE the AAP Section 0.5.6
      matrix and MUST NOT be done by any future agent.

    Mirror relationship to ../acl/x_[scope]_case_delete_manager.xml and
    ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_delete_manager.xml:
      This file is the case_party-table analog of the manager-delete ACL
      already authored for the case and case_task tables. The ONLY
      differences between those files and this one are:
        - <name>             x_[scope]_case_party  (vs x_[scope]_case
                                                    or x_[scope]_case_task)
        - <sys_id>           MD5("x_[scope]_case_party.delete.case_manager")
                                                   (the deterministic key
                                                    derived from a stable
                                                    canonical identifier
                                                    unique to this ACL)
        - <sys_name>         x_[scope]_case_party  (vs x_[scope]_case
                                                    or x_[scope]_case_task)
        - <sys_update_name>  sys_security_acl_x_[scope]_case_party_delete_manager
                                                   (vs the equivalent for
                                                    case / case_task)
        - <description>      references the case_party table semantic
      All other fields (active, admin_overrides, advanced, condition,
      operation, roles, script, sys_class_name, sys_created_by, sys_policy,
      sys_scope, sys_package, type, audit timestamps) are byte-for-byte
      identical so that the manager's delete privilege is uniformly
      unconditional across every table in the scoped application as the
      AAP matrix mandates.

    The literal `[scope]` placeholder is preserved verbatim per AAP
    convention (Section 0.7.2 "Scoped-namespace-only constraint"); the
    Personal Developer Instance auto-assigns the actual concrete scope id
    at App Engine Studio creation time, and the Update-Set apply-time
    renaming propagates consistently across all bracketed placeholders in
    this artifact. The deterministic sys_id below is computed against the
    `[scope]` literal and remains stable across re-imports onto fresh
    PDIs.
-->
<record_update table="sys_security_acl">
    <sys_security_acl action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <admin_overrides>true</admin_overrides>
        <advanced>false</advanced>
        <condition/>
        <description>Allows users with the x_[scope]_case_manager role to delete case_party records. Only role with delete privilege per AAP Section 0.5.6.</description>
        <name>x_[scope]_case_party</name>
        <operation>delete</operation>
        <roles>x_[scope]_case_manager</roles>
        <script/>
        <sys_class_name>sys_security_acl</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>1f8bdcb79b5060d68ca63d034186c83a</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>x_[scope]_case_party</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_[scope]">x_[scope]</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_[scope]</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_security_acl_x_[scope]_case_party_delete_manager</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <type>record</type>
    </sys_security_acl>
</record_update>
