<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the table-level CREATE ACL that
    grants the scoped role `x_[scope]_case_manager` UNCONDITIONAL create access
    on the `x_[scope]_case` custom table inside the scoped application
    `x_[scope]`. This is the CREATE companion to the case_manager
    read / write / delete ACLs (../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml,
    ../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_manager.xml, ../acl/x_[scope]_case_delete_manager.xml)
    and together those four files materialize the AAP Section 0.5.6 row:
    "x_[scope]_case_manager : Create=Yes, Read=All, Write=All, Delete=Yes."

    The case_manager role is the highest-tier scoped role for case-management
    operations; per AAP Section 0.5.6 the manager has UNCONDITIONAL create
    privileges on the case table. CREATE is the "entry-point" privilege of
    the case lifecycle: it is the operation that brings new x_[scope]_case
    rows into existence so that every downstream privilege (read, write,
    delete) and every downstream Flow-Designer-driven state-machine
    transition (Draft -> Open -> In Progress -> Pending -> Resolved ->
    Closed per AAP Section 0.5.5) has a record to act upon. Without this
    ACL no x_[scope]_case_manager-tier user could file a new case from the
    internal native form view, and the manager would be reduced to a
    read/write/delete-only role on records originating elsewhere
    (specifically: agent submissions and external portal submissions),
    which directly contradicts the AAP matrix's "Create=Yes" cell for the
    manager row.

    AAP cross-references:
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - case_manager row (verbatim from AAP):
            | Role                    | Create | Read | Write | Delete |
            | x_[scope]_case_manager  |  Yes   | All  |  All  |  Yes   |
        This file authors the single "Create = Yes" cell. The "All" Read
        cell is authored by ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml; the
        "All" Write cell by ../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_manager.xml; the
        "Yes" Delete cell by ../acl/x_[scope]_case_delete_manager.xml. Each
        row of the ACL matrix maps to exactly one or zero ACL XML files -
        this per-cell granularity is what lets the Update Set add or remove
        role privileges independently without entangling roles or operations.
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - all-roles create coverage on x_[scope]_case:
            - case_manager: Create=Yes -> THIS FILE
            - case_agent:   Create=Yes -> ../acl/x_[scope]_case_create_agent.xml
                                          (also unconditional; per AAP both
                                           manager and agent can create)
            - case_viewer:  Create=No  -> deliberate absence of any
                                          x_[scope]_case_create_viewer.xml
                                          (deny-by-default)
        Together these three facts implement the user prompt's contract that
        managers (operational oversight tier) and agents (operational worker
        tier) can both file new cases, while the lowest-privilege viewer
        (audit / compliance / supervisor tier) cannot. The agent's create
        is paired with read/write _agent_assigned restrictions that limit
        the agent's subsequent visibility of and edits to their own
        creations to "Assigned only" rows; the manager has no such
        post-create restriction (manager Read=All, Write=All).
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 3 - ACLs):
            "Role-based access enforced - case_viewer cannot write;
             case_agent cannot access unassigned cases; case_manager has
             full access."
        The clause "case_manager has full access" requires that the manager
        role be able to perform every CRUD operation on the case table; of
        the four operations, CREATE is the operation that brings new rows
        into existence so the others have something to act upon. This ACL
        satisfies the create operation half of "full access"; the parallel
        read / write / delete halves are satisfied by the three sibling
        manager ACLs.
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 1 - Data model):
            "All 3 custom tables created with correct fields and types -
             Zero missing mandatory fields."
        Part of validating the data model is end-to-end exercising the
        case form by creating a new case row and confirming every
        mandatory field round-trips correctly into the database. The demo
        manager (../seed-data/users/sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_manager.xml)
        executes that exercise during the round-trip-verify phase per
        ../docs/validation-gates.md, and THIS ACL is what authorizes that
        manager-as-creator session.
      - Section 0.7.4 (Other User-Provided Rules) - "Cases created,
        assigned, progressed through all defined states, and closed via
        both internal UI and external portal." This success-criterion
        bullet implies authenticated case_manager users must be able to
        create cases via the internal native form view; THIS ACL is what
        makes that path permitted.
      - Section 0.5.5 (State-Machine Transition Map): Every case begins in
        the Draft state. The state machine then drives Draft -> Open ->
        In Progress -> (Pending) -> Resolved -> Closed. The very first
        operation in this lifecycle is the INSERT that produces the Draft
        row; this ACL authorizes that insert when the caller carries the
        x_[scope]_case_manager role. Without it the manager could only
        ever observe and edit cases originated by agents or by the
        external portal - the management tier could never originate cases
        themselves, which would be a glaring gap in operational coverage.
      - Section 0.4.3 (Design Pattern Applications - Scoped role-based
        access control): "Three named roles paired with table-level and
        field-level ACLs whose conditions are encoded as scripted ACL
        expressions, replacing ArkCase's ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig
        map." This ACL is the table-level CREATE binding for the
        highest-tier scoped role and is one of the declarative facts the
        platform's sys_security_acl evaluator consumes when authorizing a
        row insert at runtime.
      - Section 0.1.2 (Technical Interpretation - Access-control
        transformation): "ApplicationRolesConfig + RolesPrivilegesService +
        URL-based privilege metadata -> scoped roles + ACLs." In ArkCase
        the equivalent of THIS file would have been a single entry in the
        rolesToPrivileges map binding the manager-equivalent role
        (e.g., ROLE_CASE_MANAGER) to a privilege identifier such as
        `acm-case-create` or `acm-case-add`, evaluated at HTTP request
        time by AcmPluginUrlPrivilege against the POST verb on the
        casefile REST endpoint. The ServiceNow target replaces both the
        map binding and the URL-privilege evaluator with this single
        declarative ACL record; the platform's sys_security_acl engine
        handles the role-membership check, condition evaluation (none here
        because manager create is unconditional), and admin-override logic
        that ArkCase implemented through hand-written Java code (see
        acm-services/acm-service-users plus the admin-plugin Java REST
        controllers under acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-admin-plugin/
        .../web/api/).

    Why <advanced>false</advanced> (no scripted condition for manager create):
      Per AAP Section 0.5.6, the case_manager role's privileges are
      unconditional ("Yes", "All", "Full access") - there is no "Assigned
      only" or other row-level filter. The manager is intentionally NOT
      scoped to a subset of cases; they have org-wide create authority
      because their job function is to originate, triage, route,
      prioritize, escalate, and close cases across all assignment
      boundaries. Additionally, the create operation has no `current`
      record to evaluate row-level predicates against - the row is being
      inserted at the moment the ACL fires, so any "Assigned only"-style
      check is logically impossible at create time (assigned_agent /
      assigned_group on the freshly-instantiated record skeleton are
      typically null until the manager populates them, making any predicate
      meaningless and noisy). For these two reasons - design intent and
      logical inapplicability - the manager create ACL is unconditional:
        - <advanced>false</advanced>      - no scripted condition
        - <condition/>                    - empty encoded query (no row filter)
        - <script/>                       - empty server-side script
      With no condition and no script, the ACL evaluates to "permit" for
      any caller who carries the x_[scope]_case_manager role. This is the
      correct semantic for the AAP's "manager has full create" requirement.
      Setting advanced=true with an empty script would be functionally
      equivalent but stylistically incorrect - the ServiceNow convention
      is to reserve advanced=true for ACLs that actually carry a scripted
      body (see, for contrast,
      ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_agent_assigned.xml and
      ../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_agent_assigned.xml where advanced=true
      and the script encodes the disjunctive ownership check
      `current.assigned_agent == gs.getUserID() ||
      gs.getUser().isMemberOf(current.assigned_group)`).

    Why CREATE is granted to manager unconditionally (design rationale):
      - Operational origination: managers must be able to file new cases
        on behalf of requesters who reach out through unsupported channels
        (phone, in-person, email forwarded from another team), to record
        retro-active findings during audit reviews, and to seed test /
        demo data while validating the application. Restricting manager
        create would defeat one of the primary use-cases of the manager
        role, which is to be the "complete" case-management persona.
      - State-machine entry point: per AAP Section 0.5.5 every case
        lifecycle begins with a Draft insert. The manager is authorized
        to drive every transition in the matrix (including the
        manager-only Resolved -> Closed transition); to drive a transition
        the case must first exist - which means the manager must be able
        to insert it. This ACL closes the loop by authorizing that initial
        insert.
      - Demo-data lifecycle: the seed script ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js
        creates ten demo cases spanning all six statuses and both case
        types (AAP Section 0.4.1 / Section 0.7.4). The script itself runs
        as the platform admin (so admin_overrides=true bypasses every
        per-role ACL during seeding), but the manual round-trip-verify
        path that exercises ../docs/validation-gates.md Gate 1 has a
        logged-in demo manager create at least one fresh case to confirm
        the form, mandatory-field validation, auto-numbering
        (CASE0000001 format per ../numbers/sys_number_x_[scope]_case.xml),
        and opened_date auto-population (per
        ../business_rules/x_[scope]_set_opened_date.xml) all work
        end-to-end. THIS ACL is what authorizes that manager-as-creator
        session.
      - Self-service intake fallback: the AAP provides an external
        Experience Portal for unauthenticated requesters to submit cases
        (per AAP Section 0.4.4 / ../portal/pages/sp_page_x_[scope]_case_submit.xml),
        but that portal runs server-side under the platform-default
        elevated context, not under any scoped role. Internal users still
        need to be able to file cases when the portal is not the right
        channel; the manager (and the agent, per the parallel
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_create_agent.xml) is the internal-channel
        creator. This ACL realizes the manager half of that channel.
      - No "Assigned only" semantic at create time: as noted above, the
        platform binds `current` to a freshly-instantiated record skeleton
        with the caller's POSTed field values at create-ACL evaluation
        time. assigned_agent and assigned_group on that skeleton are
        typically null (or whatever the form defaulted them to), so any
        "Assigned only"-style predicate would either always-permit or
        always-deny based on those nulls - neither of which expresses any
        meaningful authorization rule. The AAP design pattern in Section
        0.4.3 reserves the "Assigned only" predicate for read/write ACLs
        (siblings ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_agent_assigned.xml and
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_agent_assigned.xml carry the scripted
        condition); create is correctly modeled as a binary role check.

    What governs the row AFTER the manager creates it:
      The newly-inserted Draft row is governed downstream by:
        (a) The before-insert business rule
            ../business_rules/x_[scope]_set_opened_date.xml, which
            auto-populates opened_date = gs.nowDateTime() on every
            successful insert (per AAP Section 0.5.7 the opened_date
            field is "Auto-set on creation").
        (b) The dictionary defaults established in
            ../dictionary/x_[scope]_case_status.xml, which set the
            default status to "Draft" so any newly-inserted row that
            does not explicitly set status lands in the Draft state
            (per AAP Section 0.5.5 the Draft state is the canonical
            entry point of the lifecycle).
        (c) The dictionary defaults in
            ../dictionary/x_[scope]_case_number.xml combined with
            ../numbers/sys_number_x_[scope]_case.xml, which auto-assign
            a unique CASE0000001-format number (read-only, per AAP
            Section 0.5.7).
        (d) The field-level ACL on `assigned_group`
            (../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_group_field_acl.xml), which
            permits the manager to write the assigned_group column at
            create time (the agent cannot, per the field-level ACL's
            role list). This is what lets the manager originate a case
            already pre-routed to a queue.
        (e) The field-level ACL on `assigned_agent`
            (../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml), which
            permits the manager (and the assigned agent later) to write
            the assigned_agent column. This lets the manager originate a
            case already pre-assigned to a specific worker if desired.
        (f) The before-update business rule
            ../business_rules/x_[scope]_validate_assigned_agent_membership.xml,
            which enforces that assigned_agent is a member of
            assigned_group on every update (and is bypassed at create
            because Glide before-INSERT business rules check this
            invariant separately).
        (g) The two case-type Flow Designer flows
            ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml and
            ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml, which fire on update
            (status change) and validate every transition rule from AAP
            Section 0.5.5. Those flows do NOT fire at create time
            (status starts in Draft and stays Draft until the first
            update).
      In short: this ACL is the gate to bring the row into existence; the
      seven artifacts above are what shape its initial state and govern
      its subsequent lifecycle. The composition of (this ACL) + (the
      manager field-level ACL grants on assigned_group / assigned_agent)
      is what gives the manager the unique ability to originate a fully
      pre-routed case in a single insert - an authority that the agent
      role does NOT have (the agent's create lands the case in pure Draft
      because the agent is denied write on assigned_group at field level).

    Why a separate file per role (instead of one create ACL with both roles):
      ServiceNow allows multiple roles in a single <roles> field as a
      comma-separated list, and that pattern technically also satisfies
      the AAP. However, the established convention in this Update Set
      (and in industry practice for scoped applications) is one ACL
      record per (table, operation, role) triple. Reasons:
        - Single-responsibility: each ACL record encodes exactly one
          authorization fact; if the AAP later removes case_manager's
          create privilege (e.g., to enforce a stricter intake-via-portal-
          only policy at a future iteration), the change is a single-file
          deletion with no risk of accidentally also revoking
          case_agent's create privilege.
        - Auditability: the file inventory under ../acl/ becomes a
          self-documenting matrix - the presence or absence of a file
          named x_[scope]_<table>_<operation>_<role>.xml is the answer to
          "does role X have privilege Y on table Z?". Reviewers can
          inspect the AAP matrix in Section 0.5.6 and verify in seconds
          that every "Yes" cell has a corresponding XML file and every
          "No" cell has a corresponding ABSENCE.
        - Update Set diff clarity: when the Update Set is re-imported on
          a fresh PDI per AAP Section 0.7.3 Gate 7, each ACL is a discrete
          row in the preview screen, making it easy to spot that
          case_manager's create privilege was installed (alongside
          case_agent's) versus a single combined row that would obscure
          the role membership.
      The companion ../acl/x_[scope]_case_create_agent.xml file authors
      the case_agent half of the Create=Yes pair using the same
      per-role-per-operation pattern.

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only context per AAP Section
    0.3.2; no code or configuration is byte-for-byte ported from these
    files):
      - acm-services/acm-service-users/src/main/java/com/armedia/acm/services/
        users/model/ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig.java
        ArkCase mapped roles to privileges through a single configuration
        map (`Map<String, List<Object>> rolesToPrivileges`) keyed by the
        property `application.rolesToPrivileges`. The class declares the
        constant `ROLES_TO_PRIVILEGES_PROP_KEY = "application.rolesToPrivileges"`
        and exposes the map via `@MapValue(value = "application.rolesToPrivileges")
        getRolesToPrivileges()`. In that model, a "manager-equivalent"
        role (e.g., ROLE_CASE_MANAGER) would have been associated with
        a create privilege identifier such as `acm-case-create` or
        `acm-case-add`. The ServiceNow target replaces this map-based
        privilege association with declarative, scoped record-level ACLs -
        this XML record is the direct equivalent of one cell in the map:
        the (case_manager, CREATE) pairing.
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-admin-plugin/src/main/java/com/
        armedia/acm/plugins/admin/service/RolesPrivilegesService.java
        Encapsulated role-CRUD and privilege-paging behavior in ArkCase
        (`retrieveRoles()`, `retrievePrivileges()`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByAuthorization(...)`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByRole(...)`, `updateRolePrivileges(...)`,
        `addRolesPrivileges(...)`, `removeRolesPrivileges(...)`, plus
        the role-name normalization step that uppercased the role,
        replaced whitespace with underscores, replaced periods with
        double-underscores, and prepended the `ROLE_` prefix from
        RolePrivilegesConstants). The service held injected dependencies
        on `UserDao`, `ApplicationRolesConfig`,
        `ApplicationPrivilegesConfig`,
        `ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig`,
        `ConfigurationPropertyService`,
        `CollectionPropertiesConfigurationService`, and
        `FunctionalAccessService` - a complex Spring/JPA stack that
        managed the role <-> privilege relationship at runtime. All of
        this Java service surface is replaced in the ServiceNow target
        by the platform's built-in sys_security_acl evaluator and by
        static role names declared in scope-prefixed sys_user_role
        records (the case_manager role is declared in
        ../roles/sys_user_role_x_[scope]_case_manager.xml; this ACL
        references it by literal name in the <roles> field). Notably,
        ArkCase's `retrievePrivilegesByRole(roleName)` method paginated
        through the rolesToPrivileges map to return a role's privileges -
        the ServiceNow analog is the platform's "Roles" related list on
        sys_security_acl, which is automatically derived from the
        <roles> field of every ACL record like THIS one; no explicit
        query service is needed.

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.7.1 and 0.7.2):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: every cross-reference resolves into
        the x_[scope] scope (sys_scope = x_[scope], sys_package source =
        x_[scope]). No global-scope ACLs are written. The <name> field
        references the scoped table x_[scope]_case (NOT the OOB `task`
        table or any other global table), and <roles> references the
        scoped role x_[scope]_case_manager. There are zero global writes
        from this file. Per AAP Section 0.3.2 "Global scope changes of
        any kind" are explicitly prohibited.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_id literals: <name>, <roles>,
        <sys_scope>, and <sys_package> all resolve their targets by name /
        source attribute lookup at Update Set apply time. The <sys_id>
        below is THIS record's own deterministic primary key (32-char
        lowercase hex MD5 of the canonical string
        "x_[scope]_case.create.case_manager", a stable canonical
        identifier for this exact ACL) and is not a cross-reference to
        any other record. Computing the sys_id deterministically
        guarantees the ACL is re-applyable / idempotent across fresh PDIs
        and round-trip Update Set previews per AAP Section 0.7.3 Gate 7,
        and matches the sibling-ACL convention:
          - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml uses
            MD5("x_[scope]_case.read.case_manager")
            = 113c23bfb587d172b83db7ac8961ade2
          - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_manager.xml uses
            MD5("x_[scope]_case.write.case_manager")
            = 4aaf9511524653d8819d7b10fa5cb207
          - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_delete_manager.xml uses
            MD5("x_[scope]_case.delete.case_manager")
            = 704775b2c264cae37cdc984ee173d307
          - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_create_agent.xml uses
            MD5("x_[scope]_case.create.case_agent")
            = 8ae51c961898321cb00dc4018d7e88d5
          - ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_viewer.xml uses
            MD5("x_[scope]_case.read.case_viewer")
            = 72b5af7b98b41a8cbe6101ffc5a034b2
          - this file uses MD5("x_[scope]_case.create.case_manager")
            = 225e62a69110cad11ec91010e2a8b380
        The canonical-string convention is "<table>.<operation>.<role>"
        where <role> uses the role's short suffix (case_manager,
        case_agent, case_viewer) so the strings remain stable even if
        the [scope] placeholder is later substituted for the concrete
        PDI-assigned scope id (the substitution applies uniformly across
        every reference in this file at Update Set apply time and does
        not affect the canonical-string-to-sys_id mapping).
      - Table-level (not field-level): <name> is `x_[scope]_case` with NO
        dot. ServiceNow's create operation has no concept of "create this
        specific column" - field-level ACLs apply only to read/write/none.
        Field-level write restrictions on assigned_group / assigned_agent
        are declared in
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_group_field_acl.xml and
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml; they govern
        the WRITE operation on those specific columns AFTER the row
        exists, not the table-level CREATE operation that THIS ACL
        governs. The <type>record</type> field below confirms this is a
        row-level (table-level) ACL, not a UI/REST/SOAP-flavored ACL.
      - Operation = create: corresponds exactly to the "Create = Yes"
        cell in the AAP matrix for the case_manager role. There is
        deliberately no field-level create restriction for any role on
        any column; field-level ACLs in ServiceNow apply only to read
        and write operations.
      - admin_overrides = true: standard ServiceNow pattern that allows
        the platform `admin` role to bypass this ACL. This is required so
        platform administrators can troubleshoot, repair, or seed scoped
        data (per AAP Section 0.7.4 the seed_demo_data.js script runs as
        admin to populate demo cases). It does NOT widen case_manager
        privileges - non-admin managers see exactly what this ACL
        permits, which is unconditional table-level create.
      - active = true: ACL is in force the moment the Update Set commits.
      - advanced = false: see "Why advanced=false" rationale above. The
        platform skips the empty <script/> body entirely.
      - condition (empty): the <condition/> encoded-query field is empty;
        no row-level filter applies (and none is meaningful pre-insert).
      - script (empty): the <script/> field is empty; the platform skips
        it because advanced=false.
      - description: a single-sentence operator-readable summary of what
        this ACL grants, mirroring the description style of the sibling
        manager ACLs. The description is surfaced in the System Security
        > Access Control list view and aids platform administrators
        during ACL audits without their needing to re-read the full
        canonical comment block above.
      - sys_class_name = sys_security_acl: matches the table name
        declared in <record_update table="sys_security_acl">; this is the
        ServiceNow convention for self-identifying record class on
        polymorphic-able tables (sys_security_acl itself is not currently
        polymorphic but the class name field is included for forward
        compatibility and for Update Set serialization completeness).
      - sys_created_by / sys_updated_by = admin: synthetic audit values
        that do not carry any PII; the literal "admin" string is the
        ServiceNow built-in admin user name (looked up by user_name at
        apply time; no admin sys_id literal is hardcoded).
      - sys_created_on / sys_updated_on = 2025-01-01 00:00:00: a fixed
        sentinel timestamp that ensures byte-stable Update Set XML output
        across re-exports of the same scoped application; this avoids
        spurious diffs in version control when the only "change" would
        be the auto-updated timestamp.
      - sys_mod_count = 0: starts at zero on first apply; the platform
        increments it on subsequent updates after the Update Set commits.

    Difference from sibling ACLs - quick reference:
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml (manager READ):
        - <operation>     create             vs read
        - <sys_id>        225e62a69110cad11ec91010e2a8b380
                                             vs 113c23bfb587d172b83db7ac8961ade2
        - <sys_update_name> *_create_manager vs *_read_manager
        - <description>                      differs in operation wording
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_write_manager.xml (manager WRITE):
        - <operation>     create             vs write
        - <sys_id>        225e62a69110cad11ec91010e2a8b380
                                             vs 4aaf9511524653d8819d7b10fa5cb207
        - <sys_update_name> *_create_manager vs *_write_manager
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_delete_manager.xml (manager DELETE):
        - <operation>     create             vs delete
        - <sys_id>        225e62a69110cad11ec91010e2a8b380
                                             vs 704775b2c264cae37cdc984ee173d307
        - <sys_update_name> *_create_manager vs *_delete_manager
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_create_agent.xml (agent CREATE -
      same operation):
        - <roles>         x_[scope]_case_manager
                                             vs x_[scope]_case_agent
        - <sys_id>        225e62a69110cad11ec91010e2a8b380
                                             vs 8ae51c961898321cb00dc4018d7e88d5
        - <sys_update_name> *_create_manager vs *_create_agent
        - <description>                      refers to manager  vs agent
        Both files have advanced=false, empty condition, and empty script
        because both manager and agent have unconditional create per the
        AAP matrix (the AAP intentionally puts manager and agent in the
        same Create=Yes bucket because both internal-tier roles need to
        be able to originate cases; only the audit-tier viewer is denied
        create). The two files are functionally parallel and together
        give the manager and agent roles identical create authority on
        x_[scope]_case; the post-create access asymmetry between the two
        roles is enforced by the read/write _agent_assigned scoping on
        the agent and by the manager-only field-level write grant on
        assigned_group.
      All other XML elements are identical between the manager-tier
      ACLs; the deterministic sys_id and the operation/role triplet are
      the defining differences. This is intentional: the homogeneity of
      the per-cell ACL files is what makes the matrix-style review
      tractable for both human auditors and automated diff tools.

    Cross-dependencies and Update-Set ordering (AAP Section 0.5.2):
      MUST be loaded AFTER:
        - ../app/sys_app/x_[scope]_case_management.xml (scoped app record;
          establishes the case-management application that owns this ACL)
        - ../app/sys_scope/x_[scope].xml (scope record - resolves
          sys_scope and sys_package source="x_[scope]")
        - ../tables/x_[scope]_case.xml (resolves
          <name>x_[scope]_case</name> by table name lookup at apply
          time; without the table being present first, this ACL would
          be orphaned and the Update Set preview would error)
        - ../roles/sys_user_role_x_[scope]_case_manager.xml (resolves
          <roles>x_[scope]_case_manager</roles> by role name lookup at
          apply time)
      MUST be loaded BEFORE:
        - ../seed-data/role_assignments/sys_user_has_role_x_[scope]_demo_manager.xml
          (the demo manager's create access during round-trip
          verification depends on this ACL being applied first; the
          seed step that grants the demo manager their role makes the
          create privilege effective)
        - ../seed-data/cases/x_[scope]_case_demo_*.xml (demo cases
          inserted by the seed pass need this ACL in place if any seed
          runs under the demo manager's identity context; the
          seed_demo_data.js script itself runs as admin so
          admin_overrides=true bypasses this ACL during seeding, but
          post-seed manager-side smoke tests against the demo dataset
          depend on this ACL being applied)
        - ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml,
          ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml (Flow Designer flows
          fire on UPDATE not CREATE, so they do not directly depend on
          this ACL; however they evaluate transitions on cases that
          must first exist - and the manager-originated cases that
          exercise the entire state machine depend on this ACL having
          authorized the original insert)
        - ../portal/rest/sys_ws_definition_x_[scope]_case_submit.xml
          (the scripted REST endpoint for the external portal runs
          server-side under the platform's elevated context, so it
          does not strictly depend on this manager-role ACL for its
          insert; however the ACL is loaded earlier in the Update Set
          ordering anyway because all ACLs are conventionally placed
          before scripted REST endpoints)
        - ../business_rules/x_[scope]_set_opened_date.xml (the
          before-insert business rule that sets opened_date fires
          AFTER the platform's ACL evaluator authorizes the insert; if
          this ACL did not authorize the manager's insert, the
          business rule would never fire and opened_date would never
          be auto-populated)
      The deny-by-default sibling pair that this file works with:
        - There is NO equivalent "deny" ACL needed for any role;
          ServiceNow ACLs are deny-by-default. A user without the
          case_manager role (and without case_agent) cannot insert
          rows on x_[scope]_case regardless of any per-role ACL state.
          Specifically: the case_viewer role cannot create cases
          because there is NO x_[scope]_case_create_viewer.xml file in
          this folder - the absence is the deny.

    The literal `[scope]` placeholder is preserved verbatim per AAP
    convention (Section 0.7.2 "Scoped-namespace-only constraint"); the
    Personal Developer Instance auto-assigns the actual concrete scope
    id at App Engine Studio creation time, and the Update-Set apply-time
    renaming propagates consistently across all bracketed placeholders
    in this artifact. The deterministic sys_id below is computed against
    the `[scope]` literal and remains stable across re-imports onto
    fresh PDIs.
-->
<record_update table="sys_security_acl">
    <sys_security_acl action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <admin_overrides>true</admin_overrides>
        <advanced>false</advanced>
        <condition/>
        <description>Table-level ACL: x_[scope]_case_manager can create x_[scope]_case records (full create access).</description>
        <name>x_[scope]_case</name>
        <operation>create</operation>
        <roles>x_[scope]_case_manager</roles>
        <script/>
        <sys_class_name>sys_security_acl</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>225e62a69110cad11ec91010e2a8b380</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>x_[scope]_case</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_[scope]">x_[scope]</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_[scope]</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_security_acl_x_[scope]_case_create_manager</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <type>record</type>
    </sys_security_acl>
</record_update>

