<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the table-level READ ACL that
    grants the scoped role `x_[scope]_case_manager` UNCONDITIONAL read access
    on records of the `x_[scope]_case_task` custom table inside the scoped
    application `x_[scope]`. This is the READ companion to the case_manager
    create / write / delete ACLs on the case_task table (whose granting ACLs
    are materialized by the sibling files
    ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_create_manager.xml,
    ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_write_manager.xml, and
    ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_delete_manager.xml). Together those four files
    realize the AAP Section 0.5.6 manager row mirrored at the case_task table
    level per AAP Section 0.5.1 row "servicenow-case-management-poc/acl/
    x_[scope]_case_task_*.xml" ("Mirror ACL pattern at task level"):
    "x_[scope]_case_manager : Create=Yes, Read=All, Write=All, Delete=Yes."

    The case_manager role is the highest-tier scoped role for case-management
    operations; per AAP Section 0.5.6 the manager has UNRESTRICTED read
    privileges on every case_task row regardless of which agent the task is
    currently assigned to (case_task.assigned_to), what type of work it
    represents (case_task.type), what stage it is in (case_task.status), or
    which parent case it belongs to (case_task.case). Read is the foundation
    privilege on which every other manager privilege builds: a manager cannot
    triage, route, prioritize, escalate, or close an individual task without
    first being able to see it, and they cannot drive the parent case's
    In Progress -> Resolved transition (which is gated by the AAP Section
    0.5.5 rule "All linked x_[scope]_case_task records have status = Closed",
    enforced by ../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml and
    ../script_includes/x_[scope]_CaseTransitionValidator.xml) without first
    READING the children of that case to count any non-Closed rows. This
    file is therefore the prerequisite ACL for every other manager-tier
    capability on the task domain.

    AAP cross-references:
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - case_manager row, mirrored at the
        case_task table level per AAP Section 0.5.1 row
        "servicenow-case-management-poc/acl/x_[scope]_case_task_*.xml"
        ("Mirror ACL pattern at task level"):
            | Role                    | Create | Read | Write | Delete |
            | x_[scope]_case_manager  |  Yes   | All  |  All  |  Yes   |
        This file authors the single "Read = All" cell of the manager row
        for the case_task table. The "Yes" Create cell is authored by
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_create_manager.xml; the "All" Write cell
        by ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_write_manager.xml; the "Yes" Delete
        cell by ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_delete_manager.xml. Each row of
        the ACL matrix maps to exactly one or zero ACL XML files - this
        per-cell granularity is what lets the Update Set add or remove role
        privileges independently without entangling roles or operations.
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - all-roles read coverage on case_task:
            - case_manager: Read=All           -> THIS FILE
            - case_agent:   Read=Assigned only -> ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_read_agent_assigned.xml
                                                  (carries the row-level filter
                                                   that dereferences current.case
                                                   and applies the parent-case
                                                   "Assigned only" predicate
                                                   "parentCase.assigned_agent =
                                                    current user OR
                                                    parentCase.assigned_group
                                                    contains current user")
            - case_viewer:  Read=All           -> ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_read_viewer.xml
                                                  (also unconditional - viewer
                                                   is the audit / supervisor tier)
        Together these three facts implement the user prompt's contract:
        the manager and viewer both see every task unconditionally (manager
        for operational oversight and reporting accuracy, viewer for audit
        / compliance review); the agent's read scope is narrowed to "Assigned
        only" so agents see only the tasks belonging to cases they are
        entitled to work on. The deny-by-default nature of ServiceNow record
        ACLs means a user with NO scoped role sees zero rows on the case_task
        table; the three read ACLs combined give each role exactly its
        prescribed visibility on the task domain.
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - relationship between this table-level
        read ACL and the case_task table's field-level ACLs:
        the case_task table has NO field-level ACLs in this scoped
        application. Per AAP Section 0.3.1 field-level ACLs are authored
        ONLY for the x_[scope]_case columns assigned_group and assigned_agent
        (sibling files ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_group_field_acl.xml
        and ../acl/x_[scope]_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml). The
        case_task columns case / subject / type / status / assigned_to /
        due_date are governed solely by table-level ACLs; therefore this
        READ ACL alone determines the manager's column-level read authority
        on EVERY column of the case_task table. There is no field-level
        layer that could narrow the columns visible to a manager.
      - Section 0.5.5 (State-Machine Transition Map) - manager-driven case
        and task operations that depend on this ACL:
            - "In Progress -> Resolved: All linked x_[scope]_case_task
               records have status = Closed". The case-resolution gate is
               implemented by the
               ../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml subflow,
               which queries child task rows via GlideRecord against
               x_[scope]_case_task with the encoded query
               `case=current.sys_id^status!=closed`. To execute that query
               on behalf of a manager driving the parent case from In
               Progress to Resolved, the platform's ACL evaluator must
               permit the manager to READ the child rows. THIS ACL
               authorizes that read unconditionally; the parallel
               ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_read_agent_assigned.xml file
               authorizes the same read for case_agent, but only on tasks
               whose parent case the agent is "Assigned" to.
            - "Resolved -> Closed: Caller has x_[scope]_case_manager role;
               auto-set closed_date." Closing a parent case requires the
               manager to FIRST confirm all child tasks remained Closed
               between the Resolved transition and the Close transition;
               that confirmation is itself a read against case_task
               authorized by THIS ACL.
            - "Any forward transition" by the manager: every UI Action and
               flow-driven transition begins with the manager opening a
               case form, which in turn loads the case's "Tasks" related
               list. That related-list load executes a GlideList query
               against case_task that is filtered by THIS ACL.
        The transition rules are validated by the two case-type Flow
        Designer flows ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml and
        ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml plus the supporting subflows
        under ../flows/sub_flows/; those flows fire AFTER the platform's
        ACL evaluator has authorized the underlying read, so this ACL is
        a prerequisite to the flow ever running for a manager.
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 3 - ACLs):
            "Role-based access enforced - case_viewer cannot write;
             case_agent cannot access unassigned cases; case_manager has
             full access."
        The clause "case_manager has full access" requires that the manager
        role be able to perform every CRUD operation on the case_task table;
        of the four operations, READ is the most-frequent and the entry
        point to all interactive workflows. This ACL satisfies that clause
        for the read operation on the task domain; the parallel clauses
        about case_viewer (which also reads all per the matrix - the AAP
        only restricts case_viewer from WRITE / CREATE / DELETE) and
        case_agent (read-restricted to "Assigned only" via parent-case
        dereference) are unaffected by this ACL and are enforced by
        separate sibling ACL files.
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 2 - Workflow):
            "All state transitions enforced for both case types - Invalid
             transitions return blocking error; task-closure check blocks
             Resolved transition."
        The "task-closure check" in the second clause is implemented as
        a GlideRecord query against x_[scope]_case_task during the
        validate_resolved_transition subflow. When that subflow fires on
        behalf of a manager, the GlideRecord MUST be allowed to traverse
        every child task to count non-Closed rows; THIS ACL is the
        underlying authorization that lets the count complete accurately.
        Without this ACL the count would be ACL-filtered to zero (no
        manager-readable rows), which would falsely permit an
        In Progress -> Resolved transition even when open tasks remain -
        directly breaking Validation Gate 2.
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 1 - Data model):
            "All 3 custom tables created with correct fields and types -
             Zero missing mandatory fields."
        This validation is performed in part by a logged-in test user
        opening the case form to inspect the related-list of tasks. The
        validation plan in ../docs/validation-gates.md exercises the demo
        manager (../seed-data/users/sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_manager.xml)
        reading each demo case's task list to verify all six case_task
        fields render correctly (case, subject, type, status, assigned_to,
        due_date - per AAP Section 0.5.7). Every one of those reads is
        authorized by THIS ACL.
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 6 - Dashboards):
            "Both dashboards render with synthetic data - All widgets
             display data; no broken report references."
        The Agent Workspace dashboard
        (../dashboards/pa_dashboards_x_[scope]_agent_workspace.xml)
        composes a "My overdue tasks" list widget powered by
        ../reports/x_[scope]_my_overdue_tasks.xml. That report is also
        rendered for the demo manager during the validation walkthrough
        (the manager has visibility into every overdue task across the
        organization). The report's underlying GlideRecord query against
        x_[scope]_case_task is evaluated against this ACL on every row;
        any restriction here would cause the dashboard to under-count
        manager-visible overdue tasks and the dashboard validation would
        fail. Manager Read=All is therefore required for accurate
        organization-wide task aggregates as well.
      - Section 0.4.3 (Design Pattern Applications - Scoped role-based
        access control): "Three named roles paired with table-level and
        field-level ACLs whose conditions are encoded as scripted ACL
        expressions, replacing ArkCase's ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig
        map." This ACL is the table-level READ binding for the highest-tier
        scoped role on the task domain, and is one of the declarative facts
        the platform's sys_security_acl evaluator consumes when authorizing
        a row read at runtime.
      - Section 0.1.2 (Technical Interpretation - Access-control
        transformation): "ApplicationRolesConfig + RolesPrivilegesService +
        URL-based privilege metadata -> scoped roles + ACLs." In ArkCase
        the equivalent of THIS file would have been a single entry in the
        rolesToPrivileges map binding a manager-equivalent role
        (e.g., ROLE_CASE_MANAGER or ROLE_TASK_MANAGER) to a privilege
        identifier such as `acm-task-read` or `acm-task-view`, evaluated
        at HTTP request time by AcmPluginUrlPrivilege against the GET verb
        on the task REST endpoint. The ServiceNow target replaces both
        the map binding and the URL-privilege evaluator with this single
        declarative ACL record; the platform's sys_security_acl engine
        handles the role-membership check, condition evaluation, and
        admin-override logic that ArkCase implemented through hand-written
        Java code (see acm-services/acm-service-users plus the
        admin-plugin Java REST controllers under
        acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-admin-plugin/.../web/api/).
      - Section 0.5.1 (File-by-File Transformation Plan): the row
        "servicenow-case-management-poc/acl/x_[scope]_case_task_*.xml"
        with "Mirror ACL pattern at task level". This file is the
        manager-read instance of that mirror.

    Why advanced=false (no scripted condition for manager read on case_task):
      Per AAP Section 0.5.6, the case_manager role's privileges are
      unconditional ("All", "Full access") - there is no "Assigned only"
      or other row-level filter. The manager is intentionally NOT scoped
      to a subset of tasks; they have org-wide read authority because
      their job function is exactly to oversee, route, and close tasks
      across all assignment boundaries. Therefore:
        - <advanced>false</advanced>      - no scripted condition
        - <condition/>                    - empty encoded query (no row filter)
        - <script/>                       - empty server-side script
      With no condition and no script, the ACL evaluates to "permit" for
      any caller who carries the x_[scope]_case_manager role. This is the
      correct semantic for the AAP's "manager has full read" requirement.
      Setting advanced=true with an empty script would be functionally
      equivalent but stylistically incorrect - the ServiceNow convention
      is to reserve advanced=true for ACLs that actually carry a scripted
      body (see, for contrast,
      ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_read_agent_assigned.xml where
      advanced=true and the script encodes the parent-case-dereferenced
      disjunctive ownership check
      `parent.assigned_agent == gs.getUserID() ||
       gs.getUser().isMemberOf(parent.assigned_group)`).

    Why READ is granted to manager unconditionally on case_task (design
    rationale):
      - Operational oversight: managers must see every task to triage
        intake, balance individual workloads across agents, identify
        overdue or stuck tasks, escalate priority items, and re-assign
        tasks abandoned by departing agents. Restricting manager read to
        "Assigned only" would defeat the entire purpose of having a
        manager tier on the task domain - they would only see tasks
        someone else had already routed to them, and by definition they
        could not RE-ROUTE tasks between agents (the WRITE companion at
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_write_manager.xml) without first being
        able to READ candidate rows.
      - State-machine entry point (parent case resolution): per AAP
        Section 0.5.5 the In Progress -> Resolved transition is gated by
        "All linked x_[scope]_case_task records have status = Closed."
        The validate_resolved_transition subflow at
        ../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml implements
        this gate by querying child task rows and counting non-Closed
        statuses; that query must traverse every child task to produce
        an accurate count, and THIS ACL is the underlying authorization
        that lets the traversal succeed for a manager-driven transition.
      - State-machine entry point (case form load): every transition
        begins by the manager opening the case form, which loads the
        Tasks related list for that case. The related-list rendering is
        a GlideList query against case_task that is filtered by THIS
        ACL on every row.
      - Reporting accuracy: the Agent Workspace dashboard
        (../dashboards/pa_dashboards_x_[scope]_agent_workspace.xml) and
        any manager-side rollups against task data execute GlideRecord /
        GlideAggregate queries against x_[scope]_case_task that evaluate
        this ACL on every row; any narrowing of manager read would
        distort the aggregates and could cause overdue tasks to be
        silently hidden from a manager's overview.
      - Audit and compliance support: managers may be called upon to
        produce a task-level report or pull a specific task record for
        legal, compliance, or executive review at any time, on any task
        regardless of assignment. The unconditional read ensures they
        can answer those requests without privilege-escalation requests
        to platform admins.
      - Demo-data lifecycle: the seed script
        ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js creates demo tasks of mixed Open /
        Closed status on selected demo cases (per AAP Section 0.4.1 -
        "at least one open and one closed task per demo case in
        `In Progress` or `Pending` state, to exercise the
        all-tasks-closed gate"). The smoke-test phase requires the
        demo manager (../seed-data/users/sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_manager.xml)
        to read all demo tasks to confirm seed completeness and to
        exercise the resolved-transition gate by manually closing the
        last open task on a candidate case; both steps are authorized
        by THIS ACL.

    Why this ACL is INDEPENDENT of the parent case's read ACL:
      ServiceNow ACL evaluation is per-table, not transitively inherited.
      Even though x_[scope]_case_task carries a reference to a
      x_[scope]_case row via its "case" field, the platform does NOT
      automatically apply the parent case's ACLs to child task records.
      Each table requires its own role-bound ACLs to govern access.
      Therefore this file is REQUIRED in addition to
      ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml - both must apply for a
      manager to be able to (a) open a case and (b) see its task list
      and individual task records. Removing this file would break
      Validation Gate 3 (ACLs) for the case_task table even if the
      case-level manager read ACL is present.

    Mirror relationship to ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml:
      This file is the case_task-table analog of the manager-read ACL
      already authored for the case table. The ONLY differences between
      that file and this one are:
        - <name>           x_[scope]_case_task   (vs x_[scope]_case)
        - <sys_id>         MD5("x_[scope]_case_task.read.case_manager")
                                                 (vs MD5("x_[scope]_case.read.case_manager"))
        - <sys_name>       x_[scope]_case_task   (vs x_[scope]_case)
        - <sys_update_name> sys_security_acl_x_[scope]_case_task_read_manager
                                                 (vs sys_security_acl_x_[scope]_case_read_manager)
        - <description>    references the case_task table semantic
      All other fields (active, admin_overrides, advanced, condition,
      operation, roles, script, sys_class_name, sys_created_by,
      sys_policy, sys_scope, sys_package, type, audit timestamps) are
      byte-for-byte identical so that the manager's read privilege is
      uniformly unconditional across both the parent case table and the
      child case_task table as the AAP matrix mandates ("manager has
      full access" - Section 0.7.3 Gate 3).

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only context per AAP Section
    0.3.2; no code or configuration is byte-for-byte ported from these
    files):
      - acm-services/acm-service-users/src/main/java/com/armedia/acm/
        services/users/model/ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig.java
        ArkCase mapped roles to privileges through a single configuration
        map (`Map<String, List<Object>> rolesToPrivileges`) keyed by the
        property `application.rolesToPrivileges`. The class declares the
        constant
        `ROLES_TO_PRIVILEGES_PROP_KEY = "application.rolesToPrivileges"`
        and exposes the map via
        `@MapValue(value = "application.rolesToPrivileges")
         getRolesToPrivileges()`. In that model, a "manager-equivalent"
        role (e.g., ROLE_CASE_MANAGER or ROLE_TASK_MANAGER) would have
        been associated with a read privilege identifier such as
        `acm-task-read` or `acm-task-view`. The ServiceNow target
        replaces this map-based privilege association with declarative,
        scoped record-level ACLs - this XML record is the direct
        equivalent of one cell in the map: the (case_manager, READ)
        pairing for the case_task table.
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-admin-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/admin/service/RolesPrivilegesService.java
        Encapsulated role-CRUD and privilege-paging behavior in ArkCase
        (`retrieveRoles()`, `retrievePrivileges()`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByAuthorization(...)`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByRole(...)`, `updateRolePrivileges(...)`,
        `addRolesPrivileges(...)`, `removeRolesPrivileges(...)`). The
        service held injected dependencies on `UserDao`,
        `ApplicationRolesConfig`, `ApplicationPrivilegesConfig`,
        `ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig`,
        `ConfigurationPropertyService`,
        `CollectionPropertiesConfigurationService`, and
        `FunctionalAccessService` - a complex Spring/JPA stack that
        managed the role <-> privilege relationship at runtime. All of
        this Java service surface is replaced in the ServiceNow target
        by the platform's built-in sys_security_acl evaluator; no
        scripted privilege resolver is needed. Notably, ArkCase's
        `retrievePrivilegesByRole(roleName)` method paginated through
        the rolesToPrivileges map to return a role's privileges - the
        ServiceNow analog is the platform's "Roles" related list on
        sys_security_acl, which is automatically derived from the
        <roles> field of every ACL record like THIS one; no explicit
        query service is needed.

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.7.1 and 0.7.2):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: every cross-reference resolves into
        the x_[scope] scope (sys_scope = x_[scope], sys_package source =
        x_[scope]). No global-scope ACLs are written. The <name> field
        references the scoped table x_[scope]_case_task (not the OOB
        `task` or `incident_task` table or any other global table), and
        <roles> references the scoped role x_[scope]_case_manager. There
        are zero global writes from this file.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_id literals: <name>, <roles>,
        <sys_scope>, and <sys_package> all resolve their targets by
        name / source attribute lookup at Update Set apply time. The
        <sys_id> below is THIS record's own deterministic primary key
        (32-char lowercase hex MD5 of the canonical string
        "x_[scope]_case_task.read.case_manager", a stable canonical
        identifier for this exact ACL) and is not a cross-reference to
        any other record. Computing the sys_id deterministically
        guarantees the ACL is re-applyable / idempotent across fresh
        PDIs and round-trip Update Set previews per AAP Section 0.7.3
        Gate 7 ("Update Set loads without errors on a fresh PDI
        instance"), and matches the sibling-ACL convention - for
        example:
          ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_read_viewer.xml uses
            MD5("x_[scope]_case_task.read.case_viewer")
            = 536eb8c8bcfc523db221fc9ea9b68505
          ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_write_manager.xml uses
            MD5("x_[scope]_case_task.write.case_manager")
            = e71dc6760bcbc259019f5fc18442c014
          ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_delete_manager.xml uses
            MD5("x_[scope]_case_task.delete.case_manager")
            = 6c1bd40bcab435a7951bfeb732cd90e0
          ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml uses
            MD5("x_[scope]_case.read.case_manager")
            = 113c23bfb587d172b83db7ac8961ade2
          this file uses
            MD5("x_[scope]_case_task.read.case_manager")
            = c97e1d074ba86bf16b3a10cb4851e562
      - Table-level (not field-level): <name> is `x_[scope]_case_task`
        with NO dot. The case_task table has no field-level ACL siblings
        in this scoped app (only the case table does, on assigned_group
        and assigned_agent). The <type>record</type> field below
        confirms this is a row-level (table-level) ACL, not a
        UI/REST/SOAP-flavored ACL.
      - Operation = read: corresponds exactly to the "Read = All" cell
        in the AAP matrix for the case_manager role mirrored to the
        case_task table. There are deliberately NO field-level read
        restrictions on x_[scope]_case_task for any role.
      - admin_overrides = true: standard ServiceNow pattern that allows
        the platform `admin` role to bypass this ACL. This is required
        so platform administrators can troubleshoot, repair, or re-seed
        scoped demo task data (per AAP Section 0.7.4 the
        seed_demo_data.js script runs as admin to populate demo tasks
        with mixed Open and Closed statuses to exercise the
        resolved-transition gate). It does NOT widen case_manager
        privileges - non-admin managers see exactly what this ACL
        permits, which is full table-level read.
      - active = true: ACL is in force the moment the Update Set commits.
      - advanced = false: see "Why advanced=false" rationale above. The
        platform skips the empty <script/> body entirely.
      - condition (empty): the <condition/> encoded-query field is
        empty; no row-level filter applies to manager reads (manager
        has "All" access, not "Assigned only").
      - script (empty): the <script/> field is empty; the platform
        skips it because advanced=false.

    Difference from sibling ACLs - quick reference:
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_create_manager.xml (manager CREATE on case_task):
        - <operation>     read              vs create
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_[scope]_case_task.read.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_[scope]_case_task.create.case_manager")
        - <sys_update_name> *_read_manager  vs *_create_manager
        - <description>                     differs in operation wording
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_write_manager.xml (manager WRITE on case_task):
        - <operation>     read              vs write
        - <sys_id>        c97e1d074ba86bf16b3a10cb4851e562
                                            vs e71dc6760bcbc259019f5fc18442c014
        - <sys_update_name> *_read_manager  vs *_write_manager
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_delete_manager.xml (manager DELETE on case_task):
        - <operation>     read              vs delete
        - <sys_id>        c97e1d074ba86bf16b3a10cb4851e562
                                            vs 6c1bd40bcab435a7951bfeb732cd90e0
        - <sys_update_name> *_read_manager  vs *_delete_manager
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_read_viewer.xml (viewer READ - same operation, same table):
        - <roles>         x_[scope]_case_manager
                                            vs x_[scope]_case_viewer
        - <sys_id>        c97e1d074ba86bf16b3a10cb4851e562
                                            vs 536eb8c8bcfc523db221fc9ea9b68505
        - <sys_update_name> *_read_manager  vs *_read_viewer
        - <description>                     refers to manager           vs viewer
        Both files have advanced=false, empty condition, and empty
        script because both manager and viewer have unconditional read
        per the AAP matrix. The two files are functionally parallel and
        together give the manager and viewer roles identical row-level
        read scope on x_[scope]_case_task (every row); the AAP
        intentionally puts manager and viewer in the same Read=All
        bucket because both serve org-wide oversight functions, while
        the case_agent role is the operational worker tier whose read
        is narrowed.
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_read_agent_assigned.xml (agent READ
      assigned-only on case_task):
        - <roles>         x_[scope]_case_manager
                                            vs x_[scope]_case_agent
        - <advanced>      false             vs true (the agent ACL
                                              carries a scripted
                                              condition that dereferences
                                              current.case to apply the
                                              parent-case "Assigned only"
                                              predicate; the manager ACL
                                              is unconditional)
        - <condition>     empty             vs encoded query that
                                              asserts parent-case
                                              "Assigned only"
        - <script>        empty             vs server-side dereference
                                              of current.case followed
                                              by disjunction of
                                              parent-case
                                              assigned_agent /
                                              assigned_group checks
        - <sys_id>        c97e1d074ba86bf16b3a10cb4851e562
                                            vs MD5("x_[scope]_case_task.read.case_agent.assigned")
        - <sys_update_name> *_read_manager  vs *_read_agent_assigned
      vs ../acl/x_[scope]_case_read_manager.xml (manager READ on parent case table):
        - <name>          x_[scope]_case_task
                                            vs x_[scope]_case
        - <sys_id>        c97e1d074ba86bf16b3a10cb4851e562
                                            vs 113c23bfb587d172b83db7ac8961ade2
        - <sys_update_name> *_case_task_read_manager
                                            vs *_case_read_manager
        - <description>                     references case_task table
                                            vs case table
        Both ACLs have identical <operation>=read,
        <roles>=x_[scope]_case_manager, <advanced>=false,
        <condition/>=empty, <script/>=empty - the only differences are
        the table name (case_task vs case) and the deterministic sys_id
        derived from that table name. This parallelism is what
        materializes the AAP rule "case_manager has full access" across
        BOTH the parent case table and the child case_task table.
      All other XML elements are identical between the manager-tier
      ACLs; the deterministic sys_id, the table name, and the
      operation/role triplet are the defining differences.

    Cross-dependencies and Update-Set ordering (AAP Section 0.5.2):
      MUST be loaded AFTER:
        - ../app/sys_app/x_[scope]_case_management.xml (scoped app
          record)
        - ../app/sys_scope/x_[scope].xml (scope record - resolves
          sys_scope and sys_package source="x_[scope]")
        - ../tables/x_[scope]_case_task.xml (resolves
          <name>x_[scope]_case_task</name> by table name lookup at
          apply time)
        - ../roles/sys_user_role_x_[scope]_case_manager.xml (resolves
          <roles>x_[scope]_case_manager</roles> by role name lookup at
          apply time)
      MUST be loaded BEFORE:
        - ../seed-data/role_assignments/sys_user_has_role_x_[scope]_demo_manager.xml
          (the demo manager's task-read access during round-trip
          verification depends on this ACL being applied first)
        - ../reports/x_[scope]_my_overdue_tasks.xml (the report's
          GlideRecord query against x_[scope]_case_task is filtered
          through this ACL when run by a logged-in manager; the report
          must not execute before the ACL is applied or the manager
          would see no overdue tasks)
        - ../dashboards/pa_dashboards_x_[scope]_agent_workspace.xml
          (the dashboard depends on the underlying my-overdue-tasks
          report which in turn depends on this ACL)
        - ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml,
          ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml,
          ../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml (Flow
          Designer flows on the parent case fire on update; their
          inline GlideRecord lookups against x_[scope]_case_task and
          the parent-case dereferences inside subflows all depend on
          this ACL having authorized the read - in particular,
          validate_resolved_transition.xml queries x_[scope]_case_task
          by case=current.sys_id^status!=closed which requires read
          access to the child task rows)
        - any cleanup or re-seed activity in ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js
          that may post-validate prior demo task rows; while
          seed_demo_data.js itself runs as admin and bypasses this ACL
          via admin_overrides, post-seed smoke tests against the demo
          dataset depend on this ACL being applied so a logged-in
          demo manager can validate end-to-end task-read capability.
      The deny-by-default sibling pair that this file works with:
        - There is NO equivalent "deny" ACL needed for any role;
          ServiceNow ACLs are deny-by-default. A user without the
          case_manager role (and without case_agent or case_viewer)
          sees zero rows on x_[scope]_case_task regardless of any
          per-role ACL state.

    The literal `[scope]` placeholder is preserved verbatim per AAP
    convention (Section 0.7.2 "Scoped-namespace-only constraint"); the
    Personal Developer Instance auto-assigns the actual concrete scope
    id at App Engine Studio creation time, and the Update-Set apply-time
    renaming propagates consistently across all bracketed placeholders
    in this artifact. The deterministic sys_id below is computed against
    the `[scope]` literal and remains stable across re-imports onto
    fresh PDIs.
-->
<record_update table="sys_security_acl">
    <sys_security_acl action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <admin_overrides>true</admin_overrides>
        <advanced>false</advanced>
        <condition/>
        <description>Allows users with the x_[scope]_case_manager role to read all case_task records (unconditional). Per AAP Section 0.5.6, manager Read=All on case_task. NO field-level ACLs exist on case_task; this table-level grant fully governs manager read authority on every column.</description>
        <name>x_[scope]_case_task</name>
        <operation>read</operation>
        <roles>x_[scope]_case_manager</roles>
        <script/>
        <sys_class_name>sys_security_acl</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>c97e1d074ba86bf16b3a10cb4851e562</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>x_[scope]_case_task</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_[scope]">x_[scope]</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_[scope]</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_security_acl_x_[scope]_case_task_read_manager</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <type>record</type>
    </sys_security_acl>
</record_update>

