<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the table-level WRITE ACL that
    grants the scoped role `x_casemgmt_case_manager` UNCONDITIONAL write access
    on records of the `x_casemgmt_case_task` custom table inside the scoped
    application `x_casemgmt`. This is the WRITE companion to the case_manager
    create/read/delete ACLs on the case_task table (whose granting ACLs are
    materialized by the sibling files
    ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_create_manager.xml,
    ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_read_manager.xml, and
    ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_delete_manager.xml). Together those four files
    realize the AAP Section 0.5.6 manager row mirrored at the case_task table
    level per AAP Section 0.5.1 row "servicenow-case-management-poc/acl/
    x_casemgmt_case_task_*.xml" ("Mirror ACL pattern at task level"):
    "x_casemgmt_case_manager : Create=Yes, Read=All, Write=All, Delete=Yes."

    The case_manager role is the highest-tier scoped role for case-management
    operations; per AAP Section 0.5.6 the manager has UNRESTRICTED write
    privileges on every case_task row regardless of which agent the task is
    currently assigned to (case_task.assigned_to), what type of work it
    represents (case_task.type), what stage it is in (case_task.status), or
    which parent case it belongs to (case_task.case). This privilege is the
    keystone that lets managers re-route tasks between agents (by editing
    case_task.assigned_to), correct intake errors on case_task.subject /
    case_task.due_date, change classification via case_task.type, and drive
    individual tasks through every status transition - including the critical
    Open -> In Progress -> Closed progression that gates the parent case's
    own In Progress -> Resolved transition (per AAP Section 0.5.5 transition
    rule "All linked x_casemgmt_case_task records have status = Closed", whose
    blocking-error wording "All tasks must be closed before resolving this
    case." is enforced server-side by the validate_resolved_transition
    subflow at ../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml).

    AAP cross-references:
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - case_manager row, mirrored at the
        case_task table level per AAP Section 0.5.1 row
        "servicenow-case-management-poc/acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_*.xml"
        ("Mirror ACL pattern at task level"):
            | Role                    | Create | Read | Write | Delete |
            | x_casemgmt_case_manager  |  Yes   | All  |  All  |  Yes   |
        This file authors the single "Write = All" cell of the manager row
        for the case_task table. The "Yes" Create cell is authored by
        ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_create_manager.xml; the "All" Read cell
        by ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_read_manager.xml; the "Yes" Delete
        cell by ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_delete_manager.xml. Each row of
        the ACL matrix maps to exactly one or zero ACL XML files - this
        per-cell granularity is what lets the Update Set add or remove role
        privileges independently without entangling roles or operations.
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - all-roles write coverage on case_task:
            - case_manager: Write=All           -> THIS FILE
            - case_agent:   Write=Assigned only -> ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_write_agent_assigned.xml
                                                   (carries the row-level filter
                                                    that dereferences current.case
                                                    and applies the parent-case
                                                    "Assigned only" predicate
                                                    "parentCase.assigned_agent =
                                                     current user OR
                                                     parentCase.assigned_group
                                                     contains current user")
            - case_viewer:  Write=No            -> deliberate absence of any
                                                   x_casemgmt_case_task_write_viewer.xml
                                                   (deny-by-default; ServiceNow
                                                    record-level ACLs deny when
                                                    no granting ACL exists)
        Together these three facts implement the user prompt's contract:
        the manager is empowered to edit any task unconditionally; the agent
        is empowered to edit only tasks whose parent case they own (where
        ownership is the disjunction of direct agent assignment and group
        membership on the parent case); the viewer is denied write entirely
        so the audit / compliance / supervisor tier cannot mutate task data.
      - Section 0.5.5 (State-Machine Transition Map) - manager-driven task
        operations that depend on this ACL:
            - "In Progress -> Resolved: All linked x_casemgmt_case_task
               records have status = Closed". The case-resolution gate is
               implemented by the ../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml
               subflow, which queries child task rows via GlideRecord and
               counts non-Closed statuses. To advance ANY task through its
               own Open -> In Progress -> Closed progression, a writer must
               pass an ACL on the case_task table. This ACL authorizes the
               manager to do so unconditionally on EVERY task; the parallel
               "Assigned only" ACL at ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_write_agent_assigned.xml
               authorizes the assigned agent to do the same only for tasks
               on cases they own. Without this ACL, a manager could not
               assist an agent who is unable or unavailable to close their
               own task - e.g., if the agent leaves the organization mid-
               case, the task would block the parent case's resolution
               permanently. The manager's unrestricted write closes that
               operational gap.
            - Cross-team task re-assignment: when the originally-assigned
               agent (case_task.assigned_to) becomes unavailable, only the
               manager can re-route the task by writing case_task.assigned_to
               to a different sys_user. Restricting manager write to
               "Assigned only" would create a chicken-and-egg problem - a
               manager could not initially re-assign a task to another agent
               because the manager themselves is rarely the original
               assigned_to, and would therefore fail the "Assigned only"
               predicate on the parent case.
        The transition rules are validated by the two case-type Flow
        Designer flows ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml and
        ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml plus the supporting subflows
        under ../flows/sub_flows/; those flows fire AFTER the platform's
        ACL evaluator has authorized the underlying write, so this ACL is
        a prerequisite to the flow ever running for a manager when the
        manager edits child tasks.
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 3 - ACLs):
            "Role-based access enforced - case_viewer cannot write;
             case_agent cannot access unassigned cases; case_manager has
             full access."
        The clause "case_manager has full access" requires that the manager
        role be able to perform every CRUD operation on the case_task
        table, of which write is the most-frequent (managers regularly
        adjust task subject/type/due_date/assigned_to during operational
        triage). This ACL satisfies that clause for the write operation on
        the task domain; the parallel clauses about case_viewer (no write)
        and case_agent (no unassigned access) are unaffected by this ACL
        and are enforced by separate sibling ACL files (case_viewer never
        appears in any case_task write/create/delete ACL; case_agent write
        on case_task is conditioned on the parent-case "Assigned only"
        filter via ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_write_agent_assigned.xml).
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 2 - Workflow): the
        manager-driven Resolved -> Closed transition on the parent case
        depends on every child task having reached Closed status. To
        manually drive a task to Closed during validation/demo, the
        validating manager (../seed-data/users/sys_user_x_casemgmt_demo_manager.xml)
        must hold this ACL or the task status update will be rejected
        before the case-resolution flow even runs.
      - Section 0.4.3 (Design Pattern Applications - Scoped role-based
        access control): "Three named roles paired with table-level and
        field-level ACLs whose conditions are encoded as scripted ACL
        expressions, replacing ArkCase's ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig
        map." This ACL is the table-level WRITE binding for the highest-
        tier scoped role on the task domain and is one of the declarative
        facts the platform's sys_security_acl evaluator consumes when
        authorizing a row update at runtime against the case_task table.
      - Section 0.1.2 (Technical Interpretation - Access-control
        transformation): "ApplicationRolesConfig + RolesPrivilegesService +
        URL-based privilege metadata -> scoped roles + ACLs." In ArkCase
        the equivalent of THIS file would have been a single entry in the
        rolesToPrivileges map binding the manager-equivalent role to a
        privilege identifier such as `acm-task-update` or `acm-task-edit`,
        evaluated at HTTP request time by AcmPluginUrlPrivilege against
        the PUT verb on the task plugin's REST endpoint. The ServiceNow
        target replaces both the map binding and the URL-privilege
        evaluator with this single declarative ACL record; the platform's
        sys_security_acl engine handles the role-membership check,
        condition evaluation, and admin-override logic that ArkCase
        implemented through hand-written Java code (see
        acm-services/acm-service-users/.../ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig.java
        plus the admin-plugin Java REST controllers under
        acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-admin-plugin/.../web/api/).

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only context per AAP Section
    0.3.2; no code or configuration is byte-for-byte ported from these
    files):
      - acm-services/acm-service-users/src/main/java/com/armedia/acm/services/
        users/model/ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig.java
        ArkCase mapped roles to privileges through a single configuration
        map (`Map<String, List<Object>> rolesToPrivileges`) keyed by the
        property `application.rolesToPrivileges`. The class declares the
        constant `ROLES_TO_PRIVILEGES_PROP_KEY = "application.rolesToPrivileges"`
        and exposes the map via `@MapValue(value = "application.rolesToPrivileges")
        getRolesToPrivileges()`. In that model, a "manager-equivalent" role
        (e.g., ROLE_TASK_MANAGER) would have been associated with a write
        privilege identifier such as `acm-task-update` or `acm-task-edit`.
        The ServiceNow target replaces this map-based privilege association
        with declarative, scoped record-level ACLs - this XML record is
        the direct equivalent of one cell in the map: the (case_manager,
        WRITE) pairing on the case_task domain.
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-admin-plugin/src/main/java/com/
        armedia/acm/plugins/admin/service/RolesPrivilegesService.java
        Encapsulated role-CRUD and privilege-paging behavior in ArkCase
        (`retrieveRoles()`, `retrievePrivileges()`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByAuthorization(...)`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByRole(...)`, `updateRolePrivileges(...)`,
        `addRolesPrivileges(...)`, `removeRolesPrivileges(...)`). The
        service held injected dependencies on `UserDao`,
        `ApplicationRolesConfig`, `ApplicationPrivilegesConfig`,
        `ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig`, `ConfigurationPropertyService`,
        `CollectionPropertiesConfigurationService`, and
        `FunctionalAccessService` - a complex Spring/JPA stack that managed
        the role <-> privilege relationship at runtime. All of this Java
        service surface is replaced in the ServiceNow target by the
        platform's built-in sys_security_acl evaluator; no scripted
        privilege resolver is needed. Notably, ArkCase's
        `updateRolePrivileges(roleName, privileges)` would have rebuilt
        the role's privilege list and persisted it via
        `configurationPropertyService.updateProperties(...)` - that
        write-time bookkeeping is, in ServiceNow, accomplished by the
        admin author of THIS XML record committing the Update Set; no
        runtime mutation is required.

    Why advanced=false (no scripted condition for manager write):
      Per AAP Section 0.5.6, the case_manager role's privileges are
      unconditional ("All", "Full access") - there is no "Assigned only"
      or other row-level filter. The manager is intentionally NOT scoped
      to a subset of tasks; they have org-wide write authority on the
      task domain because their job function is exactly to oversee, route,
      and unblock task work across all assignment boundaries. Therefore:
        - <advanced>false</advanced>      - no scripted condition
        - <condition/>                    - empty encoded query (no row filter)
        - <script/>                       - empty server-side script
      With no condition and no script, the ACL evaluates to "permit" for
      any caller who carries the x_casemgmt_case_manager role. This is the
      correct semantic for the AAP's "manager has full write" requirement.
      Setting advanced=true with an empty script would be functionally
      equivalent but stylistically incorrect - the ServiceNow convention
      is to reserve advanced=true for ACLs that actually carry a scripted
      body (see, for contrast,
      ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_write_agent_assigned.xml where
      advanced=true and the script encodes the parent-case-dereferenced
      disjunctive ownership check
      `parent.assigned_agent == gs.getUserID() ||
       gs.getUser().isMemberOf(parent.assigned_group)`).

    Why WRITE is granted to manager unconditionally (design rationale):
      - Cross-team task re-assignment: when an assigned agent is unable
        or unavailable to complete a task (e.g., agent leaves the
        organization, agent is overloaded, task was misclassified to the
        wrong specialty), only the manager can re-route the task by
        writing case_task.assigned_to to a different sys_user. Restricting
        manager write to "Assigned only" would create a chicken-and-egg
        problem - a manager could not re-route a task because they
        themselves are rarely the original assigned_to.
      - Records-management oversight: tasks under audit, compliance
        review, or escalation may need their subject/due_date/type
        amended for clarity, accuracy, or operational scheduling. Only
        managers have this editorial authority across all tasks regardless
        of assignment.
      - State-machine integrity (the resolved-transition gate): per AAP
        Section 0.5.5 the parent case's In Progress -> Resolved transition
        is gated by the rule "All linked x_casemgmt_case_task records have
        status = Closed" with the verbatim blocking-error message "All
        tasks must be closed before resolving this case." If a child task
        is stuck (e.g., its assigned agent left the organization, or the
        task is no longer relevant), the manager - and only the manager -
        must be able to write case_task.status to Closed so the parent
        case can be resolved. Without this ACL, no path exists to unblock
        the gate, and the case lifecycle would be permanently stalled.
      - Demo-data lifecycle: the seed script ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js
        runs as the platform admin (which bypasses this ACL via
        admin_overrides=true) but post-seed re-runs in interactive mode
        from the demo manager
        (../seed-data/users/sys_user_x_casemgmt_demo_manager.xml) depend
        on this ACL being applied so the manager can manually advance a
        seeded Open task to Closed during smoke testing without needing
        the admin login.
      - Field-level write integrity: unlike the case table, the case_task
        table has NO field-level ACLs in this scoped application (per AAP
        Section 0.3.1, field-level ACLs are authored only for the
        x_casemgmt_case columns assigned_group and assigned_agent; the
        case_task columns case/subject/type/status/assigned_to/due_date
        are governed solely by table-level ACLs). Therefore THIS ACL
        alone determines the manager's authority over EVERY column on
        the case_task table. There is no field-level layer that could
        narrow or widen this grant.

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.7.1 and 0.7.2):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: every cross-reference resolves into
        the x_casemgmt scope (sys_scope = x_casemgmt, sys_package source =
        x_casemgmt). No global-scope ACLs are written. The <name> field
        references the scoped table x_casemgmt_case_task (not the OOB
        `task` or `incident_task` table or any other global table), and
        <roles> references the scoped role x_casemgmt_case_manager. There
        are zero global writes from this file.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_id literals: <name>, <roles>,
        <sys_scope>, and <sys_package> all resolve their targets by
        name / source attribute lookup at Update Set apply time. The
        <sys_id> below is THIS record's own deterministic primary key
        (32-char lowercase hex MD5 of the canonical string
        "x_casemgmt_case_task.write.case_manager", a stable canonical
        identifier for this exact ACL) and is not a cross-reference to
        any other record. Computing the sys_id deterministically guarantees
        the ACL is re-applyable / idempotent across fresh PDIs and round-
        trip Update Set previews per AAP Section 0.7.3 Gate 7 ("Update
        Set loads without errors on a fresh PDI instance").
      - Table-level (not field-level): <name> is `x_casemgmt_case_task`
        with NO dot. The case_task table has no field-level ACL siblings
        in this scoped app (only the case table does, on assigned_group
        and assigned_agent). The <type>record</type> field below confirms
        this is a row-level (table-level) ACL, not a UI/REST/SOAP-flavored
        ACL.
      - Operation = write: corresponds exactly to the "Write = All" cell
        in the AAP matrix for the case_manager role mirrored to the
        case_task table.
      - admin_overrides = true: standard ServiceNow pattern that allows
        the platform `admin` role to bypass this ACL. This is required so
        platform administrators can troubleshoot, repair, or re-seed
        scoped demo task data (per AAP Section 0.7.4 the seed_demo_data.js
        script runs as admin to populate demo tasks with mixed Open and
        Closed statuses to exercise the resolved-transition gate). It
        does NOT widen case_manager privileges - non-admin managers see
        exactly what this ACL permits, which is full table-level write.
      - active = true: ACL is in force the moment the Update Set commits.
      - advanced = false: see "Why advanced=false" rationale above. The
        platform skips the empty <script/> body entirely.
      - condition (empty): the <condition/> encoded-query field is empty;
        no row-level filter applies to manager writes (manager has "All"
        access, not "Assigned only").
      - script (empty): the <script/> field is empty; the platform skips
        it because advanced=false.

    Difference from sibling ACLs - quick reference:
      vs ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_create_manager.xml (manager CREATE on case_task):
        - <operation>     write             vs create
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_casemgmt_case_task.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_casemgmt_case_task.create.case_manager")
        - <sys_update_name> *_write_manager vs *_create_manager
      vs ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_read_manager.xml (manager READ on case_task):
        - <operation>     write             vs read
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_casemgmt_case_task.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_casemgmt_case_task.read.case_manager")
        - <sys_update_name> *_write_manager vs *_read_manager
      vs ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_delete_manager.xml (manager DELETE on case_task):
        - <operation>     write             vs delete
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_casemgmt_case_task.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_casemgmt_case_task.delete.case_manager")
        - <sys_update_name> *_write_manager vs *_delete_manager
      vs ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_write_agent_assigned.xml (agent WRITE assigned-only on case_task):
        - <roles>         x_casemgmt_case_manager
                                            vs x_casemgmt_case_agent
        - <advanced>      false             vs true (the agent ACL carries a
                                              scripted condition; the manager
                                              ACL is unconditional)
        - <condition>     empty             vs encoded query that asserts
                                              parent-case "Assigned only"
        - <script>        empty             vs server-side dereference of
                                              current.case followed by
                                              disjunction of parent-case
                                              assigned_agent/assigned_group
                                              checks
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_casemgmt_case_task.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_casemgmt_case_task.write.case_agent.assigned")
        - <sys_update_name> *_write_manager vs *_write_agent_assigned
      vs ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_write_manager.xml (manager WRITE on parent case table):
        - <name>          x_casemgmt_case_task
                                            vs x_casemgmt_case
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_casemgmt_case_task.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_casemgmt_case.write.case_manager")
        - <sys_update_name> *_case_task_write_manager
                                            vs *_case_write_manager
        Both ACLs have identical <operation>=write, <roles>=x_casemgmt_case_manager,
        <advanced>=false, <condition/>=empty, <script/>=empty - the only
        differences are the table name (case_task vs case) and the
        deterministic sys_id derived from that table name.
      All other XML elements are identical between the manager-tier ACLs;
      the deterministic sys_id, the table name, and the operation/role
      triplet are the defining differences.

    Cross-dependencies and Update-Set ordering (AAP Section 0.5.2):
      MUST be loaded AFTER:
        - ../app/sys_app/x_casemgmt_case_management.xml (scoped app record)
        - ../app/sys_scope/x_casemgmt.xml (scope record - resolves
          sys_scope and sys_package source="x_casemgmt")
        - ../tables/x_casemgmt_case_task.xml (resolves
          <name>x_casemgmt_case_task</name> by table name lookup at apply
          time)
        - ../roles/sys_user_role_x_casemgmt_case_manager.xml (resolves
          <roles>x_casemgmt_case_manager</roles> by role name lookup at
          apply time)
      MUST be loaded BEFORE:
        - ../seed-data/role_assignments/sys_user_has_role_x_casemgmt_demo_manager.xml
          (the demo manager's task-write access during round-trip
          verification depends on this ACL being applied first)
        - ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml,
          ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml (Flow Designer flows on the
          parent case fire on update; their validate_resolved_transition
          subflow at ../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml
          may be exercised end-to-end by a manager who first updates child
          tasks to Closed status - the task updates depend on this ACL
          having authorized them)
        - any cleanup or re-seed activity in ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js
          that may update prior demo task rows; while seed_demo_data.js
          itself runs as admin and bypasses this ACL via admin_overrides,
          post-seed smoke tests against the demo dataset depend on this
          ACL being applied so a logged-in demo manager can validate end-
          to-end task-write capability.
      The deny-by-default sibling pair that this file works with:
        - x_casemgmt_case_task_write_viewer.xml (DOES NOT EXIST - by design;
          case_viewer Write=No is enforced structurally by the absence of
          a granting ACL)
      Adding x_casemgmt_case_task_write_viewer.xml would VIOLATE the AAP
      Section 0.5.6 matrix and MUST NOT be done by any future agent.

    The concrete scope identifier `casemgmt` is used per AAP convention
    (Section 0.7.2 "Scoped-namespace-only constraint"); ServiceNow
    Update Set imports use a standard XML parser, so the scope id
    must be concrete in the XML before export. The same identifier
    is used consistently across every artifact in this scoped
    application. The deterministic sys_id below is computed against
    the `casemgmt` literal and remains stable across re-imports onto
    fresh PDIs.
-->
<record_update table="sys_security_acl">
    <sys_security_acl action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <admin_overrides>true</admin_overrides>
        <advanced>false</advanced>
        <condition/>
        <description>Allows users with the x_casemgmt_case_manager role to write/update all case_task records (unconditional). Per AAP Section 0.5.6, manager Write=All on case_task. NO field-level ACLs exist on case_task; this table-level grant fully governs manager write authority on every column.</description>
        <name>x_casemgmt_case_task</name>
        <operation>write</operation>
        <roles>x_casemgmt_case_manager</roles>
        <script/>
        <sys_class_name>sys_security_acl</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>e71dc6760bcbc259019f5fc18442c014</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>x_casemgmt_case_task</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_casemgmt">x_casemgmt</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_casemgmt</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_security_acl_x_casemgmt_case_task_write_manager</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <type>record</type>
    </sys_security_acl>
</record_update>
