<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the table-level WRITE ACL that
    grants the scoped role `x_casemgmt_case_manager` UNCONDITIONAL write access
    on records of the `x_casemgmt_case_party` custom table inside the scoped
    application `x_casemgmt`. This is the WRITE companion to the case_manager
    create / read / delete ACLs whose granting ACLs are materialized by the
    sibling files:
        - ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_create_manager.xml
          (manager-create grant on case_party records)
        - ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_read_manager.xml
          (manager-read grant: read-all on case_party records)
        - ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_delete_manager.xml
          (manager-delete grant: only role with delete privilege on case_party)
    Together those four files realize the AAP Section 0.5.6 manager row
    mirrored at the case_party table level per AAP Section 0.5.1 row
    "servicenow-case-management-poc/acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_*.xml"
    ("Mirror ACL pattern at party level"):
        | Role                    | Create | Read | Write | Delete |
        | x_casemgmt_case_manager  |  Yes   | All  |  All  |  Yes   |

    The case_manager role is the highest-tier scoped role for case-management
    operations; per AAP Section 0.5.6 the manager has UNRESTRICTED write
    privileges on every case_party row regardless of which agent or group
    currently owns the parent case (case_party.case), what variant the row
    represents (case_party.party_type = Person | Organization), or which
    person / organization / role_label the row carries. This privilege is the
    keystone that lets managers correct mis-classified parties (changing
    party_type from Person to Organization or vice-versa as data-quality
    rework), reassign Person rows to different sys_user references when an
    individual leaves or is replaced, swap Organization references when
    company name changes or merger events occur, edit role_label to refine
    the participant role taxonomy (Requester / Respondent / Witness /
    Counsel / Other), and re-parent a party from one case to another by
    editing case_party.case (records-management oversight scenario).

    AAP cross-references:
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - case_manager row, mirrored at the
        case_party table level per AAP Section 0.5.1 row
        "servicenow-case-management-poc/acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_*.xml"
        ("Mirror ACL pattern at party level"):
            | Role                    | Create | Read | Write | Delete |
            | x_casemgmt_case_manager  |  Yes   | All  |  All  |  Yes   |
        This file authors the single "Write = All" cell of the manager row
        for the case_party table. The "Yes" Create cell is authored by
        ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_create_manager.xml; the "All" Read cell
        by ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_read_manager.xml; the "Yes" Delete
        cell by ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_delete_manager.xml. Each row of
        the ACL matrix maps to exactly one or zero ACL XML files - this
        per-cell granularity is what lets the Update Set add or remove role
        privileges independently without entangling roles or operations.
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - all-roles write coverage on case_party:
            - case_manager: Write=All           -> THIS FILE
            - case_agent:   Write=Assigned only -> ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_write_agent_assigned.xml
                                                   (carries the row-level
                                                    filter that dereferences
                                                    current.case and applies
                                                    the parent-case "Assigned
                                                    only" predicate
                                                    "parentCase.assigned_agent
                                                     = current user OR
                                                     parentCase.assigned_group
                                                     contains current user")
            - case_viewer:  Write=No            -> deliberate absence of any
                                                   x_casemgmt_case_party_write_viewer.xml
                                                   (deny-by-default; ServiceNow
                                                    record-level ACLs deny when
                                                    no granting ACL exists)
        Together these three facts implement the user prompt's contract:
        the manager is empowered to edit any party association unconditionally;
        the agent is empowered to edit only parties whose parent case they own
        (where ownership is the disjunction of direct agent assignment and
        group membership on the parent case); the viewer is denied write
        entirely so the audit / compliance / supervisor tier cannot mutate
        party association data.
      - Section 0.5.6 (ACL Matrix) - relationship to case_party field-level
        ACLs:
            The case_party table has NO field-level ACL counterpart files
            (unlike the parent x_casemgmt_case table which carries
            ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_assigned_group_field_acl.xml and
            ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_assigned_agent_field_acl.xml). Per AAP
            Section 0.5.6, the case-table's sensitive fields - assigned_group
            and assigned_agent - require additional role gating beyond the
            table-level ACL because they govern case ownership and the
            "Assigned only" predicate's evaluation. The case_party table's
            fields (case, party_type, person, organization, role_label) carry
            no analogous role-based field gating per AAP design: any role
            authorized to write the row at the table level may write any
            column. THIS table-level WRITE ACL therefore fully governs
            manager write authority on every column of every case_party row.
      - Section 0.4.3 (Polymorphic association via single-table choice +
        UI Policy): "case_party collapses ArkCase's two association tables
        (acm_person_assoc, acm_person_org_assoc) into one ServiceNow table
        with a Choice discriminator (party_type) and a UI Policy that
        conditionally shows person (reference->sys_user) or organization
        (reference->core_company)." Because BOTH polymorphic sub-shapes
        (Person and Organization) are stored in a single physical table,
        a single ACL record (this one) governs WRITE access for the
        manager role across BOTH variants - there is no need for separate
        Person / Organization manager-write ACLs. This is a deliberate
        simplification of the source ArkCase model: ArkCase had separate
        DELETE and UPDATE privilege identifiers for Person and Organization
        associations (managed by acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-person-
        plugin services), but the collapsed ServiceNow target needs only
        one declarative ACL per CRUD operation per role.
      - Section 0.5.5 (State-Machine Transition Map) - manager-driven
        case-party operations that depend on this ACL:
            The case state-machine (driven by ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml
            and ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml) does NOT directly
            mutate case_party rows; the parent case lifecycle (Draft -> Open
            -> In Progress -> Pending -> Resolved -> Closed) is independent
            of party-association lifecycle. However, in practice, manager
            workflow during case progression frequently involves:
              - Adding a Witness party while transitioning from Open to
                In Progress (governed by the manager-create ACL)
              - Updating a Respondent's role_label or organization reference
                during the In Progress phase as new facts emerge
                (governed by THIS ACL)
              - Correcting a Person party's `person` reference when the
                requester contacts the case manager about an account
                consolidation or name change (governed by THIS ACL)
            None of these party-mutation operations is gated by the
            case-status state machine; they are gated solely by THIS ACL
            (and the case_agent-assigned write ACL for non-manager roles).
            This separation of concerns - case state machine vs. party
            association management - is intentional and matches the AAP's
            "Mirror ACL pattern" guidance that party-table ACLs follow the
            same role gating as case-table ACLs without introducing
            additional state-machine entanglement.
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 3 - ACLs):
            "Role-based access enforced - case_viewer cannot write;
             case_agent cannot access unassigned cases; case_manager has
             full access."
        The clause "case_manager has full access" requires that the manager
        role be able to perform every CRUD operation on the case_party
        table, of which write is the second most-frequent (after read).
        This ACL satisfies that clause for the write operation on the
        party domain; the parallel clauses about case_viewer (no write)
        and case_agent (no unassigned access) are unaffected by this ACL
        and are enforced by separate sibling ACL files (case_viewer never
        appears in any case_party write/create/delete ACL; case_agent
        write on case_party is conditioned on the parent-case "Assigned
        only" filter via ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_write_agent_assigned.xml).
      - Section 0.7.3 (Validation Framework, Gate 1 - Data model) and
        Gate 2 (Workflow): both gates depend on a logged-in test user
        being able to mutate party fields and exercise the polymorphic
        UI Policy. The validation plan in ../docs/validation-gates.md
        exercises party-association management as the demo manager
        (../seed-data/users/sys_user_x_casemgmt_demo_manager.xml); every
        party-update step in that validation requires this ACL to
        authorize the underlying row update.
      - Section 0.4.3 (Design Pattern Applications - Scoped role-based
        access control): "Three named roles paired with table-level and
        field-level ACLs whose conditions are encoded as scripted ACL
        expressions, replacing ArkCase's ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig
        map." This ACL is the table-level WRITE binding for the highest-
        tier scoped role on the party domain and is one of the declarative
        facts the platform's sys_security_acl evaluator consumes when
        authorizing a row update at runtime against the case_party table.
      - Section 0.1.2 (Technical Interpretation - Access-control
        transformation): "ApplicationRolesConfig + RolesPrivilegesService +
        URL-based privilege metadata -> scoped roles + ACLs." In ArkCase
        the equivalent of THIS file would have been TWO entries in the
        rolesToPrivileges map (because ArkCase modeled person-association
        and organization-association in TWO separate tables, acm_person_assoc
        and acm_person_org_assoc) binding the manager-equivalent role to
        write privilege identifiers such as `acm-person-association-edit`
        / `acm-person-association-update` and
        `acm-organization-association-edit` / `acm-organization-association-update`,
        evaluated at HTTP request time by AcmPluginUrlPrivilege against the
        PUT / POST verbs on the person plugin's REST endpoints
        (acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-person-plugin/.../web/api/
        OrganizationAssociationAPIController.java and the Person association
        controllers). The ServiceNow target replaces both map bindings
        AND the URL-privilege evaluator with this single declarative ACL
        record - because the target's case_party table is polymorphic
        (party_type Choice = Person | Organization with conditional person
        and organization reference fields per AAP Section 0.4.3 Polymorphic
        association via single-table choice + UI Policy), one ACL governs
        write for both Person and Organization variants.

    Why advanced=false (no scripted condition for manager write):
      Per AAP Section 0.5.6, the case_manager role's privileges are
      unconditional ("All", "Full access") - there is no "Assigned only"
      or other row-level filter. The manager is intentionally NOT scoped
      to a subset of cases or parties; they have org-wide write authority
      on case_party because their job function is exactly to oversee,
      route, classify, and correct party associations across all
      assignment boundaries. Therefore:
        - <advanced>false</advanced>      - no scripted condition
        - <condition/>                    - empty encoded query (no row filter)
        - <script/>                       - empty server-side script
      With no condition and no script, the ACL evaluates to "permit" for
      any caller who carries the x_casemgmt_case_manager role. This is the
      correct semantic for the AAP's "manager has full write" requirement.
      Setting advanced=true with an empty script would be functionally
      equivalent but stylistically incorrect - the ServiceNow convention
      is to reserve advanced=true for ACLs that actually carry a scripted
      body (see, for contrast, ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_write_agent_assigned.xml
      where advanced=true and the script encodes the parent-case "Assigned
      only" disjunctive ownership check that traverses current.case
      via getRefRecord() to evaluate parentCase.assigned_agent and
      parentCase.assigned_group membership).

    Why WRITE is granted to manager unconditionally (design rationale):
      - Cross-team routing and intake correction: when a portal-submitted
        case lands with mis-classified parties (a Person row that should
        have been an Organization, an Organization with the wrong company
        reference), only the manager has authority to re-classify by
        editing party_type and the conditional person / organization
        references. Restricting manager write to "Assigned only" would
        create a chicken-and-egg problem - a manager could not initially
        repair an unassigned case's party associations because they
        weren't yet the assigned agent on the parent case.
      - Records-management oversight: parties associated to cases under
        audit, compliance review, or regulatory scrutiny may need their
        role_label refined (e.g., upgrading "Witness" to "Subject" as
        new facts emerge), their person reference re-pointed to a
        different sys_user (when account consolidation occurs), or their
        organization reference re-pointed to a different core_company
        (when corporate restructuring happens). Only managers have this
        editorial authority across all parties on all cases.
      - Polymorphic data integrity: because case_party is polymorphic
        (Person | Organization variants share one table per AAP Section
        0.4.3), the platform's UI Policy
        ../ui_policy/x_casemgmt_case_party_conditional_fields.xml shows
        person when party_type=Person and organization when
        party_type=Organization. If a row's party_type is ever found
        wrong post-creation (e.g., a Person was misclassified at intake
        as an Organization), the UI Policy alone cannot self-heal -
        someone must edit the row to swap the reference fields. The
        manager has authority to do so via THIS ACL; no other role does
        unconditionally.
      - Audit trail correction: while case_viewer holds read-only audit
        access, real-world compliance reviews sometimes surface
        retroactive party data quality issues (typo in role_label, wrong
        person reference, etc.) that must be corrected without losing
        the audit trail. The manager performs these corrections under
        their unconditional write grant; the platform's sys_audit
        records the change, preserving the audit history while allowing
        the data correction.
      - Demo-data lifecycle: the seed script ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js
        runs as the platform admin (which bypasses this ACL via
        admin_overrides=true) but post-seed re-runs in interactive mode
        from the demo manager (sys_user_x_casemgmt_demo_manager.xml)
        depend on this ACL being applied so the manager can manually
        update a seeded demo party association during smoke testing
        without needing the admin login. The mix of Person and
        Organization seed parties per case (per AAP Section 0.5.1
        "at least one Person and one Organization party per demo case
        to exercise the polymorphic UI policy") is exercised both at
        seed-time (admin) and at validation-time (manager via THIS ACL).

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only context per AAP Section
    0.3.2; no code or configuration is byte-for-byte ported from these
    files):
      - acm-services/acm-service-users/src/main/java/com/armedia/acm/
        services/users/model/ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig.java
        ArkCase mapped roles to privileges through a single configuration
        map (`Map<String, List<Object>> rolesToPrivileges`) keyed by the
        property `application.rolesToPrivileges`. The class declares the
        constant `ROLES_TO_PRIVILEGES_PROP_KEY = "application.rolesToPrivileges"`
        and exposes the map via `@MapValue(value = "application.rolesToPrivileges")
        getRolesToPrivileges()`. In that model, a "manager-equivalent"
        role (e.g., ROLE_PERSON_MANAGER / ROLE_ORG_MANAGER) would have
        been associated with write privilege identifiers such as
        `acm-person-association-edit` and `acm-organization-association-
        edit` (one identifier per association table, since ArkCase used
        two separate tables). The ServiceNow target replaces this
        map-based privilege association with declarative, scoped record-
        level ACLs - this XML record is the direct equivalent of the
        union of those two ArkCase map cells: the (case_manager, WRITE)
        pairing on the polymorphic case_party domain that subsumes both
        Person and Organization variants.
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-admin-plugin/src/main/java/com/
        armedia/acm/plugins/admin/service/RolesPrivilegesService.java
        Encapsulated role-CRUD and privilege-paging behavior in ArkCase
        (`retrieveRoles()`, `retrievePrivileges()`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByAuthorization(...)`,
        `retrievePrivilegesByRole(...)`, `updateRolePrivileges(...)`,
        `addRolesPrivileges(...)`, `removeRolesPrivileges(...)`). The
        service held injected dependencies on `UserDao`, `ApplicationRolesConfig`,
        `ApplicationPrivilegesConfig`, `ApplicationRolesToPrivilegesConfig`,
        `ConfigurationPropertyService`, `CollectionPropertiesConfigurationService`,
        and `FunctionalAccessService` - a complex Spring/JPA stack that
        managed the role <-> privilege relationship at runtime. All of
        this Java service surface is replaced in the ServiceNow target by
        the platform's built-in sys_security_acl evaluator; no scripted
        privilege resolver is needed. Notably, ArkCase's
        `updateRolePrivileges(roleName, privileges)` would have rebuilt
        the role's privilege list and persisted it via
        `configurationPropertyService.updateProperties(...)` - that
        write-time bookkeeping is, in ServiceNow, accomplished by the
        admin author of THIS XML record committing the Update Set; no
        runtime mutation is required. THIS ACL governs the WRITE of
        CASE_PARTY RECORDS specifically; it does NOT govern WRITE of
        case rows (governed by ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_write_manager.xml)
        or case_task rows (governed by
        ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_write_manager.xml).

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.7.1 and 0.7.2):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: every cross-reference resolves into
        the x_casemgmt scope (sys_scope = x_casemgmt, sys_package source =
        x_casemgmt). No global-scope ACLs are written. The <name> field
        references the scoped table x_casemgmt_case_party (not any OOB
        global table such as `task` or `incident_task`), and <roles>
        references the scoped role x_casemgmt_case_manager. There are
        zero global writes from this file.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_id literals: <name>, <roles>,
        <sys_scope>, and <sys_package> all resolve their targets by
        name / source attribute lookup at Update Set apply time. The
        <sys_id> below is THIS record's own deterministic primary key
        (32-char lowercase hex MD5 of the canonical string
        "x_casemgmt_case_party.write.case_manager", a stable canonical
        identifier for this exact ACL) and is not a cross-reference to
        any other record. Computing the sys_id deterministically
        guarantees the ACL is re-applyable / idempotent across fresh
        PDIs and round-trip Update Set previews per AAP Section 0.7.3
        Gate 7 ("Update Set loads without errors on a fresh PDI
        instance").
      - Table-level (not field-level): <name> is `x_casemgmt_case_party`
        with NO dot. The case_party table has no field-level ACLs by
        design (unlike the parent case table which has field-level ACLs
        on assigned_group and assigned_agent), so this table-level
        write ACL fully governs manager write authority on every column.
        The <type>record</type> field below confirms this is a row-level
        (table-level) ACL, not a UI/REST/SOAP-flavored ACL.
      - Operation = write: corresponds exactly to the "Write = All" cell
        in the AAP matrix for the case_manager role mirrored to the
        case_party table.
      - admin_overrides = true: standard ServiceNow pattern that allows
        the platform `admin` role to bypass this ACL. This is required
        so platform administrators can troubleshoot, repair, or re-seed
        scoped party data (per AAP Section 0.7.4 the
        ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js script runs as admin to populate
        demo party rows). It does NOT widen case_manager privileges -
        non-admin managers see exactly what this ACL permits, which is
        full table-level write.
      - active = true: ACL is in force the moment the Update Set commits.
      - advanced = false: see "Why advanced=false" rationale above. The
        platform skips the empty <script/> body entirely.
      - condition (empty): the <condition/> encoded-query field is empty;
        no row-level filter applies to manager writes (manager has
        "All" access, not "Assigned only").
      - script (empty): the <script/> field is empty; the platform skips
        it because advanced=false.

    Difference from sibling ACLs - quick reference:
      vs ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_create_manager.xml (manager CREATE on case_party):
        - <operation>     write             vs create
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_casemgmt_case_party.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_casemgmt_case_party.create.case_manager")
        - <sys_update_name> *_write_manager vs *_create_manager
        - <description>                     differs in operation wording
      vs ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_read_manager.xml (manager READ on case_party):
        - <operation>     write             vs read
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_casemgmt_case_party.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_casemgmt_case_party.read.case_manager")
        - <sys_update_name> *_write_manager vs *_read_manager
      vs ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_delete_manager.xml (manager DELETE on case_party):
        - <operation>     write             vs delete
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_casemgmt_case_party.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_casemgmt_case_party.delete.case_manager")
        - <sys_update_name> *_write_manager vs *_delete_manager
      vs ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_write_agent_assigned.xml (agent WRITE assigned-only on case_party):
        - <roles>         x_casemgmt_case_manager
                                            vs x_casemgmt_case_agent
        - <advanced>      false             vs true (the agent ACL carries a
                                              scripted condition that
                                              dereferences current.case and
                                              evaluates the parent-case
                                              "Assigned only" predicate; the
                                              manager ACL is unconditional)
        - <condition>     empty             vs encoded query / parent-case filter
        - <script>        empty             vs server-side disjunction of
                                              parentCase.assigned_agent /
                                              parentCase.assigned_group checks
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_casemgmt_case_party.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_casemgmt_case_party.write.case_agent.assigned")
        - <sys_update_name> *_write_manager vs *_write_agent_assigned
      vs ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_write_manager.xml (manager WRITE on the parent case table):
        - <name>          x_casemgmt_case_party
                                            vs x_casemgmt_case
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_casemgmt_case_party.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_casemgmt_case.write.case_manager")
        - <sys_name>      x_casemgmt_case_party
                                            vs x_casemgmt_case
        - <sys_update_name> *_case_party_write_manager
                                            vs *_case_write_manager
      vs ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_write_manager.xml (manager WRITE on the case_task table):
        - <name>          x_casemgmt_case_party
                                            vs x_casemgmt_case_task
        - <sys_id>        MD5("x_casemgmt_case_party.write.case_manager")
                                            vs MD5("x_casemgmt_case_task.write.case_manager")
        - <sys_name>      x_casemgmt_case_party
                                            vs x_casemgmt_case_task
        - <sys_update_name> *_case_party_write_manager
                                            vs *_case_task_write_manager
      All other XML elements are identical between the manager-tier write
      ACLs across the three custom tables; the deterministic sys_id and
      the (table, operation, role) triplet are the defining differences.
      This uniformity is what guarantees the manager has IDENTICAL
      unconditional write authority on case, case_task, and case_party
      tables - exactly the AAP Section 0.5.6 "manager has full access"
      contract.

    Cross-dependencies and Update-Set ordering (AAP Section 0.5.2):
      MUST be loaded AFTER:
        - ../app/sys_app/x_casemgmt_case_management.xml (scoped app record)
        - ../app/sys_scope/x_casemgmt.xml (scope record - resolves
          sys_scope and sys_package source="x_casemgmt")
        - ../tables/x_casemgmt_case_party.xml (resolves
          <name>x_casemgmt_case_party</name> by table name lookup at apply
          time)
        - ../roles/sys_user_role_x_casemgmt_case_manager.xml (resolves
          <roles>x_casemgmt_case_manager</roles> by role name lookup at
          apply time)
      MUST be loaded BEFORE:
        - ../seed-data/role_assignments/sys_user_has_role_x_casemgmt_demo_manager.xml
          (the demo manager's write access during round-trip verification
          depends on this ACL being applied first)
        - ../seed-data/parties/x_casemgmt_case_party_demo_*.xml seed records
          insertion (the demo party rows are inserted by the seed script
          running as admin, which bypasses this ACL via admin_overrides;
          however, post-seed manual updates to demo parties by the demo
          manager during round-trip verification depend on this ACL being
          applied first)
        - any cleanup or re-seed activity in
          ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js that may update prior demo party
          rows; while seed_demo_data.js itself runs as admin and bypasses
          this ACL via admin_overrides, post-seed smoke tests against the
          demo dataset depend on this ACL being applied so a logged-in
          demo manager can validate end-to-end party-write capability.
      The deny-by-default sibling that this file works with:
        - x_casemgmt_case_party_write_viewer.xml (DOES NOT EXIST - by
          design; case_viewer Write=No is enforced structurally by the
          absence of a granting ACL)
      Adding x_casemgmt_case_party_write_viewer.xml would VIOLATE the AAP
      Section 0.5.6 matrix and MUST NOT be done by any future agent.

    Mirror relationship to ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_write_manager.xml and
    ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_write_manager.xml:
      This file is the case_party-table analog of the manager-write ACL
      already authored for the case and case_task tables. The ONLY
      differences between those files and this one are:
        - <name>             x_casemgmt_case_party  (vs x_casemgmt_case
                                                    or x_casemgmt_case_task)
        - <sys_id>           MD5("x_casemgmt_case_party.write.case_manager")
                                                   (the deterministic key
                                                    derived from a stable
                                                    canonical identifier
                                                    unique to this ACL)
        - <sys_name>         x_casemgmt_case_party  (vs x_casemgmt_case
                                                    or x_casemgmt_case_task)
        - <sys_update_name>  sys_security_acl_x_casemgmt_case_party_write_manager
                                                   (vs the equivalent for
                                                    case / case_task)
        - <description>      references the case_party table semantic
      All other fields (active, admin_overrides, advanced, condition,
      operation, roles, script, sys_class_name, sys_created_by, sys_policy,
      sys_scope, sys_package, type, audit timestamps) are byte-for-byte
      identical so that the manager's write privilege is uniformly
      unconditional across every table in the scoped application as the
      AAP matrix mandates.

    The concrete scope identifier `casemgmt` is used verbatim per AAP convention (Section 0.7.2 "Scoped-namespace-only constraint"). ServiceNow Update Set imports use a standard XML parser, so the
    scope id is concrete in the XML before export. The same identifier
    is used consistently across every artifact in this scoped application. The deterministic sys_id below is computed against the
    `casemgmt` literal and remains stable across re-imports onto fresh
    PDIs.
-->
<record_update table="sys_security_acl">
    <sys_security_acl action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <admin_overrides>true</admin_overrides>
        <advanced>false</advanced>
        <condition/>
        <description>Allows users with the x_casemgmt_case_manager role to write/update all case_party records (unconditional). Per AAP Section 0.5.6, manager Write=All on case_party. NO field-level ACLs exist on case_party; this table-level grant fully governs manager write authority on every column.</description>
        <name>x_casemgmt_case_party</name>
        <operation>write</operation>
        <roles>x_casemgmt_case_manager</roles>
        <script/>
        <sys_class_name>sys_security_acl</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>fc7c07fba024d5b59b782d83d22156b4</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>x_casemgmt_case_party</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_casemgmt">x_casemgmt</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_casemgmt</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_security_acl_x_casemgmt_case_party_write_manager</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <type>record</type>
    </sys_security_acl>
</record_update>
