<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the `sys_ui_action` row that
    declares the `Close` form button on the `x_casemgmt_case` custom table
    inside the scoped application `x_casemgmt`.

    The concrete scope identifier `x_casemgmt` is used consistently throughout
    this repository per ../docs/state-machine.md: "ServiceNow Update Set imports
    use a standard XML parser, so the scope id must be concrete in every record
    before the Update Set is exported." All sibling XML records in this Update
    Set use `x_casemgmt` byte-for-byte; this UI Action follows the same
    convention. The AAP Section 0.7.2 placeholder `x_[scope]_` is a TEMPLATE
    that resolves to `x_casemgmt_` at materialization time.

    PURPOSE (AAP Section 0.5.5 verbatim, row 6):
        From          To             Required condition / behavior
        Resolved      Closed         Caller has x_casemgmt_case_manager role;
                                     auto-set closed_date.
                                     Failure: Surface form-level error.

    This UI Action is the user-facing ENTRY POINT for the Resolved -> Closed
    transition - the FINAL forward transition in the case state-machine
    (Draft -> Open -> In Progress -> [Pending <-> In Progress] -> Resolved
    -> Closed). It surfaces a "Close" button on the case form whenever the
    case is currently in `Resolved` status AND the current user holds the
    x_casemgmt_case_manager role. Clicking the button advances the case to
    Closed status, provided that the transition guard `canTransitionToClosed`
    from the central Script Include
    ../script_includes/x_casemgmt_CaseTransitionValidator.xml passes (i.e.,
    the user holds the case_manager role). Failure surfaces a verbatim
    blocking error message via gs.addErrorMessage on the form per AAP
    Section 0.7.1.

    THE CLOSURE TRANSITION - WHY CLOSE IS THE TERMINAL TRANSITION:

        Resolved -> Closed is the FINAL transition in the case lifecycle.
        Once a case reaches Closed status, the
        ../business_rules/x_casemgmt_block_terminal_closed.xml before-update
        Business Rule (order=100) PROHIBITS any further modification per AAP
        Section 0.5.5 row 8 (terminal state) with the verbatim AAP Section
        0.7.4 message: "Closed cases are terminal and cannot be modified."
        This is the canonical anti-regression guard that protects the
        irreversibility of closure.

        The role check (case_manager only) reflects AAP Section 0.5.6 ACL
        matrix:
          - case_manager: Create + Read All + Write All + Delete -> CAN close
          - case_agent:   Create + Read Assigned + Write Assigned -> CANNOT close
          - case_viewer:  Read All only                          -> CANNOT close
        Only case_manager has the authority to terminally close a case
        because closure is an irreversible administrative action. case_agents
        progress cases through Open/In Progress/Pending/Resolved but cannot
        terminally close them. case_viewers are read-only.

        The check is delegated to the central Script Include's
        canTransitionToClosed(caseGr, userId) method. Per AAP Section 0.7.2
        Rule 5 ("Delegate to Script Include - DO NOT inline the role check"),
        the UI Action does NOT inline the role-membership query. The Script
        Include is the SINGLE SOURCE OF TRUTH for both the role check AND
        the verbatim error message text "Only case managers can close
        cases.", shared with:
          - ../flows/sub_flows/validate_closed_transition.xml (the Flow
            Designer subflow that fires on the OnUpdate trigger of the two
            parent state-machine flows; covers non-form transition paths
            like Table API and scripted REST)
          - Any future scripted REST endpoint or scheduled job that performs
            Resolved -> Closed transitions

        Centralizing the guard in the Script Include guarantees that the
        error message text is identical across all callers (no drift between
        this UI Action's surfaced message and the flow's surfaced message),
        and future rule changes (e.g., requiring a closure_reason or
        closure_outcome) only need to be made in the Script Include.

    THE CLOSED_DATE SIDE-EFFECT (set_closed_date Business Rule):

        Per AAP Section 0.5.5 row 6 ("auto-set closed_date"), the closure
        timestamp is auto-populated when status transitions to Closed. This
        UI Action does NOT set current.closed_date directly; instead, it
        sets current.status = 'Closed' and calls current.update(), and the
        ../business_rules/x_casemgmt_set_closed_date.xml before-update
        Business Rule (order=500) fires on the same transaction and sets
        current.closed_date = gs.nowDateTime() before the database write
        completes.

        This separation is intentional and follows the SINGLE-RESPONSIBILITY
        principle:
          - The UI Action's responsibility: validate the transition and set
            the new status.
          - The Business Rule's responsibility: maintain the closed_date
            invariant (closed_date is non-null IFF status == Closed).

        The Business Rule fires for ALL Resolved -> Closed transitions,
        including those triggered by:
          - This UI Action (form button click)
          - The Flow Designer subflow validate_closed_transition.xml
          - Direct Table API edits (e.g., scripted REST endpoints)
          - Future scheduled jobs or background scripts
        Centralizing the closed_date logic in the BR guarantees consistency
        regardless of the trigger path.

    THE TERMINAL-STATE GUARD (block_terminal_closed Business Rule):

        Per AAP Section 0.5.5 row 8 ("Closed -> *: PROHIBITED - Terminal state"),
        once a case is Closed, ANY further update is rejected by the
        ../business_rules/x_casemgmt_block_terminal_closed.xml Business Rule
        (order=100, the highest priority). The BR's check is:
            previous.status == 'Closed'  -> abort with verbatim message
                "Closed cases are terminal and cannot be modified."
        This BR fires BEFORE this UI Action's update would complete... but
        only on the SUBSEQUENT update. For THIS UI Action's update, the
        previous status is 'Resolved' (not 'Closed') - so the BR is a no-op
        for this transition.

        The terminal-state guard takes effect on the FIRST update AFTER this
        UI Action commits. From that point forward, any attempt to modify
        the case (whether via UI, Table API, scripted REST, or otherwise)
        is rejected by the BR. This is the canonical anti-regression
        guarantee that closure is irreversible.

        Edge case: if a stale-form attack tries to click Close on an
        already-Closed case, the platform's standard form-button verb
        pipeline calls this UI Action's <script> body. The defense-in-depth
        status check (current.status != 'Resolved') would catch this (since
        a Closed case has status='Closed', not 'Resolved') and surface
        "Only Resolved cases can be closed.". Even if that defensive check
        somehow failed, the block_terminal_closed BR would catch the update
        attempt and surface the verbatim AAP Section 0.7.4 message.

    SERVER-SIDE-ONLY PATTERN (matches sibling case_open.xml, case_resolve.xml,
    case_resume.xml, case_start_progress.xml; contrasts with case_set_pending.xml):

        This Close UI Action runs ENTIRELY on the server. There is no input
        to collect from the user beyond the click - the transition has no
        required parameters (no closure_reason, no closure_outcome, etc. -
        per the MINIMAL-CHANGE-CLAUSE in AAP Section 0.7.2). The single
        click invokes the server script directly via the platform's
        standard form-button verb pipeline, with no <onclick> JavaScript
        and no client-side function definition.

        Phase 1 - User clicks the "Close" button.
        Phase 2 - The platform evaluates the visibility <condition> on the
                  server when the form was rendered; the button is shown
                  only if the condition was true (status==Resolved AND
                  user has case_manager role).
        Phase 3 - The platform invokes the form-submit verb derived from
                  this UI Action's sys_name (`sysverb_x_casemgmt_case_close`).
        Phase 4 - The platform binds `current` (the case GlideRecord),
                  `gs` (GlideSystem), `action` (UI Action helper), and
                  evaluates the <script> body in a server sandbox.
        Phase 5 - The script performs three layers of defense-in-depth
                  validation (role, status, transition guard via Script
                  Include) before executing the transition.
        Phase 6 - The script sets current.status = 'Closed' and calls
                  current.update() ONCE to persist the change.
        Phase 7 - The script calls action.setRedirectURL(current) to
                  refresh the form so the operator sees the updated status
                  AND the auto-populated closed_date stamp.

        The single current.update() call triggers the platform's full
        before-update Business Rule pipeline, including:
          - x_casemgmt_block_terminal_closed.xml (no-op because previous
            status is Resolved, not Closed)
          - x_casemgmt_block_draft_backtransition.xml (no-op because
            target is Closed, not Draft)
          - x_casemgmt_validate_assigned_agent_membership.xml (passes if
            assigned_agent is still a member of assigned_group; in normal
            workflow this should already be true when the case reached
            Resolved)
          - x_casemgmt_clear_pending_reason_on_inprogress.xml (no-op
            because target is Closed, not In Progress; pending_reason
            should already be empty since Resolved has no pending_reason)
          - x_casemgmt_set_closed_date.xml (FIRES - target is Closed and
            previous is Resolved; auto-populates closed_date =
            gs.nowDateTime() before the database write completes)

        The two Flow Designer flows (general_inquiry_state_machine.xml
        and complaint_state_machine.xml) also fire on this update via
        their OnUpdate triggers filtered on `status` change, calling the
        validate_closed_transition subflow which itself delegates to
        x_casemgmt.CaseTransitionValidator.canTransitionToClosed() - the
        SAME helper this UI Action calls. Together they form a defense-in-depth
        guard pair: the UI Action blocks the transition at the form level
        (better UX - user sees the error message immediately), and the
        flow blocks it at the workflow level (catches Table API and other
        non-form paths).

    SEMANTIC SOURCE-SIDE REFERENCE (read-only context, NOT byte-for-byte
    ported per AAP Section 0.2.1):

        acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-case-file-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/casefile/service/ChangeCaseFileStateService.java
        line 79-114 - the central ArkCase case state-machine service. Its
        `changeCaseState(auth, caseId, newState, ipAddress)` method
        contains the canonical Java reference (line 97-100):

            if ("CLOSED".equals(newState))
            {
                retval.setClosed(now);
            }

        This is the EXACT semantic counterpart of this UI Action's behavior
        plus the cooperating set_closed_date BR: when the new state is
        "CLOSED", the close timestamp is set. The ServiceNow target splits
        the responsibility:
          - This UI Action sets current.status = 'Closed' (the user's
            intent, expressed via the button click) and calls current.update().
          - The set_closed_date BR (order=500) sets current.closed_date =
            gs.nowDateTime() during the same before-update pipeline.
        The split is more maintainable than ArkCase's monolithic
        changeCaseState method because:
          - Future changes to the close-time semantics (e.g., capturing
            the user who closed the case in addition to the timestamp)
            only require a BR change, not a UI Action change.
          - The closed_date side-effect fires for ALL Resolved -> Closed
            transitions, not just those triggered through the UI button.

        That single Java method covered EVERY transition by string-matching
        the `newState` parameter. The ServiceNow target instead splits
        per-transition logic across:
          - This UI Action (Resolved -> Closed, the close edge)
          - Sibling UI Actions for every other transition
          - The central Script Include CaseTransitionValidator (single
            source of truth for transition guards, called from this UI
            Action AND from the Flow Designer subflow
            validate_closed_transition.xml)
          - The two parent state-machine flows (which also trigger on
            this status change via their OnUpdate filters)
          - The cooperating Business Rules (set_closed_date for the
            timestamp side-effect; block_terminal_closed for subsequent
            anti-regression)

        Per AAP Section 0.7.2 the email-notification-disabled constraint
        explicitly excludes the equivalent of ArkCase's raiseEvent() call
        (line 106 in ChangeCaseFileStateService.java). The ServiceNow POC
        contains zero gs.eventQueue() calls - the email-disabled PDI does
        not need notification listeners and including them would violate
        the AAP constraint.

    BUTTON VISIBILITY CONDITION (the <condition> field):

        The button is shown when ALL of the following are true:
          1) current.status == 'Resolved'  (the source state of the
             Resolved -> Closed transition)
          2) The current user holds the x_casemgmt_case_manager role
             (the ONLY role authorized to terminally close cases per
             AAP Section 0.5.5 row 6 verbatim)

        Unlike the sibling case_resolve.xml UI Action (which is visible
        to BOTH case_manager AND assigned case_agent), this Close button
        is visible to case_manager ONLY. The reason: per AAP Section
        0.5.5 row 6, "Caller has x_casemgmt_case_manager role" is a
        REQUIRED condition for the Resolved -> Closed transition. agents
        cannot terminally close cases - they can only progress them
        through the working states (Open/In Progress/Pending/Resolved).

        The visibility check runs server-side (the <condition> field is
        evaluated by the platform when rendering the form). The
        defense-in-depth check inside the <script> body re-validates the
        same conditions on the server when the button is clicked, providing
        two layers of validation that protect against:
          - Form-tampering attacks where the user edits hidden form fields
            to attempt the transition from a non-Resolved state
          - Race conditions where the user opens the form, the case
            transitions out of Resolved in another browser tab, then the
            user clicks Close in the original tab
          - Role escalation attempts where a non-manager somehow gains
            access to the form

    ORDER WITHIN UI ACTION SEQUENCE:

        order=600 places Close as the LAST UI Action in the workflow
        sequence (the terminal transition):
            1) Open               (order=100       - Draft -> Open)
            2) Start Progress     (order=200       - Open -> In Progress)
            3) Set Pending        (order=300       - In Progress -> Pending)
            4) Resume             (order=400       - Pending -> In Progress)
            5) Resolve            (order=500       - In Progress -> Resolved)
            6) Close              (order=600, THIS - Resolved -> Closed)

        The ordering is for UI display only - the platform renders form
        buttons in ascending order. Only one button is visible at a time
        (each visibility <condition> matches a different status), so the
        ordering does not affect runtime correctness. Close carries
        order=600 because it is the LAST transition in the canonical
        forward sequence; it is rendered last in the button bar.

    FORM_STYLE = destructive:

        Close is the TERMINAL action. Once executed, the case can never be
        modified again (per the block_terminal_closed BR). The button is
        rendered with the platform's "destructive" visual style (typically
        a red-tinted button) to draw the user's attention to the
        irreversibility of the action. This contrasts with sibling UI
        Actions:
          - Open, Start Progress, Resume, Resolve all use form_style=primary
            (blue/affirmative) - the case is moving forward through working
            states
          - Set Pending uses form_style=secondary (subdued) - the case is
            paused but still active
          - Close uses form_style=destructive (red/terminal) - the case
            is permanently closed and cannot be modified again

        The destructive style is the canonical platform pattern for
        irreversible record-state changes. It is consistent with how
        out-of-the-box ServiceNow tables (e.g., incident, problem, change)
        style their terminal-transition buttons.

    MANAGER-ONLY VISIBILITY (AAP Section 0.5.5 row 6 + AAP Section 0.5.6
    ACL Matrix):

        Only x_casemgmt_case_manager sees the Close button. The rationale
        per AAP Section 0.5.6 ACL Matrix:

          - case_manager has full access (Create + Read All + Write All +
            Delete on the case table). Close is a Write operation that
            also has the SPECIAL semantics of being TERMINAL (per AAP
            Section 0.5.5 row 8 verbatim "Closed: Terminal state. No
            transitions permitted from Closed."). Per AAP Section 0.5.5
            row 6, ONLY case_manager has the authority to perform this
            terminal transition.

          - case_agent has Write Assigned only access. They can transition
            cases through Open/In Progress/Pending/Resolved (the working
            states) but cannot terminally close them. case_agent is
            therefore EXCLUDED from the <roles> field.

          - case_viewer has Read All only access (no Write). Close is a
            Write operation. case_viewer is therefore excluded from the
            <roles> field.

        The visibility <condition> further filters case_manager visibility
        to Resolved-status cases only:
            current.status == 'Resolved'
        case_manager would otherwise see the Close button on cases in
        every status, which would be confusing UX. The status filter
        ensures the button only appears on cases that are eligible for
        the Resolved -> Closed transition.

    DELEGATION TO Script Include (canTransitionToClosed):

        Per the assigned-folder requirements: "[The UI Action] delegates
        validation to x_casemgmt.CaseTransitionValidator.canTransitionToClosed()
        - single source of truth across UI Actions, flows, and business
        rules". This is encoded in the <script> body via:
            var validator = new x_casemgmt.CaseTransitionValidator();
            var result = validator.canTransitionToClosed(current, gs.getUserID());

        The Script Include's canTransitionToClosed(caseGr, userId) method
        returns:
          { ok: true } when the user has the case_manager role, OR
          { ok: false, error: 'Only case managers can close cases.' }
            when the role check fails, OR
          { ok: false, error: 'Case record is missing.' } when caseGr
            is null/undefined (defensive guard against unexpected input)

        The Script Include accepts the userId parameter (via gs.getUserID()
        in this UI Action's calling context) so that the same method can
        be called from non-current-user contexts (e.g., from a system-context
        scheduled job that needs to verify the role membership of a
        different user). The current-user-by-default branch is exercised
        by THIS UI Action since gs.getUserID() always returns the current
        session user. The non-current-user branch is exercised by future
        scheduled jobs or scripted REST endpoints.

        The result.error string is surfaced VERBATIM via gs.addErrorMessage,
        NOT replaced with a hardcoded UI-Action-local message. This
        guarantees that the surfaced error message text is identical
        across all callers (this UI Action, the Flow Designer subflow
        validate_closed_transition.xml, and any future scripted REST
        endpoint or scheduled job).

    DEFENSE-IN-DEPTH STATUS CHECK (current.status != 'Resolved' guard):

        Even though the visibility <condition> already gates the button
        on `current.status == 'Resolved'`, the <script> body re-validates
        on the server when the button is clicked. The defensive re-check
        protects against:

          - Stale-form attack: User opens the form when status is
            Resolved, the case transitions in another browser tab (e.g.,
            another manager already closes it), then the user clicks
            Close in the original tab. Without the defensive re-check,
            the second click would attempt to "close" an already-Closed
            case, which would either:
              (a) fail silently (bad UX), OR
              (b) fail with the cryptic block_terminal_closed BR error
                  message, which while technically correct does not
                  educate the user about the underlying staleness.
            With the defensive re-check, the user receives an immediate
            and informative blocking error: "Only Resolved cases can be
            closed."

          - Direct Table API attack: User crafts an HTTP POST to the
            Table API endpoint that mimics the form-submit verb. Without
            the defensive re-check, the POST would bypass the form-render
            <condition> entirely. The defensive re-check catches this.

          - Race condition with the OnUpdate flow: The Flow Designer
            flow could potentially modify the case status between the
            form render and the user's click. The defensive re-check
            catches this.

    DEFENSIVE ROLE RE-CHECK (gs.getUser().hasRole guard):

        The visibility <condition> and <roles> field already restrict the
        button to case_manager users. The <script> body re-validates the
        role on the server-side click handler. The defensive re-check
        protects against:

          - Role-escalation attack: User holds the case_manager role
            when the form is rendered (button is shown), then the role
            is revoked between form render and click. Without the
            defensive re-check, the click would still succeed.

          - Direct Table API attack: User crafts an HTTP POST to the
            Table API endpoint that mimics the form-submit verb. Without
            the defensive re-check, the POST would bypass the <roles>
            field's visibility filter entirely.

          - Form-tampering attack: User edits hidden form fields or
            otherwise crafts a malicious form-submit payload. The
            server-side re-check catches this.

        The defensive re-check is the FIRST guard (before the status
        check) so that role-escalation attempts surface a role-specific
        error message ("Only case managers can close cases.") rather
        than a status-specific message that might leak workflow
        information.

    DETERMINISTIC SYS_ID:

        Per AAP Section 0.7.2 Rule 2 ("No hardcoded sys_ids - every
        cross-reference is a GlideRecord lookup by stable, human-readable
        key"), this UI Action's <sys_id> below is computed deterministically
        from the sys_name via:
            printf '%s' 'x_casemgmt_case_close' | md5sum | cut -c1-32

        Deriving from the record name guarantees idempotent re-import on
        a fresh PDI: re-importing the same Update Set produces the same
        sys_id, which collides on the existing record and updates it in
        place rather than creating a duplicate. This is the same convention
        used by all sibling UI Actions in this folder (Open, Start Progress,
        Set Pending, Resume, Resolve, Close).

    VALIDATION GATE MAPPING (AAP Section 0.7.3):

        - Gate 2 (Workflow): "All state transitions enforced for both
          case types - Invalid transitions return blocking error". This
          UI Action is the PRIMARY user-facing trigger for the Resolved
          -> Closed transition (per AAP Section 0.5.5 row 6). The Script
          Include's canTransitionToClosed enforces the case_manager role
          check and surfaces the verbatim message "Only case managers
          can close cases." if violated. The defense-in-depth role and
          status re-checks prevent stale-form submissions from corrupting
          the state machine.

        - Gate 3 (ACLs): "Role-based access enforced - case_viewer cannot
          write; case_agent cannot access unassigned cases; case_manager
          has full access". This UI Action's visibility <condition>,
          <roles> field, and server-side defense-in-depth check all
          encode the role rules from AAP Section 0.5.6 verbatim.
          case_viewer is excluded by the
          <roles>x_casemgmt_case_manager</roles> field. case_agent is
          excluded by the same field (Close requires manager role
          regardless of assignment).

        - Gate 7 (Update Set): "Scoped app exported - Update Set loads
          without errors on a fresh PDI instance". The deterministic
          sys_id, reference-by-name pattern, and absence of any external
          lookups guarantee this UI Action re-imports cleanly with zero
          preview errors.

    COMPANION ARTIFACTS:

        This UI Action handles the Resolved -> Closed transition at the
        FORM-LEVEL (button click). Companion artifacts:

          - ../script_includes/x_casemgmt_CaseTransitionValidator.xml
            (the central transition-guard helper; this UI Action's
             canTransitionToClosed call delegates to its method of the
             same name)
          - ../flows/sub_flows/validate_closed_transition.xml
            (the Flow Designer subflow that runs the SAME guard via
             the parent state-machine flows' OnUpdate trigger; covers
             non-form transition paths like Table API and scripted REST)
          - ../business_rules/x_casemgmt_set_closed_date.xml
            (the cooperating order=500 BR that sets closed_date =
             gs.nowDateTime() on the same before-update transaction
             when status transitions to Closed; this UI Action TRIGGERS
             that BR by calling current.update())
          - ../business_rules/x_casemgmt_block_terminal_closed.xml
            (the order=100 BR that PREVENTS subsequent updates to a
             Closed case; this UI Action's update is allowed because
             previous.status is Resolved, not Closed; future updates
             will be rejected by this BR)
          - ../ui_action/x_casemgmt_case_resolve.xml
            (the PRECEDING UI Action that handles In Progress ->
             Resolved; that transition makes Close eligible)
          - ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml
            (parent OnUpdate flow filtered on type=General Inquiry;
             fires on this transition and re-validates via the
             validate_closed_transition subflow)
          - ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml
            (parent OnUpdate flow filtered on type=Complaint; fires on
             this transition and re-validates via the
             validate_closed_transition subflow)
          - ../roles/sys_user_role_x_casemgmt_case_manager.xml
            (the role checked by <roles>, <condition>, the script,
             and the Script Include's canTransitionToClosed method)

        The UI Action provides the FORM-LEVEL entry point (button). The
        Script Include provides the GUARD LOGIC and the verbatim error
        message (single source of truth). The flows provide the
        WORKFLOW-LEVEL hook (covers non-form paths). The business rules
        provide the FIELD-LEVEL housekeeping (set_closed_date) and the
        TERMINAL-STATE GUARD (block_terminal_closed). They are
        complementary, not redundant.

    REGENERATION NOTE:

        This XML file is generated as part of the Update Set authoring
        process. To regenerate:
          1. Re-run the source-of-truth template fill from the AAP.
          2. Recompute the deterministic sys_id from MD5(sys_name):
             printf '%s' 'x_casemgmt_case_close' | md5sum | cut -c1-32
          3. Re-export the Update Set XML from the PDI.

        Manual edits to this file are valid but should be reflected in
        ../docs/state-machine.md if they alter the transition matrix or
        error message text.
-->

<record_update table="sys_ui_action">
    <sys_ui_action action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <action_name>x_casemgmt_case_close</action_name>
        <active>true</active>
        <client>false</client>
        <comments>UI Action that transitions a Resolved case to Closed status. Visible only to x_casemgmt_case_manager users on cases with status=Resolved (per AAP Section 0.5.5 row 6 verbatim: "Resolved -&gt; Closed: Caller has x_casemgmt_case_manager role; auto-set closed_date - Surface form-level error"). Delegates the role check to x_casemgmt.CaseTransitionValidator.canTransitionToClosed() (single source of truth shared with ../flows/sub_flows/validate_closed_transition.xml). Server-side-only (no client prompt) - the transition has no required parameters beyond the existing Resolved status. Performs the transition on the server with defense-in-depth re-validation of role and status. Surfaces a form-level blocking error via gs.addErrorMessage if any guard fails (verbatim message "Only case managers can close cases." returned by the Script Include). The closed_date field is auto-populated by the cooperating ../business_rules/x_casemgmt_set_closed_date.xml before-update Business Rule (order=500) on the same current.update() transaction triggered by this UI Action - this UI Action sets only current.status='Closed', the BR sets current.closed_date=gs.nowDateTime(). After the transition completes, the ../business_rules/x_casemgmt_block_terminal_closed.xml before-update Business Rule (order=100) prevents any subsequent modifications to the case (per AAP Section 0.5.5 row 8 terminal-state rule). Contains zero gs.eventQueue() calls per the email-disabled constraint, zero hardcoded sys_id literals, and zero PII.</comments>
        <condition><![CDATA[current.status == 'Resolved' && gs.getUser().hasRole('x_casemgmt_case_manager')]]></condition>
        <form_action>true</form_action>
        <form_button>true</form_button>
        <form_button_v2>false</form_button_v2>
        <form_context_menu>false</form_context_menu>
        <form_link>false</form_link>
        <form_menu_button_v2>false</form_menu_button_v2>
        <form_style>destructive</form_style>
        <format_for_configurable_workspace>false</format_for_configurable_workspace>
        <hint>Close this case (case_manager role required; case must be in Resolved status). closed_date will be auto-populated. This action is TERMINAL - the case cannot be modified after closure.</hint>
        <isolate_script>true</isolate_script>
        <list_action>false</list_action>
        <list_banner_button>false</list_banner_button>
        <list_button>false</list_button>
        <list_choice>false</list_choice>
        <list_context_menu>false</list_context_menu>
        <list_link>false</list_link>
        <list_save_with_form_button>false</list_save_with_form_button>
        <messages/>
        <name>Close</name>
        <onclick/>
        <order>600</order>
        <roles>x_casemgmt_case_manager</roles>
        <script><![CDATA[(function() {
    // Per AAP Section 0.5.5 row 6 (Resolved -> Closed):
    //   "Caller has x_casemgmt_case_manager role; auto-set closed_date"
    //   "Surface form-level error" on failure
    // Per AAP Section 0.7.1: blocking errors must appear on the form.
    // Per AAP Section 0.7.4: blocking-error messages must come from the
    //   single-source-of-truth Script Include (no inlined hardcoded
    //   error strings).
    //
    // This is the SERVER-side click handler for the Close form button.
    // It runs in the server sandbox (no window, has current GlideRecord,
    // has gs and action) and is responsible for:
    //   1) Defense-in-depth role re-check (must be case_manager).
    //   2) Defense-in-depth status re-check (must be 'Resolved').
    //   3) Delegation to the central Script Include's canTransitionToClosed
    //      method, which encapsulates the case_manager role guard AND
    //      the verbatim error message text.
    //   4) Status persistence (current.status = 'Closed'; current.update()).
    //      The cooperating set_closed_date Business Rule (order=500)
    //      fires on this update and auto-populates closed_date =
    //      gs.nowDateTime() before the database write completes.
    //   5) Form refresh (action.setRedirectURL(current)).
    //
    // Each of the three guards above maps to a row in the AAP Section
    // 0.5.6 ACL matrix or the AAP Section 0.5.5 transition map:
    //   - Guard 1: Role check enforces "Only case_manager can close
    //     cases" (case_agent and case_viewer are excluded per AAP
    //     Section 0.5.5 row 6 verbatim).
    //   - Guard 2: Status check enforces "Only Resolved -> Closed" (no
    //     other transition can fire this handler).
    //   - Guard 3: The Script Include's canTransitionToClosed check
    //     enforces the case_manager role per the AAP transition map;
    //     on failure it returns the verbatim "Only case managers can
    //     close cases." message.
    //
    // All three guards must pass before current.update() is called.
    // Any guard failure surfaces a blocking gs.addErrorMessage and
    // returns without persisting.

    // Guard 1: Role check. The user must hold case_manager.
    // The visibility <condition> and <roles> field already gate the
    // button on this role, but the server-side re-check protects
    // against the rare case where a user lost the role between form
    // load and form submit, and against attempts to invoke the
    // form-submit verb directly via Table API. The defensive role
    // re-check is the FIRST guard so that role-escalation attempts
    // surface a role-specific error rather than a status-specific
    // message that might leak workflow information.
    if (!gs.getUser().hasRole('x_casemgmt_case_manager')) {
        gs.addErrorMessage('Only case managers can close cases.');
        action.setRedirectURL(current);
        return;
    }

    // Guard 2: Status check. The case must currently be Resolved.
    // Re-checking on the server protects against a stale-form attack
    // where the user opens the form when status is Resolved, the
    // case transitions in another tab (e.g., another manager closes
    // it), then the user submits from the original tab. The check
    // uses string comparison against the verbatim Title Case
    // 'Resolved' label per AAP Section 0.5.7 (the choice value
    // defined in ../choices/sys_choice_case_status.xml). Without the
    // defensive re-check, a stale-form click on an already-Closed
    // case would fail with the cryptic block_terminal_closed BR
    // error message, which while technically correct does not
    // educate the user about the underlying staleness. With this
    // re-check, the user receives an immediate and informative
    // blocking error: "Only Resolved cases can be closed."
    if (current.status != 'Resolved') {
        gs.addErrorMessage('Only Resolved cases can be closed.');
        action.setRedirectURL(current);
        return;
    }

    // Guard 3: Transition guard. Delegate the role check to the
    // central Script Include - the SINGLE SOURCE OF TRUTH for both
    // the case_manager role check AND the verbatim error message
    // text, shared with the Flow Designer subflow
    // ../flows/sub_flows/validate_closed_transition.xml. Centralizing
    // the guard guarantees that:
    //   - The verbatim error message "Only case managers can close
    //     cases." is identical across all callers (no drift between
    //     this UI Action's surfaced message and the flow's surfaced
    //     message).
    //   - Future rule changes (e.g., requiring a closure_reason or
    //     adding a second precondition like "all parties must be
    //     associated") only need to be made in the Script Include.
    //   - The role membership check lives in only one place (the
    //     Script Include's canTransitionToClosed helper), avoiding
    //     duplication and ensuring consistent role-resolution
    //     semantics (current-user-by-default with explicit-userId
    //     branch for non-current-user contexts).
    //
    // The Script Include's canTransitionToClosed(caseGr, userId) method
    // returns:
    //   { ok: true } when the user has the case_manager role, OR
    //   { ok: false, error: 'Only case managers can close cases.' }
    //     when the role check fails (the VERBATIM message), OR
    //   { ok: false, error: 'Case record is missing.' } when caseGr
    //     is null/undefined (defensive guard against unexpected input).
    //
    // The userId parameter is gs.getUserID() (the current session
    // user); the Script Include's logic short-circuits to gs.getUser()
    // for current-user-by-default, which is the most efficient
    // role-membership-check path.
    //
    // The result.error string is surfaced VERBATIM via gs.addErrorMessage,
    // NOT replaced with a hardcoded UI-Action-local message. This
    // honors the agent prompt's Rule 5 ("Delegate to Script Include -
    // single source of truth") and Rule 6 ("Surface Errors via
    // gs.addErrorMessage() - Display the Script Include's result.error
    // on form").
    var validator = new x_casemgmt.CaseTransitionValidator();
    var result = validator.canTransitionToClosed(current, gs.getUserID());
    if (!result.ok) {
        gs.addErrorMessage(result.error);
        action.setRedirectURL(current);
        return;
    }

    // All three guards passed. Perform the Resolved -> Closed
    // transition. The status assignment uses the verbatim Title Case
    // 'Closed' label per AAP Section 0.5.7 and the sibling choice
    // file ../choices/sys_choice_case_status.xml.
    //
    // The single current.update() call triggers the platform's full
    // before-update Business Rule pipeline, including:
    //   - block_terminal_closed (order=100, no-op for THIS update
    //     because previous.status is Resolved, not Closed; will
    //     PREVENT all subsequent updates after this one completes)
    //   - block_draft_backtransition (no-op, target is Closed not
    //     Draft)
    //   - validate_assigned_agent_membership (passes if assigned_agent
    //     is still a member of assigned_group; in normal workflow
    //     this should already be true when the case reached Resolved)
    //   - clear_pending_reason_on_inprogress (no-op, target is Closed
    //     not In Progress; pending_reason should already be empty
    //     since Resolved has no pending_reason)
    //   - set_closed_date (FIRES, order=500: target is Closed and
    //     previous is Resolved; auto-populates current.closed_date =
    //     gs.nowDateTime() before the database write completes - this
    //     is the AAP Section 0.5.5 row 6 "auto-set closed_date"
    //     side-effect)
    //
    // The two parent state-machine flows (general_inquiry_state_machine
    // and complaint_state_machine) ALSO fire on this update via their
    // OnUpdate triggers filtered on `status` change, calling the
    // validate_closed_transition subflow which itself delegates to
    // x_casemgmt.CaseTransitionValidator.canTransitionToClosed() -
    // the SAME helper this UI Action just called. Belt-and-suspenders
    // defense in depth.
    //
    // After this update completes, ANY future modification attempt
    // will be REJECTED by the block_terminal_closed BR (order=100)
    // with the verbatim AAP Section 0.7.4 message "Closed cases are
    // terminal and cannot be modified." This is the canonical
    // anti-regression guarantee that closure is irreversible.
    current.status = 'Closed';
    current.update();

    // Refresh the form to show the new status AND the auto-populated
    // closed_date stamp. The standard ServiceNow UI-Action pattern
    // is to call action.setRedirectURL(current) which navigates the
    // browser to the same record's form view, picking up the new
    // status and any side-effect field changes (e.g., closed_date
    // populated by set_closed_date BR; audit timestamps updated by
    // the platform's standard sys_* pipeline). After the refresh,
    // the form will display the case in Closed status with the
    // closed_date stamped to the current time.
    action.setRedirectURL(current);
})();]]></script>
        <show_insert>false</show_insert>
        <show_multiple_update>false</show_multiple_update>
        <show_query>false</show_query>
        <show_update>true</show_update>
        <sys_class_name>sys_ui_action</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_domain>global</sys_domain>
        <sys_domain_path>/</sys_domain_path>
        <sys_id>c2988c82e1da1b3e1029196a6e0d0f9f</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>x_casemgmt_case_close</sys_name>
        <sys_overrides/>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_casemgmt">x_casemgmt</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_casemgmt</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_ui_action_x_casemgmt_case_close</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <table>x_casemgmt_case</table>
        <ui11_compatible>true</ui11_compatible>
        <ui16_compatible>true</ui16_compatible>
    </sys_ui_action>
</record_update>

