<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the SINGLE `sp_page` row that
    defines the CASE STATUS LOOKUP page of the unauthenticated Experience Portal
    inside the scoped application `x_casemgmt`. This page is the SECOND of the
    two Service Portal pages required by AAP Section 0.4.4 ("two unauthenticated
    pages: case submission and case status lookup").

    PURPOSE (AAP Section 0.1.1 / Section 0.4.4 / Section 0.7.4 / Validation
    Gate 5 "Portal - lookup"):

      AAP Section 0.4.4 verbatim ("UI Design - External Experience Portal UI"):
        "Page 2 - Case Status Lookup: a single input (case number) and a result
         panel that shows status, subject, opened_date when found, or the literal
         text 'No case found with that number.' when not found. No internal
         fields (assigned_group, assigned_agent, description, closed_date,
         requester_*) are exposed."

      AAP Section 0.5.1 (in-scope artifact verbatim):
        "servicenow-case-management-poc/portal/sp_page_x_casemgmt_case_status.xml -
         case status lookup page (unauthenticated)".

      AAP Section 0.7.4 (verbatim): the literal text
        'No case found with that number.'
      MUST appear when the lookup case number does not match. That message is
      rendered by the embedded lookup widget, NOT by this page record - but
      THIS page is the entry-point that hosts the lookup widget which renders
      the verbatim no-match message.

      Validation Gate 5 ("Portal - lookup") verbatim from AAP Section 0.7.3:
        "Status lookup returns correct data for valid case number - Correct
         status/subject/opened_date returned; 'No case found with that number.'
         for invalid number."
      Without this page record, anonymous users would have no entry-point to
      reach the lookup widget, so this file is a foundational artifact for
      Gate 5.

    THE PAGE IS THE SHELL, THE WIDGET IS THE CONTENT:
      This file authors ONLY page-level metadata: URL slug, title, anonymous-
      access flags, behavioral toggles (omit_watcher, hide_for_kb), and the
      page layout JSON that embeds ONE widget (the case lookup widget). All
      interactive UI elements (case-number input, lookup button, REST call,
      result-panel rendering, verbatim no-case-found message) live in the
      embedded widget record at
      ../widgets/sp_widget_x_casemgmt_case_lookup_widget.xml. The lookup widget
      issues a GET to the scripted REST endpoint at
      ../rest/sys_ws_definition_x_casemgmt_case_status_lookup.xml which executes
      a Script Include that performs a GlideRecord query on the case table by
      `number` and returns ONLY the whitelisted three fields (status, subject,
      opened_date) - or a 404 with the verbatim no-match message.

      The user journey:
        anonymous user navigates to
          [instance URL]/x_casemgmt_case_portal?id=x_casemgmt_case_status
          -> THIS page record renders
          -> page's <page_internal> JSON embeds the lookup widget
          -> lookup widget renders 1-input form (case number) + result panel
          -> user enters case number + clicks Lookup
          -> widget GETs /api/x_casemgmt/case_status_lookup?number=<value>
          -> Script Include performs GlideRecord query on x_casemgmt_case
             with addQuery('number', value)
          -> on match: REST returns {status, subject, opened_date} (only those
             three fields - whitelist enforced server-side)
          -> on no-match: REST returns 404 with body
             {"error": "No case found with that number."}
          -> lookup widget displays the result panel OR the verbatim
             "No case found with that number." text from the 404 body.

    UNAUTHENTICATED ANONYMOUS-ACCESS DESIGN (AAP Section 0.4.4 verbatim:
    "two unauthenticated pages"):
      Three configuration mechanisms work together to make this page renderable
      by anonymous, unauthenticated callers:

        1. <public>true</public> - explicit signal to the platform's
           authorization layer that THIS PAGE is exempt from the standard
           authentication challenge.

        2. <internal>false</internal> - the page is publicly accessible and
           NOT restricted to "internal" (employee) users. ServiceNow's
           Service Portal pages can be either internal-only (employees only)
           or public (anyone, including anonymous). Setting internal=false
           is the second leg of the public-access tripod.

        3. <roles/> - empty. No roles are required to view the page. The
           Service Portal page-level role-based gating is bypassed by the
           empty roles list.

      All three mechanisms are necessary; omitting any one breaks the
      anonymous-access guarantee:
        - Without <public>true</public>, the platform's auth layer redirects
          anonymous users to the portal's login_page (which itself points
          BACK at the SUBMISSION page x_casemgmt_case_submit, NOT this status
          page - so anonymous users would never see this page).
        - Without <internal>false</internal>, internal employees would see
          the page but anonymous external requesters would not.
        - Without an empty <roles/>, even authenticated users would need
          to hold a specific role, defeating the "anyone can look up by case
          number" intent.

      The PARENT portal record (../sp_portal_x_casemgmt_case_portal.xml) ALSO
      sets <public>true</public>. The two records work together: the portal
      record makes the URL space anonymous-accessible at the portal layer,
      and THIS page makes the page itself anonymous-accessible at the page
      layer. Both layers must be public for end-to-end anonymous access to
      this page.

      Note: unlike the sibling submission page (which IS the portal's
      <homepage>/<login_page>), THIS status page is reachable ONLY via
      direct URL `?id=x_casemgmt_case_status`. The portal does NOT redirect
      anonymous users here automatically; users must explicitly know they
      want to look up an existing case and navigate to the URL with the
      query parameter (typically by clicking a "Look up an existing case"
      link from the submission page, or by using a bookmark provided in
      the post-submission confirmation message).

    URL ROUTING / PAGE id (CONSISTENT WITH THE SIBLING SUBMIT PAGE):
      The <id> field is the URL slug used in the ?id= query parameter when
      callers navigate to the portal. The full URL becomes:
        [instance URL]/x_casemgmt_case_portal?id=x_casemgmt_case_status

      CONVENTION CONSISTENCY (Code Review CP2 MEDIUM finding remediation,
      Resolution B): Both Service Portal pages in this scoped application
      use the SCOPE-PREFIXED convention for their <id> fields:
        - sp_page_x_casemgmt_case_submit.xml: <id>x_casemgmt_case_submit</id>
        - sp_page_x_casemgmt_case_status.xml: <id>x_casemgmt_case_status</id>
        (THIS file)

      The PREFIXED convention is applied uniformly to BOTH pages because:
        (1) ServiceNow's sp_page table is in the GLOBAL scope, not in the
            scoped application's scope. Scope prefixes therefore protect
            against name collisions with other scoped apps that may also
            land on the same PDI in the future (e.g., another scoped app
            attempting to author its own `case_status` page would collide
            with a non-prefixed slug here).
        (2) The portal record's <homepage>/<login_page>/<homepage_dv>/
            <login_page_dv> fields require the submit page id to be
            scope-prefixed (`x_casemgmt_case_submit`); applying the same
            convention to the status page produces an internally
            consistent code base.
        (3) ServiceNow's Service Portal URL convention permits any string
            as the <id> field value. The slug appearing in the `?id=` URL
            parameter is purely a URL-routing key matched against the
            <id> field; both BARE and PREFIXED slugs render identically
            at runtime - the only operational difference is collision
            safety in the global sp_page namespace.

      The <sys_update_name> is also scope-prefixed
      (<sys_update_name>sp_page_x_casemgmt_case_status</sys_update_name>),
      providing the global cross-record key that ServiceNow's Update Set
      engine uses to identify this record across all sp_page records on
      the PDI. The two fields work together:
        - <id> = URL slug AND collision-safe global identifier
        - <sys_update_name> = Update Set engine's record-identity key

      This convention matches the canonical Service Portal best practice
      of scope-prefixing all sp_page <id> values authored by a scoped
      application.

    PAGE LAYOUT (page_internal JSON):
      ServiceNow's Service Portal page layout is JSON stored in the
      <page_internal> field. The JSON describes a Bootstrap-style structure
      of containers, rows, columns (size 1-12), and widget instances. For
      this simple lookup page, a SINGLE container with ONE row and ONE
      full-width column embedding ONE widget (the lookup widget) is
      sufficient.

      The widget is referenced BY ITS `id` FIELD VALUE
      (x_casemgmt_case_lookup_widget) in the JSON's widget_id /
      widgetReference fields - NOT by sys_id. This honors the no-hardcoded-
      sys_id rule (AAP Section 0.7.2). The widget id resolves at render time
      against the sp_widget record at
      ../widgets/sp_widget_x_casemgmt_case_lookup_widget.xml.

      The widget instance options object is empty ({}) because the lookup
      widget does not accept configuration parameters from the page; all
      interactive state (case-number input value, REST response handling,
      result-panel display logic, verbatim no-case-found message) lives
      within the widget itself. The widget does NOT transitively embed
      another widget (unlike the submission widget, which embeds the
      confirmation widget on success - the lookup widget renders results
      INLINE in its own template via ng-if/ng-show conditions on
      response.found vs response.error states).

      The container/row/column ids (container_main, row_lookup, col_lookup,
      instance_lookup_widget) are local to this page record and are used by
      Service Portal for DOM ids at render time. They do NOT need scope
      prefixes because they are not cross-referenced by any other record -
      they exist purely within this page's layout JSON.

      JSON is wrapped in CDATA to allow angle brackets and ampersands etc.
      without XML-escaping. The CDATA section's ABSOLUTE constraint is that
      the CDATA-end-marker sequence (right-bracket-right-bracket-greater-
      than) must NOT appear inside the JSON; verified - no such sequence
      is present.

    DEFAULT THEME / NO CUSTOM CSS (AAP Section 0.4.4 verbatim: "Visual
    treatment: ServiceNow Experience Portal default theme. No custom CSS,
    no custom branding."):
      <page_specific_css/> is intentionally an empty self-closing element.
      No custom CSS rules are authored or referenced by this page record.
      The platform's default Service Portal theme (inherited from the parent
      portal record, which itself uses the platform default theme with empty
      <theme/> and <theme_dv/>) is used at render time. This guarantees
      PDI-release portability and matches the AAP minimal-change clause
      (AAP Section 0.7.2).

    OUT-OF-SCOPE FIELDS (deliberately empty):
      <category/> - empty. The page is NOT added to a navigation menu,
        breadcrumb, or category dropdown. Per AAP Section 0.4.4, the page
        is reachable only via direct URL (?id=x_casemgmt_case_status). No
        navigation chrome integration.
      <dynamic_title_structure/> - empty. The static <title>Case Status Lookup</title>
        is sufficient; no dynamic title fragments (e.g., per-case-number
        substituted titles like "Status of CASE0000123") are needed for a
        generic anonymous lookup page.
      <hide_for_kb>true</hide_for_kb> - the page is NOT exposed to the
        Knowledge Base integration. Knowledge-base integration is OUT OF
        SCOPE per AAP Section 0.3.2.
      <omit_watcher>true</omit_watcher> - no automatic watchers are added
        when anonymous users land on this page. Anonymous users have no
        sys_user record to add as a watcher anyway, but setting this
        explicitly avoids unexpected behavior on edge cases.

    NO PORTAL FIELD ON THE PAGE RECORD:
      Service Portal pages do NOT have a direct <portal> field. Pages are
      associated with portals via URL routing convention: when a user
      navigates to `[instance URL]/<portal_url_suffix>?id=<page_id>`, the
      portal looks up the sp_page record by <id> and renders it within the
      portal's chrome (theme, header, footer). The portal record's
      <homepage>/<homepage_dv> fields reference the homepage page ONLY.
      Other pages (like THIS status lookup page) are reachable via direct
      URL with the appropriate ?id= query parameter; the portal does not
      enumerate them. This is the canonical ServiceNow convention and is
      documented in the agent prompt's Key Insight #11.

    SCOPE BINDING (AAP Sections 0.5.2 and 0.7.2):
      <sys_scope> and <sys_package> reference the scoped application by its
      actual scope NAME (`x_casemgmt`), not by sys_id. The actual scope
      record's <name> is `x_casemgmt` per ../../app/sys_scope/x_casemgmt.xml,
      and <scope>x_casemgmt</scope> per ../../app/sys_app/x_casemgmt_case_management.xml.
      ALL sibling XMLs in this scoped application (the portal, tables,
      dictionary entries, ACLs, roles, REST definitions, business rules,
      sibling pages, etc.) reference the scope by that same name (`x_casemgmt`).
      Update Set re-import resolves cross-references by matching the
      <sys_scope> text-node value against the scope record's <name>/<source>
      fields, so this MUST match the actual sibling-file convention to avoid
      preview errors. This is the same convention applied in
      ./sp_page_x_casemgmt_case_submit.xml,
      ../sp_portal_x_casemgmt_case_portal.xml,
      ../../tables/x_casemgmt_case.xml,
      ../../roles/sys_user_role_x_casemgmt_case_manager.xml,
      and every other sibling record.

      The display_value="Case Management" attribute is descriptive metadata
      that ServiceNow uses for human-readable display on the Update Set
      preview page; the actual reference resolution uses the text-node value.
      The source="x_casemgmt" attribute on <sys_package> carries the scope
      identifier for the platform's package-scope linkage.

    CROSS-REFERENCES BY NAME / NO HARDCODED SYS_IDS (AAP Section 0.7.2):
      Every cross-reference is a name lookup against a stable identifier:
        - <sys_scope> resolves against the scope record's <name>
          (`x_casemgmt`).
        - <sys_package> resolves against the sys_app record's <scope>
          (`x_casemgmt`).
        - The widget reference inside <page_internal> JSON
          (x_casemgmt_case_lookup_widget) resolves against the sp_widget
          record's <id> field at
          ../widgets/sp_widget_x_casemgmt_case_lookup_widget.xml.

      The ONLY sys_id literal in this file is <sys_id> itself (THIS record's
      own primary key). It is the deterministic 32-char lowercase hex MD5
      of `sp_page_x_casemgmt_case_status`:
        printf '%s' 'sp_page_x_casemgmt_case_status' | md5sum | cut -c1-32
        -> 8881e418f5d24b17b641505a4f1dc814
      Per AAP Section 0.7.2, the no-hardcoded-sys_id rule applies to
      references TO OTHER records, not to a record's own identity primary
      key. The deterministic MD5-derivation matches the convention used by
      every sibling record in this scoped app (e.g., the submit page's
      sys_id is MD5("sp_page_x_casemgmt_case_submit"), the portal record's
      sys_id is MD5("sp_portal_x_casemgmt_case_portal"), etc.). This makes
      the XML byte-stable: re-running the agent that authored this file
      produces the identical 32-char hex string each time.

    NO PII, NO EMAIL (AAP Sections 0.7.2, 0.3.2):
      The description below contains ZERO PII (no real names, no real email
      addresses, no real organization names). Email notifications are
      explicitly disabled on the PDI per AAP Section 0.7.2 Email-disabled
      constraint - no notification triggers are configured by this page
      record.

    WHITELIST ENFORCEMENT IS DELEGATED (NOT in this file):
      Per AAP Section 0.4.4 and Section 0.7.4, the case status lookup flow
      whitelists exactly three response fields: status, subject, opened_date.
      Internal fields (assigned_group, assigned_agent, description,
      closed_date, requester_name, requester_email, audit fields) are
      explicitly NOT exposed. THIS page record does NOT enforce that
      whitelist. The enforcement happens in two places:
        - Server-side: the Script Include behind the scripted REST
          case_status_lookup endpoint constructs a response object that
          contains ONLY status/subject/opened_date - never reads the other
          fields and never includes them in the response body.
        - Client-side: the lookup widget's HTML template only renders three
          result fields, even if the response contained extra keys.
      THIS page is purely the URL entry-point and layout container; field
      validation, response-shape definitions, and output restrictions are
      widget-level and Script-Include-level concerns.

    THE VERBATIM "No case found with that number." TEXT IS NOT IN THIS FILE:
      Per AAP Section 0.7.4 (verbatim), the no-match message MUST be the
      literal string "No case found with that number." (no paraphrase). That
      text is rendered by ../widgets/sp_widget_x_casemgmt_case_lookup_widget.xml,
      which interprets the 404 response body from the scripted REST endpoint
      and displays the verbatim message in its result panel. THIS page
      record only embeds the lookup widget; the widget is responsible for
      the verbatim message. No text content is hard-coded in this page
      record; even the <title> "Case Status Lookup" is a separate concern
      (browser-tab title and portal chrome) from the no-match message.

    `casemgmt` SCOPE IDENTIFIER (AAP Section 0.7.1 implicit / Section 0.7.2):
      All `x_casemgmt_*` references use the concrete scope identifier `casemgmt` per AAP
      Section 0.7.2 ("Scoped-namespace-only constraint"). ServiceNow Update Set
      imports use a standard XML parser, so the scope id is concrete in the XML
      before export. The same identifier is used consistently across every
      sibling XML in this scoped application.

    XML CONVENTIONS HONORED (matching sibling files in this app):
      - Wrapper element: <record_update table="sp_page"> per the agent
        prompt's Phase 1 specification, matching the sibling pattern used
        by ./sp_page_x_casemgmt_case_submit.xml,
        ../sp_portal_x_casemgmt_case_portal.xml,
        ../../tables/x_casemgmt_case.xml, and other primary-record XMLs.
      - Indentation: 4 spaces for record fields (matching sibling-file
        convention).
      - Element ordering: alphabetical within the record (matching
        sibling-file convention used by the submit page and portal record).
      - sys_scope text-node value: `x_casemgmt` (NOT
        `x_casemgmt_case_management`). The actual scope record's <name> is
        `x_casemgmt` per ../../app/sys_scope/x_casemgmt.xml, matching every
        sibling XML in this scoped app.
      - sys_package text-node value: `x_casemgmt` with `source="x_casemgmt"`
        attribute, matching the sys_app record's <scope>x_casemgmt</scope>
        per ../../app/sys_app/x_casemgmt_case_management.xml.
      - Deterministic 32-char lowercase hex sys_id: computed as
        MD5("sp_page_x_casemgmt_case_status") = 8881e418f5d24b17b641505a4f1dc814.
        Re-generation of this XML is byte-identical (no random UUIDs).
      - Audit fields: <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by> and
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on> for stable
        repeatable timestamps (the same date is used by EVERY sibling
        record in this scoped app for repeatable XML re-generation).
      - No smart quotes, no leading/trailing whitespace, no BOM. Strict
        XML conformance for ServiceNow Update Set re-import preview
        (AAP Section 0.7.3 validation gate 7).

    SOURCE-SIDE SEMANTIC REFERENCE (read-only context, NOT byte-for-byte
    ported per AAP Section 0.5.1):

      acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-case-file-plugin/src/main/java/com/
      armedia/acm/plugins/casefile/service/GetCaseByNumberService.java
        line 36-39 - public interface GetCaseByNumberService { CaseFile
                     getCaseByNumber(String caseNumber); }
      acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-case-file-plugin/src/main/java/com/
      armedia/acm/plugins/casefile/service/GetCaseByNumberServiceImpl.java
        line 47-50 - public CaseFile getCaseByNumber(String caseNumber) {
                       return getCaseFileDao().findByCaseNumber(caseNumber);
                     }
      acm-services/acm-service-portal-gateway/src/main/java/com/armedia/acm/
      portalgateway/service/DefaultPluggablePortalRequestService.java
        line 86-92 - public PortalResponse getRequestStatus(String portalId,
                       String portalUserId, String requestType,
                       String requestId) throws PortalRequestServiceException
                     { ... return getServiceProvider(requestType).
                       getRequestStatus(portalId, portalUserId, requestId); }

      ArkCase implements anonymous case-by-number lookup through a Spring
      service (`GetCaseByNumberService.getCaseByNumber(String caseNumber)`)
      that delegates to a JPA DAO method (`findByCaseNumber`). The portal
      gateway (`PortalRequestService.getRequestStatus(...)`) wraps that
      lookup for unauthenticated callers and returns a `PortalResponse`. The
      ServiceNow target collapses both surfaces into a single anonymous
      Service Portal page (THIS file) that embeds a widget that GETs from a
      scripted REST endpoint - no Spring beans, no JPA DAO, no
      `PortalRequestService`. The Java code's `getCaseByNumber()` and
      `getRequestStatus()` map semantically to the
      page->widget->REST->Script-Include->GlideRecord chain triggered by
      THIS page's lookup widget, with the additional response-shape
      whitelisting (status, subject, opened_date only) enforced server-side
      by the Script Include.

    CROSS-REFERENCES (AAP Section 0.5.2 dependency ordering):
      THIS RECORD MUST LOAD AFTER:
        - ../../app/sys_scope/x_casemgmt.xml (scope record; <sys_scope>
          cross-reference resolves against this record's <name>)
        - ../../app/sys_app/x_casemgmt_case_management.xml (scoped
          application record; <sys_package> cross-reference resolves
          against this record's <scope>)

      THIS RECORD SHOULD LOAD AFTER (but ServiceNow's two-pass import
      tolerates any order within the same Update Set, since references
      resolve by name):
        - ../widgets/sp_widget_x_casemgmt_case_lookup_widget.xml (the widget
          embedded in this page's <page_internal> layout JSON; cross-
          reference resolves against this record's <id> field at render
          time, but the platform tolerates any ordering within an Update
          Set because the JSON-embedded widget reference is resolved
          lazily during page render, not during XML import)

      THIS RECORD IS REFERENCED BY:
        - (none) - this page is a leaf in the dependency tree; nothing
          else references it directly. The portal record references the
          submission page (as homepage/login_page), but does NOT reference
          this status page directly. This page is reachable only via
          direct URL `?id=x_casemgmt_case_status`.

    VALIDATION-GATE MAPPING (AAP Section 0.7.3 - the seven validation
    gates):
      This page record is the FOUNDATIONAL artifact for one of the seven
      validation gates:

        Gate 5 ("Portal - lookup"): "Status lookup returns correct data for
          valid case number - Correct status/subject/opened_date returned;
          'No case found with that number.' for invalid number." The page's
          <public>true</public> flag and <internal>false</internal> setting
          plus the empty <roles/> together permit anonymous callers to
          render the page. The <page_internal> layout JSON embeds the
          lookup widget which renders the form, calls the REST endpoint,
          and triggers the case status query. Without this page record,
          anonymous users would have no entry-point to the case status
          lookup flow.

      Gates 1 (data model), 2 (workflow), 3 (ACLs), 4 (portal-submission is
      handled by ./sp_page_x_casemgmt_case_submit.xml), 6 (dashboards), and
      7 (Update Set integrity) are not directly affected by this file -
      though Gate 7 implicitly requires THIS record's XML to be well-formed
      and to resolve all cross-references on Update Set preview.
-->
<record_update table="sp_page">
    <sp_page action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <category/>
        <description>Unauthenticated Service Portal page for case status lookup. Embeds the case lookup widget (sp_widget_x_casemgmt_case_lookup_widget) which renders a single case-number input plus result panel showing ONLY status, subject, opened_date on match, or the verbatim text 'No case found with that number.' on no-match. Reachable via direct URL [instance URL]/x_casemgmt_case_portal?id=x_casemgmt_case_status. Member of the x_casemgmt_case_portal Experience Portal but NOT its homepage (the submission page is the homepage). Replaces ArkCase's GetCaseByNumberService and PortalRequestService.getRequestStatus anonymous-status-lookup pattern. Per AAP Sections 0.4.4 and 0.7.4 (verbatim no-case-found message) and Validation Gate 5 (Portal - lookup).</description>
        <draft>false</draft>
        <dynamic_title_structure/>
        <hide_for_kb>true</hide_for_kb>
        <id>x_casemgmt_case_status</id>
        <internal>false</internal>
        <omit_watcher>true</omit_watcher>
        <page_internal><![CDATA[
{
    "containers": [
        {
            "id": "container_main",
            "containerClass": "container",
            "rows": [
                {
                    "id": "row_lookup",
                    "columns": [
                        {
                            "id": "col_lookup",
                            "size": 12,
                            "instances": [
                                {
                                    "id": "instance_lookup_widget",
                                    "widget_id": "x_casemgmt_case_lookup_widget",
                                    "widgetReference": "x_casemgmt_case_lookup_widget",
                                    "title": "Case Status Lookup",
                                    "options": {}
                                }
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
]]></page_internal>
        <page_specific_css/>
        <public>true</public>
        <roles/>
        <sys_class_name>sp_page</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>8881e418f5d24b17b641505a4f1dc814</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>Case Status Lookup</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_casemgmt">x_casemgmt</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_casemgmt</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sp_page_x_casemgmt_case_status</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <title>Case Status Lookup</title>
    </sp_page>
</record_update>
