<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the SINGLE `sp_page` row that
    defines the CASE SUBMISSION page of the unauthenticated Experience Portal
    inside the scoped application `x_[scope]`. This page is the FIRST of the
    two Service Portal pages required by AAP Section 0.4.4 ("two unauthenticated
    pages: case submission and case status lookup").

    PURPOSE (AAP Section 0.1.1 / Section 0.4.4 / Section 0.7.4 / Validation
    Gate 4 "Portal - submission"):

      AAP Section 0.4.4 verbatim ("UI Design - External Experience Portal UI"):
        "Page 1 - Case Submission: a simple form with five inputs (subject,
         type, description, requester_name, requester_email). On submit, calls
         the scripted REST endpoint, displays a confirmation panel showing the
         returned case number and a friendly 'Your case has been submitted'
         message."

      AAP Section 0.5.1 (in-scope artifact verbatim):
        "servicenow-case-management-poc/portal/sp_page_x_[scope]_case_submit.xml -
         case submission page (unauthenticated)".

      AAP Section 0.7.4 (verbatim): the friendly success message
        'Your case has been submitted'
      MUST be displayed after successful submission. That message is rendered
      by the embedded confirmation widget (transitively via the submission
      widget), NOT by this page record - but THIS page is the entry-point that
      hosts the submission widget which embeds the confirmation widget.

      Validation Gate 4 ("Portal - submission") verbatim from AAP Section 0.7.3:
        "Case created from unauthenticated portal submission - Case appears in
         internal list with Draft status and correct case number."
      Without this page record, the submission widget cannot be reached by
      anonymous users, so this file is a foundational artifact for Gate 4.

    THE PAGE IS THE SHELL, THE WIDGET IS THE CONTENT:
      This file authors ONLY page-level metadata: URL slug, title, anonymous-
      access flags, behavioral toggles (omit_watcher, hide_for_kb), and the
      page layout JSON that embeds ONE widget (the case submission widget).
      All interactive UI elements (form inputs, validation, REST call, success
      handling) live in the embedded widget record at
      ../widgets/sp_widget_x_[scope]_case_submission_widget.xml. The submission
      widget then transitively embeds the confirmation widget at
      ../widgets/sp_widget_x_[scope]_case_confirmation_widget.xml after a
      successful POST to the scripted REST submit endpoint at
      ../rest/sys_ws_definition_x_[scope]_case_submit.xml.

      The user journey:
        anonymous user navigates to [instance URL]/x_[scope]_case_portal
          -> portal record's homepage_dv redirects to ?id=x_[scope]_case_submit
          -> THIS page record renders
          -> page's <page_internal> JSON embeds the submission widget
          -> submission widget renders 5-field form
          -> user fills + clicks Submit
          -> widget POSTs to /api/x_[scope]/case_submit
          -> Script Include creates GlideRecord on x_[scope]_case (status=Draft)
          -> REST returns {number}
          -> submission widget swaps in the embedded confirmation widget
          -> confirmation widget displays case number + "Your case has been
             submitted" verbatim text.

    UNAUTHENTICATED ANONYMOUS-ACCESS DESIGN (AAP Section 0.4.4 verbatim:
    "two unauthenticated pages"):
      Three configuration mechanisms work together to make this page renderable
      by anonymous, unauthenticated callers:

        1. <public>true</public> - explicit signal to the platform's
           authorization layer that THIS PAGE is exempt from the standard
           authentication challenge.

        2. <internal>false</internal> - the page is publicly accessible and
           NOT restricted to "internal" (employee) users. ServiceNow's
           Service Portal pages can be either internal-only (employees only)
           or public (anyone, including anonymous). Setting internal=false
           is the second leg of the public-access tripod.

        3. <roles/> - empty. No roles are required to view the page. The
           Service Portal page-level role-based gating is bypassed by
           the empty roles list.

      All three mechanisms are necessary; omitting any one breaks the
      anonymous-access guarantee:
        - Without <public>true</public>, the platform's auth layer redirects
          anonymous users to the portal's login_page (which itself points
          BACK at this page, but the redirect adds the wrong query string
          and breaks the URL contract).
        - Without <internal>false</internal>, internal employees would
          see the page but anonymous external requesters would not.
        - Without an empty <roles/>, even authenticated users would need
          to hold a specific role, defeating the "anyone can submit"
          intent.

      The PARENT portal record (../sp_portal_x_[scope]_case_portal.xml) ALSO
      sets <public>true</public> and a <login_page> redirect target that
      points to THIS page's id. The two records work together: the portal
      record makes the URL space anonymous-accessible at the portal layer,
      and THIS page makes the page itself anonymous-accessible at the page
      layer. Both layers must be public for end-to-end anonymous access.

    URL ROUTING / PAGE id (CRITICAL CROSS-REFERENCE TO PORTAL RECORD):
      The <id> field is the URL slug used in the ?id= query parameter when
      callers navigate to the portal. The full URL becomes:
        [instance URL]/x_[scope]_case_portal?id=x_[scope]_case_submit

      The portal record at ../sp_portal_x_[scope]_case_portal.xml references
      THIS page's id in BOTH its <homepage> and its <login_page> fields:
        <homepage display_value="Case Submission">x_[scope]_case_submit</homepage>
        <homepage_dv display_value="Case Submission">x_[scope]_case_submit</homepage_dv>
        <login_page display_value="Case Submission">x_[scope]_case_submit</login_page>
        <login_page_dv display_value="Case Submission">x_[scope]_case_submit</login_page_dv>

      For those four cross-references to resolve correctly during Update Set
      preview, THIS page's <id> field MUST be exactly:
        x_[scope]_case_submit

      The scope-prefixed id ensures global uniqueness across all sp_page
      records on the PDI (which is critical because sp_page.id is a primary-
      key-like field within the portal). It also matches the established
      naming convention used by every sibling record in this scoped app
      (e.g., x_[scope]_case for the table, x_[scope]_case_manager for the
      role, x_[scope]_case_portal for the portal). The literal [scope]
      placeholder is preserved; the PDI auto-resolves it to the actual
      scope id (e.g., x_<actual_scope>_case_submit) at App Engine Studio
      creation time when the Update Set is imported.

    PAGE LAYOUT (page_internal JSON):
      ServiceNow's Service Portal page layout is JSON stored in the
      <page_internal> field. The JSON describes a Bootstrap-style structure
      of containers, rows, columns (size 1-12), and widget instances. For
      this simple submission page, a SINGLE container with ONE row and ONE
      full-width column embedding ONE widget (the submission widget) is
      sufficient.

      The widget is referenced BY ITS `id` FIELD VALUE
      (x_[scope]_case_submission_widget) in the JSON's widget_id /
      widgetReference fields - NOT by sys_id. This honors the no-hardcoded-
      sys_id rule (AAP Section 0.7.2). The widget id resolves at render
      time against the sp_widget record at
      ../widgets/sp_widget_x_[scope]_case_submission_widget.xml.

      The widget instance options object is empty ({}) because the
      submission widget does not accept configuration parameters from the
      page; all interactive state lives within the widget itself. The
      widget transitively embeds the confirmation widget via $sp.getWidget()
      (server-side prep) and the <sp-widget> directive (template-side
      render) based on its own internal form-submitted state - the
      embedding decision is widget-level, not page-level.

      The container/row/column ids (container_main, row_submit, col_submit,
      instance_submission_widget) are local to this page record and are
      used by Service Portal for DOM ids at render time. They do NOT need
      scope prefixes because they are not cross-referenced by any other
      record - they exist purely within this page's layout JSON.

      JSON is wrapped in CDATA to allow `<`, `>`, `&` etc. without XML-
      escaping. The CDATA section's ABSOLUTE constraint is that the literal
      string `]]>` must NOT appear inside the JSON; verified - no such
      sequence is present.

    DEFAULT THEME / NO CUSTOM CSS (AAP Section 0.4.4 verbatim: "Visual
    treatment: ServiceNow Experience Portal default theme. No custom CSS,
    no custom branding."):
      <page_specific_css/> is intentionally an empty self-closing element.
      No custom CSS rules are authored or referenced by this page record.
      The platform's default Service Portal theme (inherited from the
      parent portal record, which itself uses the platform default theme
      with empty <theme/> and <theme_dv/>) is used at render time. This
      guarantees PDI-release portability and matches the AAP minimal-
      change clause (AAP Section 0.7.2).

    OUT-OF-SCOPE FIELDS (deliberately empty):
      <category/> - empty. The page is NOT added to a navigation menu,
        breadcrumb, or category dropdown. Per AAP Section 0.4.4, the page
        is reachable only via direct URL (root portal URL or
        ?id=x_[scope]_case_submit). No navigation chrome integration.
      <dynamic_title_structure/> - empty. The static <title>Submit a Case</title>
        is sufficient; no dynamic title fragments (e.g., per-requester
        substituted titles) are needed for a generic anonymous submission
        page.
      <hide_for_kb>true</hide_for_kb> - the page is NOT exposed to the
        Knowledge Base integration. Knowledge-base integration is OUT OF
        SCOPE per AAP Section 0.3.2.
      <omit_watcher>true</omit_watcher> - no automatic watchers are added
        when anonymous users land on this page. Anonymous users have no
        sys_user record to add as a watcher anyway, but setting this
        explicitly avoids unexpected behavior on edge cases.

    SCOPE BINDING (AAP Sections 0.5.2 and 0.7.2):
      <sys_scope> and <sys_package> reference the scoped application by
      its actual scope NAME (`x_[scope]`), not by sys_id. The actual scope
      record's <name> is `x_[scope]` per ../../app/sys_scope/x_[scope].xml,
      and <scope>x_[scope]</scope> per ../../app/sys_app/x_[scope]_case_management.xml.
      ALL sibling XMLs in this scoped application (the portal, tables,
      dictionary entries, ACLs, roles, REST definitions, business rules,
      etc.) reference the scope by that same name (`x_[scope]`). Update
      Set re-import resolves cross-references by matching the <sys_scope>
      text-node value against the scope record's <name>/<source> fields,
      so this MUST match the actual sibling-file convention to avoid
      preview errors. This is the same convention applied in
      ../sp_portal_x_[scope]_case_portal.xml,
      ../../tables/x_[scope]_case.xml,
      ../../roles/sys_user_role_x_[scope]_case_manager.xml,
      and every other sibling record.

      The display_value="Case Management" attribute is descriptive metadata
      that ServiceNow uses for human-readable display on the Update Set
      preview page; the actual reference resolution uses the text-node
      value. The source="x_[scope]" attribute on <sys_package> carries
      the scope identifier for the platform's package-scope linkage.

    CROSS-REFERENCES BY NAME / NO HARDCODED SYS_IDS (AAP Section 0.7.2):
      Every cross-reference is a name lookup against a stable identifier:
        - <sys_scope> resolves against the scope record's <name>
          (`x_[scope]`).
        - <sys_package> resolves against the sys_app record's <scope>
          (`x_[scope]`).
        - The widget reference inside <page_internal> JSON
          (x_[scope]_case_submission_widget) resolves against the
          sp_widget record's <id> field at
          ../widgets/sp_widget_x_[scope]_case_submission_widget.xml.

      The ONLY sys_id literal in this file is <sys_id> itself (THIS
      record's own primary key). It is the deterministic 32-char lowercase
      hex MD5 of `sp_page_x_[scope]_case_submit`:
        printf '%s' 'sp_page_x_[scope]_case_submit' | md5sum | cut -c1-32
        -> 6a1f3c2ffd653613304512a734aab83b
      Per AAP Section 0.7.2, the no-hardcoded-sys_id rule applies to
      references TO OTHER records, not to a record's own identity primary
      key.

    NO PII, NO EMAIL (AAP Sections 0.7.2, 0.3.2):
      The description below contains ZERO PII (no real names, no real
      email addresses, no real organization names). Email notifications
      are explicitly disabled on the PDI per AAP Section 0.7.2 Email-
      disabled constraint - no notification triggers are configured by
      this page record.

    WHITELIST ENFORCEMENT IS DELEGATED (NOT in this file):
      Per AAP Section 0.4.4 and Section 0.7.4, the case submission flow
      whitelists exactly five fields: subject, type, description,
      requester_name, requester_email. THIS page record does NOT enforce
      that whitelist. The enforcement happens in two places:
        - Client-side: the submission widget's HTML template only renders
          5 inputs and its controller only POSTs 5 keys.
        - Server-side: the Script Include behind the scripted REST submit
          endpoint silently drops any non-whitelisted fields before
          calling GlideRecord.insert() on x_[scope]_case.
      THIS page is purely the URL entry-point and layout container; field
      validation, payload-shape definitions, and input restrictions are
      widget-level and Script-Include-level concerns.

    THE VERBATIM "Your case has been submitted" TEXT IS NOT IN THIS FILE:
      Per AAP Section 0.7.4 (verbatim), the success message MUST be the
      literal string "Your case has been submitted" (no paraphrase). That
      text is rendered by ../widgets/sp_widget_x_[scope]_case_confirmation_widget.xml,
      which is transitively embedded by the submission widget after a
      successful POST. THIS page record only embeds the submission widget
      directly; the confirmation widget is reached via a chain:
        page -> submission widget -> (on submit success) -> confirmation widget.
      No text content is hard-coded in this page record; even the <title>
      "Submit a Case" is a separate concern (browser-tab title and portal
      chrome) from the success message.

    `[scope]` PLACEHOLDER PRESERVATION (AAP Section 0.7.1 implicit /
    Section 0.7.2):
      All `x_[scope]_*` references preserve the literal `[scope]`
      placeholder in square brackets. The PDI auto-resolves to the actual
      scope id (e.g., `x_<actual_scope>_case_submit`) at App Engine Studio
      creation time when the Update Set is imported. This placeholder
      convention is observed consistently across every sibling XML in this
      scoped application.

    XML CONVENTIONS HONORED (matching sibling files in this app):
      - Wrapper element: <record_update table="sp_page"> per the agent
        prompt's Phase 1 specification, matching the sibling pattern used
        by ../sp_portal_x_[scope]_case_portal.xml,
        ../../tables/x_[scope]_case.xml, and other primary-record XMLs.
      - Indentation: 4 spaces for record fields (matching sibling-file
        convention).
      - Element ordering: alphabetical within the record (matching
        sibling-file convention used by the portal record).
      - sys_scope text-node value: `x_[scope]` (NOT
        `x_[scope]_case_management`). The actual scope record's <name>
        is `x_[scope]` per ../../app/sys_scope/x_[scope].xml, matching
        every sibling XML in this scoped app.
      - sys_package text-node value: `x_[scope]` with `source="x_[scope]"`
        attribute, matching the sys_app record's <scope>x_[scope]</scope>
        per ../../app/sys_app/x_[scope]_case_management.xml.
      - Deterministic 32-char lowercase hex sys_id: computed as
        MD5("sp_page_x_[scope]_case_submit") = 6a1f3c2ffd653613304512a734aab83b.
        Re-generation of this XML is byte-identical (no random UUIDs).
      - Audit fields: <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by> and
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on> for stable
        repeatable timestamps (the same date is used by EVERY sibling
        record in this scoped app for repeatable XML re-generation).
      - No smart quotes, no leading/trailing whitespace, no BOM. Strict
        XML conformance for ServiceNow Update Set re-import preview
        (AAP Section 0.7.3 validation gate 7).

    SOURCE-SIDE SEMANTIC REFERENCE (read-only context, NOT byte-for-byte
    ported per AAP Section 0.5.1):

      acm-services/acm-service-portal-gateway/src/main/java/com/armedia/acm/
      portalgateway/service/DefaultPluggablePortalRequestService.java
        line 48 - public class DefaultPluggablePortalRequestService implements
                  PortalRequestService { ... }
        line 60-65 - submitRequest(...) implementation; resolves provider by
                     request type and forwards.

      acm-standard-applications/arkcase/src/main/webapp/resources/modules/
      cases/services/case-info.client.service.js
        line 13 - angular.module('services').factory('Case.InfoService', ...)
        line 39-42 - save: { method: 'POST', url: 'api/latest/plugin/casefile' }
        line 21-22 - var caseGetUrl = 'api/latest/plugin/casefile/byId/';
                     var caseUrl = 'api/latest/plugin/casefile/';

      ArkCase implements anonymous portal access through a Java Spring service
      that resolves a `PortalRequestServiceProvider` bean by request type
      (e.g., FOIA) and forwards the call. The internal AngularJS UI uses
      Case.InfoService to POST a case-save payload over $resource. The
      ServiceNow target collapses both surfaces into a single anonymous
      Service Portal page (THIS file) that embeds a widget that POSTs to
      a scripted REST endpoint - no Spring beans, no $resource, no
      AngularJS factory pattern. The Java code's submitRequest() method
      maps semantically to the page->widget->REST->Script-Include->GlideRecord
      chain triggered by THIS page's submission widget.

    CROSS-REFERENCES (AAP Section 0.5.2 dependency ordering):
      THIS RECORD MUST LOAD AFTER:
        - ../../app/sys_scope/x_[scope].xml (scope record; <sys_scope>
          cross-reference resolves against this record's <name>)
        - ../../app/sys_app/x_[scope]_case_management.xml (scoped
          application record; <sys_package> cross-reference resolves
          against this record's <scope>)

      THIS RECORD SHOULD LOAD AFTER (but ServiceNow's two-pass import
      tolerates any order within the same Update Set, since references
      resolve by name):
        - ../widgets/sp_widget_x_[scope]_case_submission_widget.xml (the
          widget embedded in this page's <page_internal> layout JSON;
          cross-reference resolves against this record's <id> field)
        - ../widgets/sp_widget_x_[scope]_case_confirmation_widget.xml
          (transitively, the confirmation widget that the submission
          widget embeds via $sp.getWidget() after successful submit)

      THIS RECORD IS REFERENCED BY:
        - ../sp_portal_x_[scope]_case_portal.xml (the portal's <homepage>,
          <homepage_dv>, <login_page>, and <login_page_dv> fields all
          reference THIS page's <id> field value)

    VALIDATION-GATE MAPPING (AAP Section 0.7.3 - the seven validation
    gates):
      This page record is the FOUNDATIONAL artifact for one of the seven
      validation gates:

        Gate 4 ("Portal - submission"): "Case created from unauthenticated
          portal submission - Case appears in internal list with Draft
          status and correct case number." The page's <public>true</public>
          flag and <internal>false</internal> setting plus the empty
          <roles/> together permit anonymous callers to render the page.
          The <page_internal> layout JSON embeds the submission widget
          which renders the form, calls the REST endpoint, and triggers
          the case creation. Without this page record, anonymous users
          would have no entry-point to the case submission flow.

      Gates 1 (data model), 2 (workflow), 3 (ACLs), 5 (portal-lookup is
      handled by sp_page_x_[scope]_case_status.xml), 6 (dashboards), and
      7 (Update Set integrity) are not directly affected by this file -
      though Gate 7 implicitly requires THIS record's XML to be well-
      formed and to resolve all cross-references on Update Set preview.
-->
<record_update table="sp_page">
    <sp_page action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <category/>
        <description>Unauthenticated Service Portal page for case submission. Embeds the case submission widget (sp_widget_x_[scope]_case_submission_widget) which renders a 5-field form (subject, type, description, requester_name, requester_email) and POSTs to /api/x_[scope]/case_submit. On success, the embedded widget transitively displays the confirmation widget (sp_widget_x_[scope]_case_confirmation_widget) with the returned case number and the verbatim message 'Your case has been submitted'. Member of the x_[scope]_case_portal Experience Portal AND serves as the portal's homepage (the portal record's homepage_dv references this page's id). Replaces ArkCase's acm-service-portal-gateway anonymous-submission pattern. Per AAP Sections 0.4.4 and 0.7.4 and Validation Gate 4 (Portal - submission).</description>
        <draft>false</draft>
        <dynamic_title_structure/>
        <hide_for_kb>true</hide_for_kb>
        <id>x_[scope]_case_submit</id>
        <internal>false</internal>
        <omit_watcher>true</omit_watcher>
        <page_internal><![CDATA[
{
    "containers": [
        {
            "id": "container_main",
            "containerClass": "container",
            "rows": [
                {
                    "id": "row_submit",
                    "columns": [
                        {
                            "id": "col_submit",
                            "size": 12,
                            "instances": [
                                {
                                    "id": "instance_submission_widget",
                                    "widget_id": "x_[scope]_case_submission_widget",
                                    "widgetReference": "x_[scope]_case_submission_widget",
                                    "title": "Submit a Case",
                                    "options": {}
                                }
                            ]
                        }
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
]]></page_internal>
        <page_specific_css/>
        <public>true</public>
        <roles/>
        <sys_class_name>sp_page</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>6a1f3c2ffd653613304512a734aab83b</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>Submit a Case</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_[scope]">x_[scope]</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_[scope]</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sp_page_x_[scope]_case_submit</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <title>Submit a Case</title>
    </sp_page>
</record_update>
