<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the `sys_dictionary` row that
    declares the `status` Choice field on the `x_[scope]_case_task` custom
    table inside the scoped application `x_[scope]_case_management`.

    Per AAP Section 0.5.7 (Data-Model Mapping verbatim) for x_[scope]_case_task:

        Field    Type     Constraints
        status   Choice   Open, In Progress, Closed

    Per AAP Section 0.4.1 (Refactored Structure Planning):
        choices/sys_choice_case_task_status.xml -> Open, In Progress, Closed
        case_task.status default = Open

    THIS DICTIONARY ENTRY ONLY DECLARES THAT THE `status` CHOICE FIELD EXISTS
    ON THE PARENT TABLE. The choice values themselves (Open, In Progress,
    Closed) are authored as separate sys_choice records in
    ../choices/sys_choice_case_task_status.xml. This separation is a
    deliberate consequence of the ServiceNow Choice-field design pattern: a
    sys_dictionary row declares the column shape; sibling sys_choice rows
    declare the allowed string-label values keyed by `name` + `element`
    lookup against this entry. The set of three labels (Open, In Progress,
    Closed) is intentionally minimal compared to x_[scope]_case.status's
    six-state lifecycle; tasks in this POC are simple work items - they do
    not have a Draft pre-state (every task is created Open and immediately
    visible to its assignee), they do not have a Pending sub-state (a task
    that is paused remains "In Progress" with the work simply not advancing),
    and they do not have a Resolved-but-not-Closed half-state (closing a
    task is a single atomic step performed by the assignee). This three-
    label vocabulary is authoritative for the entire POC.

    THIS FIELD IS THE LINCHPIN OF THE CASE-RESOLUTION GUARD. Per AAP Section
    0.5.5 ("In Progress -> Resolved: All linked x_[scope]_case_task records
    have status = Closed") and AAP Section 0.7.4 verbatim, the case state-
    machine flow surfaces the literal blocking error message
        "All tasks must be closed before resolving this case."
    when ANY child task on the case has status != Closed. The query that
    drives the gate, executed by ../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml
    and by the canTransitionToResolved() static method on
    ../script_includes/x_[scope]_CaseTransitionValidator.xml, is:

        var gr = new GlideRecord('x_[scope]_case_task');
        gr.addQuery('case', current.sys_id);
        gr.addQuery('status', '!=', 'Closed');
        gr.setLimit(1);
        gr.query();
        if (gr.next()) {
            // Block the transition and surface the AAP Section 0.7.4
            // verbatim message on the form.
        }

    The query string literal `'Closed'` MUST byte-match the choice value
    authored in ../choices/sys_choice_case_task_status.xml; any divergence
    (e.g., "CLOSED", "closed", "Done", "Complete") would silently let
    cases resolve while open work remained, defeating the AAP Section
    0.7.3 workflow validation gate.

    Operational role of the `status` field on case_task rows:
      - Categorizes each task into exactly one of three lifecycle stages
        so that internal users (case_manager and assigned case_agent)
        can triage at-a-glance: an "Open" task is queued and not yet
        being worked; an "In Progress" task is currently being executed;
        a "Closed" task is finished and contributes to satisfying the
        case-resolution gate.
      - Surfaces on the auto-generated x_[scope]_case_task list view per
        AAP Section 0.4.4 ("Internal user UI" requires "ServiceNow's
        automatic native list and form views for the three custom
        tables").
      - Surfaces on the auto-generated form layout when a user opens an
        individual task record - the assignee toggles status from Open
        to In Progress when starting work and from In Progress to Closed
        when finishing. The form may further be governed by ACLs in
        ../acl/ that restrict write access to the assignee.
      - Surfaces in the parent case's Related List of tasks (rendered
        via the `case` reference field declared in
        ../dictionary/x_[scope]_case_task_case.xml). The Status column
        appears beside Subject, Type, and Due Date so that an internal
        user reviewing a case sees at-a-glance how many child tasks are
        still preventing resolution.
      - Drives the Agent Workspace dashboard's "My overdue tasks" list
        report (per AAP Section 0.5.1: list filtered by
        `due_date < javascript:gs.daysAgoStart(0) AND status != Closed
        AND assigned_to = javascript:gs.getUserID()`). The `status !=
        Closed` clause uses the exact label declared in the sibling
        sys_choice file. Closed tasks are deliberately excluded because
        a finished task cannot be overdue regardless of when its
        due_date fell.
      - The synthetic seed data per AAP Section 0.4.1 minimum-data
        thresholds ("at least one open and one closed task per demo
        case in `In Progress` or `Pending` state, to exercise the
        all-tasks-closed gate") populates this field across both
        Open and Closed labels to deterministically exercise the
        case-resolution gate during fresh-PDI re-import validation.
        Demo cases in Resolved or Closed status carry only Closed
        tasks (otherwise the gate would have blocked the parent case's
        prior In Progress -> Resolved transition); demo cases in
        In Progress or Pending status carry a mix of statuses on
        purpose so that an attempt to advance them through Resolved
        will trigger the verbatim blocking error and confirm the gate
        works end-to-end.

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only, NOT byte-for-byte ported):
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-task-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/task/model/AcmTask.java line 81:
            private String status;
        ArkCase's task `status` was a free-form String field on the
        AcmTask domain object. The field carried NO Bean Validation
        constraints (no @Size, no @NotNull, no @Pattern), so any
        caller could assign any string (despite implementing
        AcmStatefulEntity at AcmTask.java line 33 / 61) and the JPA /
        Activiti layer enforced no enumeration. ArkCase's task-status
        vocabulary was distributed across BPMN process variables and
        Activiti ProcessInstance state; the legal labels included
        ASSIGNED, IN_PROGRESS, COMPLETE, CLOSED, DELETE, NOT_STARTED,
        and several engine-internal identifiers. The ServiceNow
        target replaces this fragmented free-form String with a
        controlled Choice vocabulary of three labels (Open, In Progress,
        Closed) through the `<choice>3</choice>` setting plus the
        sibling sys_choice records. AAP Section 0.1.2 codifies this
        kind of free-form-String -> Choice tightening as the
        ServiceNow-side equivalent of ArkCase's bean-validation
        enforcement.
      - AcmTask.java line 82 also declared `private String pendingStatus;`
        which ArkCase used as a transient sub-state holder while a
        task was being routed through buckslip approvals. The
        ServiceNow target intentionally OMITS pendingStatus because
        the POC scope (AAP Section 0.3.2) explicitly excludes
        BPMN/Activiti, buckslip, and any approval-routing capability;
        all transient state is collapsed back into the single `status`
        Choice. This is consistent with the AAP Section 0.5.7 verbatim
        case_task field set, which lists status as the sole lifecycle
        column.
      - The field name is `status` (lowercase, 6 chars; NOT `state`,
        NOT `taskStatus`, NOT `task_status`) per AAP Section 0.5.7
        verbatim. The intentional naming symmetry with x_[scope]_case
        .status means cross-table reports can render a unified "Status"
        column header without per-table label aliasing, mirroring the
        same naming-symmetry rationale that established `subject` on
        both x_[scope]_case and x_[scope]_case_task and `type` on
        both as well.

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.7.1, 0.7.2, 0.7.4):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: `<name>` resolves to
        `x_[scope]_case_task` within the scoped application, and
        `<sys_scope>` / `<sys_package>` bind THIS dictionary record to
        the same scope by `source` attribute lookup. NO global-scope
        writes - the OOB tables `task`, `incident`, `sys_user`, etc.
        are never modified by this dictionary entry or any other
        artifact in the Update Set.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_ids: the `<sys_scope>` and
        `<sys_package>` text-node values resolve by scope source name
        (`x_[scope]_case_management`), not by literal sys_id. The
        `<sys_id>` text-node value is THIS record's own deterministic
        primary key (MD5 of the canonical field identifier
        `x_[scope]_case_task.status`) and is NOT a reference to any
        other record. The MD5 derivation guarantees that re-generation
        of this Update Set on any agent run produces a byte-identical
        `<sys_id>` (no random UUIDs), which is required for clean
        Update-Set re-import on a fresh PDI without creating duplicate
        sys_dictionary rows. The same derivation pattern is used by
        every sys_dictionary record in this Update Set (e.g.,
        x_[scope]_case_task.subject -> 8cd658b766c404ce4445d191adabd14c,
        x_[scope]_case_task.type    -> 180d00dda06c4b93e4c2c106b621d153,
        x_[scope]_case.status       -> 5f0be2eaed29d45b1d63d64e876d22c4).
      - The literal `[scope]` placeholder is preserved per AAP
        convention; the PDI auto-assigns the actual scope id at App
        Engine Studio creation time. The placeholder appears in
        `<name>`, `<sys_scope>`, `<sys_package>`, and
        `<sys_update_name>` consistently.
      - mandatory=true at the dictionary level. AAP Section 0.5.7's
        verbatim case_task table does not explicitly tag `status`
        with the word "Mandatory" the way it does for `case`,
        `subject`, `assigned_to`, and `due_date`. However, the agent
        prompt's Phase 4 explicitly instructs `<mandatory>true</mandatory>`
        and the implicit requirement is unavoidable for two reasons:
          * The case-resolution gate (AAP Section 0.5.5 / 0.7.4) is
            keyed on `status != Closed`. A NULL status would either
            silently pass the gate (incorrect) or fail it on a row
            that the user has not yet had a chance to populate
            (incorrect). Mandatory enforcement at the dictionary level
            forces every task to land in the controlled vocabulary
            from the moment of insert.
          * The default_value=Open below ensures that the mandatory
            constraint is never a friction point for callers; new
            tasks land in Open without explicit caller action.
        Mandatory enforcement runs at the platform-validation level
        on every insert / update through the standard form, the
        Table API, and any GlideRecord.insert() invocation in
        ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js.
      - read_only=false: an internal user (case_manager or the
        assigned case_agent within the AAP Section 0.5.6 "Assigned
        only" condition, transitively through the parent case) editing
        the task record changes status to drive the task's lifecycle
        forward (Open -> In Progress -> Closed). The read_only=false
        setting permits the write through the standard form, the
        Table API, and the seed scripts. Internal-user write
        authorization is governed by the table-level ACLs in ../acl/ -
        this dictionary entry deliberately does NOT carry per-role
        write_roles since the table-level ACLs apply uniformly across
        all editable fields on x_[scope]_case_task. There is no
        backward-transition prohibition on case_task.status (unlike
        x_[scope]_case.status, which prohibits any backward transition
        to Draft and prohibits any transition out of Closed); a task
        accidentally moved from Closed to In Progress by an authorized
        user is recoverable in the POC. If the surrounding parent
        case has already advanced to Resolved or Closed, the
        resolution-gate logic is one-shot evaluated at the moment of
        the parent case's transition - re-opening a child task does
        NOT retroactively roll back the parent case.
      - default_value=Open (Title Case, NOT "OPEN", NOT "open", NOT
        "New") per AAP Section 0.4.1 verbatim ("case_task.status
        default = Open") and the agent prompt's Phase 4. New tasks -
        whether created via the internal form, the Table API, or seed
        scripts - start in Open status. This default is what allows
        seed scripts and bulk-task-creation flows to omit the status
        field from their INSERT payload while still landing every
        new task in the correct starting state. It also means a
        case_manager creating a fresh task on an active case does
        NOT need to remember to pick a status; the form is pre-
        populated and the task is immediately visible to its
        assignee at creation time.
      - audit=false per AAP Section 0.3.1 minimal-change clause and
        the agent prompt's Phase 4. Unlike x_[scope]_case.status
        (which uses audit=true so that compliance teams can
        reconstruct the lifecycle of every case), the case_task POC
        does not require per-field audit history on the task. Record-
        level changes are still captured by the standard sys_*
        audit columns (sys_updated_on, sys_updated_by) declared at
        the table level in ../tables/x_[scope]_case_task.xml. If a
        future enhancement requires per-status forensics on tasks
        (e.g., to compute average task-cycle time from Open to
        Closed), audit=true can be added without breaking any
        existing artifact in this Update Set.
      - max_length=40 per the agent prompt's Phase 3 verbatim. The
        longest defined label is "In Progress" (11 characters); the
        40-character ceiling accommodates extensible future labels
        (e.g., "Awaiting Review", "Pending Reassignment") without a
        schema migration. The same 40-character ceiling is used on
        every Choice field in this Update Set (case.type, case.status,
        case.priority, case.pending_reason, case_task.type,
        case_party.party_type) for consistency.
      - choice=3 = "Choice list, no description column" per the agent
        prompt's Phase 3 verbatim. This is the standard Choice-field
        configuration when a sibling sys_choice record set defines
        the allowed values; the form renderer presents the field as
        a select dropdown sourced from the matching sys_choice rows.
        choice=0 (free-form String) would defeat the purpose of
        constraining the field to a controlled vocabulary; choice=1
        (Choice list with description) would impose a description
        column that AAP Section 0.5.7 does not specify; choice=2
        (Suggestion list) would let users input arbitrary strings
        adjacent to the suggested ones, which would silently break
        the resolution-gate query (a typo'd "closed" or "Closd" would
        evade `status != 'Closed'` and falsely pass the gate).
      - unique=false: multiple tasks with the same status are
        explicitly permitted, both within a single case (a case in
        early lifecycle may have three Open tasks queued for the same
        assignee) and across cases (every active case may have an
        Open task). Uniqueness is not a meaningful concept for a
        categorical Choice field.
      - text_index=false per the agent prompt's Phase 6 verbatim. A
        Choice field with three labels does not benefit from a text
        index; users navigate status via the Choice dropdown and
        list-view filters, not free-form full-text search. The
        resolution-gate query uses `addQuery('status', '!=', 'Closed')`
        which is served by the standard column index, not a text
        index.
      - spell_check=false per the agent prompt's Phase 6 verbatim.
        A controlled Choice vocabulary is by definition correctly
        spelled; spell_check on a Choice field would produce false
        positives on label tokens that the platform dictionary does
        not recognize.
      - No reference target: this is a String-backed Choice field,
        not a Reference field. All `<reference*>` elements are empty
        and `<table_reference>false</table_reference>`. The field
        does NOT reference an external lookup table; the choice
        values live as sys_choice rows keyed by element name.
      - No PII: the field stores only categorical labels chosen from
        a controlled vocabulary; no real names, email addresses,
        organizational identifiers, or any source-side ArkCase
        production data are derived from or stored in this column at
        any point in the build (per AAP Section 0.3.2 synthetic-data-
        only constraint).

    Cross-references (AAP Section 0.5.2 dependency ordering):
      - This record MUST load AFTER:
          * ../tables/x_[scope]_case_task.xml (parent table; the
            `<name>x_[scope]_case_task</name>` element below references
            the table by name, and the table must exist before any of
            its dictionary entries can be attached)
          * ../app/sys_app/x_[scope]_case_management.xml and
            ../app/sys_scope/x_[scope].xml (scoped application records;
            <sys_scope> and <sys_package> resolve against them by source
            name)
      - This record MUST load BEFORE:
          * ../choices/sys_choice_case_task_status.xml (the choice
            values Open, In Progress, Closed - which reference this
            dictionary entry by `name` + `element` lookup against the
            strings `x_[scope]_case_task` and `status`)
          * ../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml (the
            subflow that queries `addQuery('status', '!=', 'Closed')`
            to gate the In Progress -> Resolved transition on the
            parent case; failure of the gate surfaces the AAP Section
            0.7.4 verbatim blocking error message "All tasks must be
            closed before resolving this case.")
          * ../script_includes/x_[scope]_CaseTransitionValidator.xml
            (canTransitionToResolved() static method queries this
            field via GlideRecord to check task closure; shared by
            both general_inquiry_state_machine.xml and
            complaint_state_machine.xml)
          * ../reports/x_[scope]_my_overdue_tasks.xml (filter:
            `due_date < javascript:gs.daysAgoStart(0) AND status !=
            Closed AND assigned_to = javascript:gs.getUserID()`;
            consumed by the Agent Workspace dashboard)
          * ../seed-data/tasks/x_[scope]_case_task_demo_*.xml
            (synthetic demo tasks per AAP Section 0.4.1 must populate
            this mandatory field; the seeded mix of Open and Closed
            statuses is what exercises the resolution-gate during
            fresh-PDI re-import validation)
          * ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js (the idempotent server-side
            seed script writes synthetic task status labels via
            GlideRecord.setValue('status', ...))

    Source for the deterministic sys_id derivation:
        echo -n "x_[scope]_case_task.status" | md5sum
        => af19c46ec8457885c75512edec980172

    The MD5 input is the canonical field identifier <name>.<element>,
    matching the same derivation pattern used across all other
    sys_dictionary records in this Update Set.

    Critical naming note carried forward to ../choices/sys_choice_case_task_status.xml:
        The middle label is "In Progress" (with a single ASCII space
        between "In" and "Progress", title case on both words), NOT
        "InProgress" (no space) and NOT "in_progress" (snake case).
        AAP Section 0.5.7 verbatim spells the label "In Progress".
        The third label is "Closed" (NOT "Complete", NOT "Done", NOT
        "Resolved"); the resolution-gate query in
        ../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml uses the
        exact string "Closed" and any deviation in the sibling
        sys_choice rows would silently break the gate.
-->
<record_update table="sys_dictionary">
    <sys_dictionary action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <array>false</array>
        <attributes/>
        <audit>false</audit>
        <calculation/>
        <choice>3</choice>
        <choice_field/>
        <choice_table/>
        <column_label>Status</column_label>
        <comments>Mandatory Choice tracking task lifecycle. Values: Open, In Progress, Closed. Default: Open. Authored as separate sys_choice rows in ../choices/sys_choice_case_task_status.xml. Used by the case state-machine flow's "all tasks closed" guard for the In Progress -&gt; Resolved transition (AAP Section 0.5.5); failure surfaces the verbatim blocking error "All tasks must be closed before resolving this case." (AAP Section 0.7.4). Replaces ArkCase AcmTask.status (free-form String, no validator).</comments>
        <create_roles/>
        <default_value>Open</default_value>
        <defaultsort/>
        <delete_roles/>
        <dependent/>
        <dependent_on_field/>
        <display>true</display>
        <dynamic_creation>false</dynamic_creation>
        <dynamic_creation_script/>
        <dynamic_default_value/>
        <dynamic_ref_qual/>
        <element>status</element>
        <element_reference>false</element_reference>
        <foreign_database/>
        <function_definition/>
        <function_field>false</function_field>
        <internal_type>string</internal_type>
        <mandatory>true</mandatory>
        <max_length>40</max_length>
        <name>x_[scope]_case_task</name>
        <next_element/>
        <primary>false</primary>
        <read_only>false</read_only>
        <read_roles/>
        <reference/>
        <reference_cascade_rule/>
        <reference_floor/>
        <reference_key/>
        <reference_qual/>
        <reference_qual_condition/>
        <reference_type/>
        <sizeclass/>
        <spell_check>false</spell_check>
        <staged>false</staged>
        <sys_class_name>sys_dictionary</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>af19c46ec8457885c75512edec980172</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name/>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_[scope]_case_management">x_[scope]_case_management</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_[scope]_case_management</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_dictionary_x_[scope]_case_task_status</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <table_reference>false</table_reference>
        <text_index>false</text_index>
        <unique>false</unique>
        <use_dependent_field>false</use_dependent_field>
        <use_dynamic_default>false</use_dynamic_default>
        <use_reference_qualifier>simple</use_reference_qualifier>
        <virtual>false</virtual>
        <virtual_type/>
        <widget/>
        <write_roles/>
        <xml_view>false</xml_view>
    </sys_dictionary>
</record_update>
