<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the `sys_dictionary` row that
    declares the `due_date` Date field on the `x_[scope]_case_task` custom
    table inside the scoped application `x_[scope]_case_management`.

    Per AAP Section 0.5.7 (Data-Model Mapping verbatim) for x_[scope]_case_task:

        Field      Type    Constraints
        due_date   Date    Mandatory

    THIS FIELD CAPTURES WHEN THE TASK IS DUE. It is the only Date column on
    the case_task table (every other timestamp surface in the POC schema -
    x_[scope]_case.opened_date and x_[scope]_case.closed_date - is a
    DateTime). The deliberate Date vs. DateTime distinction is significant:
    tasks in this POC are unit-of-work delegations with day-level
    granularity. A task is "due today", "due tomorrow", "due Friday" - never
    "due at 3:47 PM on Friday". Date-level precision avoids spurious
    overdue-by-one-hour edge cases at midnight rollover, simplifies the
    "My Overdue Tasks" report's date-arithmetic, and renders cleanly on the
    auto-generated form layout (the platform's Date picker is simpler than
    the DateTime picker - no time-of-day spinner, no timezone qualifier).

    Critical behaviors that depend on this field (AAP Sections 0.4.1,
    0.4.4, 0.5.7, 0.7.4):

      1. "MY OVERDUE TASKS" REPORT FOR AGENT WORKSPACE DASHBOARD
         (../reports/x_[scope]_my_overdue_tasks.xml,
          ../dashboards/pa_dashboards_x_[scope]_agent_workspace.xml)
         Per AAP Section 0.4.1 the Agent Workspace dashboard surfaces a
         "My overdue tasks" list widget whose underlying report filters
         x_[scope]_case_task rows by:
             due_date < javascript:gs.daysAgoStart(0)
               AND status != Closed
               AND assigned_to = javascript:gs.getUserID()
         The first filter clause (`due_date < javascript:gs.daysAgoStart(0)`)
         REQUIRES this dictionary entry to exist with
         `<internal_type>glide_date</internal_type>` so the platform's
         report engine can compare the column to the
         `javascript:gs.daysAgoStart(0)` script-time value. The
         `gs.daysAgoStart(0)` function returns the start of today (midnight
         today, in the session's timezone), and the comparison
         `due_date < <start of today>` returns rows whose due date is on
         any day BEFORE today. Tasks due today are NOT flagged as overdue
         until tomorrow - this is the conventional and expected semantic
         for an overdue list. Without this dictionary record, the report's
         WHERE-clause would fail to compile and the dashboard widget would
         render empty or error.

         The choice of `glide_date` over `glide_date_time` is critical for
         this comparison. With `glide_date`, the column stores a date
         (YYYY-MM-DD, no time-of-day component); the `<` comparison
         against `gs.daysAgoStart(0)` (which evaluates to today's
         midnight) correctly returns yesterday's and earlier rows but
         excludes today's rows. If this column were `glide_date_time`, a
         task with `due_date = 2025-04-30 00:00:00` would be excluded
         (correctly), but a task with `due_date = 2025-04-30 14:30:00`
         would also be excluded (also correctly, since 14:30 today is
         not before midnight today) - HOWEVER, a task created with
         `due_date = 2025-04-30 00:00:00` could appear or not appear in
         the overdue list depending on micro-second ordering between
         insert and query, leading to spurious flicker. `glide_date`
         eliminates this entire class of edge cases.

      2. AUTOMATIC FORM-LAYOUT INCLUSION ON x_[scope]_case_task
         (parent table ../tables/x_[scope]_case_task.xml automatic form
          layout per AAP Section 0.4.4 "Internal user UI" requirements)
         Per AAP Section 0.4.4 ("ServiceNow's automatic native list and
         form views for the three custom tables"), when an internal user
         opens a x_[scope]_case_task record, the form auto-renders every
         dictionary field in declared order. This entry contributes the
         "Due Date" picker (a date picker that lets the task creator
         select a calendar date by clicking through a month-grid widget,
         with no hour/minute/second spinners). Due date is one of the
         four user-facing input fields a case_agent or case_manager fills
         in when creating a new task from the parent case's Related List
         (the others being Subject, Type, Assigned To - with Status
         defaulting to Open at insert time and Case auto-populated from
         the Related List context).

      3. RELATED-LIST DISPLAY COLUMN ON THE PARENT CASE FORM
         (parent table ../tables/x_[scope]_case.xml automatic Related
          List rendering per AAP Section 0.4.4)
         Per AAP Section 0.4.4 the parent case form auto-renders a
         Related List of x_[scope]_case_task rows filtered by
         `case = current.sys_id`. The default columns surfaced in the
         related list - Subject, Type, Status, Assigned To, Due Date -
         allow a manager or agent reviewing the case to see at-a-glance
         WHEN each pending task is due. The "Due Date" column renders
         using the platform's locale-aware date format (e.g., MM/DD/YYYY
         in en-US, DD/MM/YYYY in en-GB) by virtue of the dictionary's
         internal_type=glide_date setting; no per-column display script
         is required.

      4. CASE-RESOLUTION GATE ANCILLARY ROLE
         (../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml,
          ../script_includes/x_[scope]_CaseTransitionValidator.xml)
         Per AAP Section 0.5.5 the case state-machine flows block the
         In Progress -> Resolved transition when ANY child task has
         status != Closed. The gate's primary key is `status` (declared
         in ../dictionary/x_[scope]_case_task_status.xml), but `due_date`
         is the ancillary signal that explains WHY the gate is blocking:
         a manager attempting to resolve a case can see in the Related
         List which open child tasks are blocking, AND when those tasks
         were due, allowing prioritization of which task to address
         first. Tasks blocking case resolution are typically those whose
         due_date has already passed and whose status is still Open or
         In Progress.

      5. SEED-DATA POPULATION VIA SYNTHETIC DATES
         (../seed-data/tasks/x_[scope]_case_task_demo_*.xml,
          ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js)
         Per AAP Section 0.7.4's minimum demo-data thresholds ("at least
         one open and one closed task per demo case in 'In Progress' or
         'Pending' state, to exercise the 'all-tasks-closed' gate"), the
         seed-data XMLs and the idempotent seed_demo_data.js script
         populate this field with synthetic dates spanning past, present,
         and future ranges so that the Agent Workspace dashboard's "My
         overdue tasks" widget displays a non-zero count on a fresh PDI
         immediately after Update Set commit. Demo tasks with status =
         Open or In Progress and due_date in the past exercise the
         overdue-list filter; demo tasks with status = Closed and any
         due_date are excluded from the overdue list (correctly - a
         closed task cannot be overdue); demo tasks with future
         due_dates exercise the form's date-picker on a non-overdue
         row. There are NO PII references in any synthetic due_date -
         the column stores only an ISO-formatted calendar date.

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only, NOT byte-for-byte ported):
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-task-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/task/model/AcmTask.java lines 70-71:
            @NotNull
            private Date dueDate;
        ArkCase's AcmTask used a JPA `Date` column to capture the task's
        due date with the Bean Validation annotation `@NotNull`. The
        `@NotNull` JSR-303 constraint was enforced by the validation
        layer at every persist / merge call site - any attempt to save
        an AcmTask with a null dueDate would throw a
        ConstraintViolationException before the JPA INSERT/UPDATE was
        emitted to MySQL. The companion getter/setter at lines 232-240
            public Date getDueDate()  { return dueDate; }
            public void setDueDate(Date dueDate) { this.dueDate = dueDate; }
        materialised the value as a java.util.Date, which carries
        millisecond-since-epoch precision (date + time + timezone) - a
        deliberate over-precision relative to what the case-management
        UX needed. ArkCase's UI normalised the value to date-only at
        display time, but the storage layer always carried the
        microsecond-precise UTC instant.

        The ServiceNow target translates these JPA semantics as follows:
          * @NotNull -> mandatory=true at the dictionary level
            (the platform's pre-insert validation pass blocks every
            null-valued INSERT/UPDATE through the form, the Table API,
            and any GlideRecord.insert() invocation - the same guarantee
            ArkCase's Bean Validation provided)
          * java.util.Date (millisecond-precise UTC instant) ->
            internal_type=glide_date (date-only, no time-of-day
            component) - an INTENTIONAL precision REDUCTION matching
            the AAP Section 0.5.7 verbatim "Date" type. The case-
            management domain UX was never going to use the millisecond
            precision; the source-side over-precision was an accident
            of the JPA Date type, not a deliberate design choice. The
            target reduces precision to match the actual semantic.
          * default behavior (no JPA default) -> default_value/ empty
            (no platform default; the user must explicitly choose a
            date when creating a task)

      - The field name is `due_date` (lowercase, snake_case; NOT
        `dueDate`, NOT `due`, NOT `task_due_date`, NOT `deadline`) per
        AAP Section 0.5.7 verbatim. The intentional rename from
        ArkCase's camelCase `dueDate` to snake_case `due_date` aligns
        with the ServiceNow convention used by OOB tables (e.g.,
        change_request.due_date, sc_req_item.due_date, task.due_date
        all use lowercase snake_case) and reads naturally on the
        auto-generated list/form views ("Due Date" column header
        derived from `<column_label>` rather than from the field
        name).

      - ArkCase's Date column had no explicit JPA length cap (the
        column was a TIMESTAMP datatype in MySQL, fixed-width). The
        ServiceNow target uses the standard 40-character Date/DateTime
        max_length per the agent prompt's Phase 3 verbatim. ServiceNow
        stores Date values in a canonical YYYY-MM-DD format (10 chars)
        with optional locale-formatting suffix; 40 chars provides ample
        headroom for any current or future canonical encoding without
        a schema migration.

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.7.1, 0.7.2, 0.7.4):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: `<name>` resolves to
        `x_[scope]_case_task` within the scoped application, and
        `<sys_scope>` / `<sys_package>` bind THIS dictionary record to
        the same scope by `source` attribute lookup. NO global-scope
        writes - the OOB tables `task`, `incident`, `sys_user`, etc.
        are never modified by this dictionary entry or any other
        artifact in the Update Set.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_ids: the `<sys_scope>` and
        `<sys_package>` text-node values resolve by scope source name
        (`x_[scope]_case_management`), not by literal sys_id. The
        `<sys_id>` text-node value is THIS record's own deterministic
        primary key (MD5 of the canonical field identifier
        `x_[scope]_case_task.due_date` =
        a20971037c6fb4c520d7a13231b15f3b) and is NOT a reference to
        any other record. The MD5 derivation guarantees that
        re-generation of this Update Set on any agent run produces a
        byte-identical `<sys_id>` (no random UUIDs), which is required
        for clean Update-Set re-import on a fresh PDI without creating
        duplicate sys_dictionary rows. The same derivation pattern is
        used by every sys_dictionary record in this Update Set (e.g.,
        x_[scope]_case_task.subject       -> 8cd658b766c404ce4445d191adabd14c,
        x_[scope]_case_task.type          -> 180d00dda06c4b93e4c2c106b621d153,
        x_[scope]_case_task.status        -> 5f0be2eaed29d45b1d63d64e876d22c4,
        x_[scope]_case_task.assigned_to   -> 388df21ea3ca149d70916144f84ecf42,
        x_[scope]_case.opened_date        -> 3e18b5498c00dfde143bbc84fced474c).
      - The literal `[scope]` placeholder is preserved per AAP
        convention; the PDI auto-assigns the actual scope id at App
        Engine Studio creation time. The placeholder appears in
        `<name>`, `<sys_scope>`, `<sys_package>`, and
        `<sys_update_name>` consistently.
      - mandatory=true at the dictionary level. AAP Section 0.5.7's
        verbatim case_task table tags `due_date` explicitly as
        Mandatory; the source-side `@NotNull` Bean Validation
        annotation reinforces this. Mandatory enforcement runs at the
        platform-validation level on every insert / update through the
        standard form, the Table API, and any GlideRecord.insert()
        invocation in ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js. The `@NotNull`
        constraint on the source side fires at the JPA persist layer;
        the ServiceNow `mandatory=true` setting fires at the platform's
        pre-insert validation pass - both are blocking validations
        with equivalent semantics.
      - read_only=false: the user creating a task chooses the due
        date, and the case_manager / assigned case_agent may edit the
        due date as project plans evolve. The read_only=false setting
        permits the write through the standard form, the Table API,
        and the seed scripts. Internal-user write authorization is
        governed by the table-level ACLs in ../acl/ - this dictionary
        entry deliberately does NOT carry per-role write_roles since
        the table-level ACLs apply uniformly across all editable
        fields on x_[scope]_case_task. There is no platform-side
        prohibition on adjusting due_date once a task is in flight,
        nor is the field locked once the task is Closed (a closed
        task's historical due date remains editable for forensic
        correction, though such edits are rare in practice).
      - default_value is EMPTY (no implicit default) per the agent
        prompt's Phase 4 verbatim. ServiceNow's static dictionary
        default_value attribute supports literal values only - a
        runtime-evaluated default like `gs.daysAgoStart(-7)` (a week
        from today) cannot be encoded as a static dictionary default
        and would in any case impose an arbitrary policy that the
        AAP does not specify. The user MUST explicitly choose a date
        when creating a task; there is no fallback. This forces the
        creator to think about realistic timing for the work, which
        is consistent with the case-management domain (assigning a
        task without thinking about when it should be done is a
        process anti-pattern).
      - audit=false per AAP Section 0.3.1 minimal-change clause and
        the agent prompt's Phase 4. The standard sys_* audit columns
        on every ServiceNow row already capture the row's last-modified
        timestamp at platform-default granularity (sys_updated_on,
        sys_updated_by); per-field audit history on due_date is not
        required for the POC. If a future enhancement requires
        forensic reconstruction of due-date adjustments (e.g., to
        compute average due-date slippage from creation to closure),
        audit=true can be added without breaking any existing artifact
        in this Update Set.
      - active=true: the field is part of the live schema from
        Update Set commit forward. There is no transitional / staged
        / inactive phase for the case_task schema in the POC.
      - display=true: the field renders on the standard list and form
        views for `x_[scope]_case_task`. Internal users (manager,
        agent, viewer) see the due date on the task form; the parent
        case's Related List of tasks also surfaces the due date column.
      - max_length=40 per the agent prompt's Phase 3 verbatim. Date
        values are stored in canonical YYYY-MM-DD format (10 chars);
        40 chars is the standard ServiceNow ceiling for date/datetime
        fields and provides headroom for any future canonical
        encoding (e.g., locale-formatted strings, ISO 8601 with
        fractional precision) without schema migration.
      - choice=0: free-form Date input (no choice list). The
        platform's standard date picker widget renders for input on
        the form; the report builder uses native Date comparison
        operators on the column. choice=3 (Choice list, no description
        column) would defeat the purpose of a calendar-pickable date
        field; choice=1 (Choice list with description) would be
        nonsensical for a continuous-domain value like a calendar
        date. Free-form Date input is the only correct setting.
      - No reference target: this is a Date field, not a Reference
        field. All `<reference*>` elements are empty and
        `<table_reference>false</table_reference>`.
      - text_index=false: Date fields are not full-text-indexed.
        The platform's standard Date comparison operators on
        GlideRecord.addQuery() (e.g., `addQuery('due_date', '<',
        javascript:gs.daysAgoStart(0))`) operate directly on the
        column without needing a full-text index.
      - unique=false: tasks legitimately share due dates when bulk-
        imported, when seed data is loaded, when a case_manager
        creates multiple tasks all due by the same Friday deadline,
        or when independent task creation flows arrive within the
        same calendar day. Uniqueness across tasks is enforced by
        sys_id (the platform-managed primary key) and by the optional
        TASK0000001-format number declared in
        ../numbers/sys_number_x_[scope]_case_task.xml, NOT by due_date.
      - virtual=false: this is a stored column, not a calculated /
        virtual derivation.
      - No PII: the field stores only a calendar date; no real names,
        email addresses, organizational identifiers, or other
        personally identifiable information are derived from or
        stored in this column. Synthetic seed data populates this
        field with arbitrary dates that do not correspond to any
        real-world events.

    Cross-references (AAP Section 0.5.2 dependency ordering):
      - This record MUST load AFTER `../tables/x_[scope]_case_task.xml`
        (parent table), since `<name>x_[scope]_case_task</name>`
        references the table by name. The parent table record creates
        the underlying sys_db_object row that this dictionary entry
        attaches a column to; loading this dictionary entry before the
        table would fail with a "table not found" preview error.
      - This record MUST load BEFORE the consumers that read or write
        the `due_date` column:
          * ../reports/x_[scope]_my_overdue_tasks.xml (the "My Overdue
            Tasks" list report on the Agent Workspace dashboard;
            filters by `due_date < javascript:gs.daysAgoStart(0) AND
            status != Closed AND assigned_to = javascript:gs.getUserID()`
            - the report's WHERE clause references this column by
            element name and would fail to compile against the table
            if this dictionary entry is absent)
          * ../dashboards/pa_dashboards_x_[scope]_agent_workspace.xml
            (the Agent Workspace dashboard that surfaces the overdue-
            tasks report widget)
          * ../seed-data/tasks/x_[scope]_case_task_demo_*.xml
            (synthetic demo tasks populate this field with arbitrary
            calendar dates - some past for the overdue-list demo, some
            present, some future - so the dashboard widgets render
            non-empty data on a fresh PDI immediately after Update Set
            commit)
          * ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js (the idempotent seed script
            that creates the demo task rows; for each demo task it
            sets `taskGr.due_date = '<calendar-date>';` - the script
            cannot set a non-existent column, so this dictionary entry
            must be present in the Update Set ahead of the seed script's
            execution)
-->
<record_update table="sys_dictionary">
    <sys_dictionary action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <array>false</array>
        <attributes/>
        <audit>false</audit>
        <calculation/>
        <choice>0</choice>
        <choice_field/>
        <choice_table/>
        <column_label>Due Date</column_label>
        <comments>Mandatory date when the task is due. Used by the My Overdue Tasks report (filter: due_date less than Today AND status not equal to Closed). Replaces ArkCase AcmTask.dueDate (@NotNull Date).</comments>
        <create_roles/>
        <default_value/>
        <defaultsort/>
        <delete_roles/>
        <dependent/>
        <dependent_on_field/>
        <display>true</display>
        <dynamic_creation>false</dynamic_creation>
        <dynamic_creation_script/>
        <dynamic_default_value/>
        <dynamic_ref_qual/>
        <element>due_date</element>
        <element_reference>false</element_reference>
        <foreign_database/>
        <function_definition/>
        <function_field>false</function_field>
        <internal_type>glide_date</internal_type>
        <mandatory>true</mandatory>
        <max_length>40</max_length>
        <name>x_[scope]_case_task</name>
        <next_element/>
        <primary>false</primary>
        <read_only>false</read_only>
        <read_roles/>
        <reference/>
        <reference_cascade_rule/>
        <reference_floor/>
        <reference_key/>
        <reference_qual/>
        <reference_qual_condition/>
        <reference_type/>
        <sizeclass/>
        <spell_check>false</spell_check>
        <staged>false</staged>
        <sys_class_name>sys_dictionary</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>a20971037c6fb4c520d7a13231b15f3b</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name/>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_[scope]_case_management">x_[scope]_case_management</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_[scope]_case_management</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_dictionary_x_[scope]_case_task_due_date</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <table_reference>false</table_reference>
        <text_index>false</text_index>
        <unique>false</unique>
        <use_dependent_field>false</use_dependent_field>
        <use_dynamic_default>false</use_dynamic_default>
        <use_reference_qualifier>simple</use_reference_qualifier>
        <virtual>false</virtual>
        <virtual_type/>
        <widget/>
        <write_roles/>
        <xml_view>false</xml_view>
    </sys_dictionary>
</record_update>
