<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the `sys_dictionary` row that
    declares the `assigned_to` Reference field on the `x_[scope]_case_task`
    custom table inside the scoped application `x_[scope]_case_management`.

    Per AAP Section 0.5.7 (Data-Model Mapping verbatim) for x_[scope]_case_task:

        Field         Type                    Constraints
        assigned_to   Reference -> sys_user   Mandatory

    THIS FIELD IS THE PER-TASK OWNERSHIP COLUMN. It captures the single
    sys_user who is responsible for completing the task. Every task in the
    POC scoped application MUST have exactly one assignee at all times -
    there is no concept of "unassigned" tasks (in contrast to AAP Section
    0.5.7's parent x_[scope]_case.assigned_agent column, which is
    explicitly Optional so that Draft and Open cases may be created
    without an owner). Tasks are atomic units of work created BY a
    case_manager or case_agent specifically to delegate to a known user;
    creating a task with no assignee would be semantically meaningless
    in this POC's workflow model.

    Critical behaviors that depend on this field (AAP Sections 0.4.1,
    0.4.4, 0.5.7, 0.7.4):

      1. "MY OVERDUE TASKS" REPORT FOR AGENT WORKSPACE DASHBOARD
         (../reports/x_[scope]_my_overdue_tasks.xml,
          ../dashboards/pa_dashboards_x_[scope]_agent_workspace.xml)
         Per AAP Section 0.4.1 the Agent Workspace dashboard surfaces a
         "My overdue tasks" list widget that filters x_[scope]_case_task
         rows by:
             due_date < javascript:gs.daysAgoStart(0)
               AND status != Closed
               AND assigned_to = javascript:gs.getUserID()
         The third filter clause (`assigned_to = javascript:gs.getUserID()`)
         REQUIRES this dictionary entry to exist with `<reference>sys_user`
         so the platform's report engine can dot-walk
         current.assigned_to.sys_id and compare it against the current
         session's user sys_id. Without this dictionary record, the
         report's WHERE-clause would fail to compile and the dashboard
         widget would render empty or error. The "My Overdue Tasks"
         widget is one of the three core components of the Agent
         Workspace dashboard - alongside "My Open Cases" (filtered by
         x_[scope]_case.assigned_agent) and "Case count by status" - so
         this field is central to the day-to-day case_agent persona's
         operational view.

      2. AUTOMATIC FORM-LAYOUT INCLUSION ON x_[scope]_case_task
         (parent table ../tables/x_[scope]_case_task.xml automatic form
          layout per AAP Section 0.4.4 "Internal user UI" requirements)
         Per AAP Section 0.4.4 ("ServiceNow's automatic native list and
         form views for the three custom tables"), when an internal user
         opens a x_[scope]_case_task record, the form auto-renders every
         dictionary field in declared order. This entry contributes the
         "Assigned To" picker (a sys_user reference picker that lets the
         task creator search by display name, user_name, email, or
         partial match against the sys_user table). It is one of the
         four user-facing input fields a case_agent fills in when
         creating a new task from the parent case's Related List (the
         others being Subject, Type, Due Date - with Status defaulting
         to Open at insert time and Case auto-populated from the
         Related List context).

      3. RELATED-LIST DISPLAY COLUMN ON THE PARENT CASE FORM
         (parent table ../tables/x_[scope]_case.xml automatic Related
          List rendering per AAP Section 0.4.4)
         Per AAP Section 0.4.4 the parent case form auto-renders a
         Related List of x_[scope]_case_task rows filtered by
         `case = current.sys_id`. The default columns surfaced in the
         related list - Subject, Type, Status, Assigned To, Due Date -
         allow a manager or agent reviewing the case to see at-a-glance
         WHO is responsible for each pending task. The "Assigned To"
         column dereferences this field's sys_id pointer to the user's
         display column (typically `name` on sys_user) for the related
         list rendering, which is a platform-native capability provided
         by virtue of declaring `<reference>sys_user</reference>` here.

      4. ACL "ASSIGNED ONLY" CASCADE FOR CASE_AGENT
         (../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_*.xml)
         Per AAP Section 0.5.6: case_agent has "Assigned only" CRUD
         access. While the AAP defines "Assigned only" at the case level
         as `assigned_agent = current user OR assigned_group contains
         current user`, the case_task table inherits a parallel
         per-task gate: a case_agent may read/write a task ONLY IF the
         agent is the task's `assigned_to` user OR the parent case's
         assigned_agent / assigned_group resolves to the agent's
         identity. The first half of that condition uses THIS field
         directly:
             current.assigned_to == gs.getUserID()
         The second half uses the `case` reference field declared in
         ../dictionary/x_[scope]_case_task_case.xml to dot-walk to the
         parent case's assigned_agent / assigned_group. This dictionary
         entry's `<reference>sys_user</reference>` makes the first
         condition expressible because the platform's reference engine
         resolves `current.assigned_to` to a sys_user sys_id at ACL
         evaluation time.

      5. SEED-DATA POPULATION VIA user_name LOOKUP
         (../seed-data/tasks/x_[scope]_case_task_demo_*.xml,
          ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js)
         Per AAP Section 0.5.2 reference-resolution rules: "User
         references (e.g., on assigned_agent, assigned_to, seed data) ->
         look up sys_user by `user_name`." The seed-data XMLs and the
         idempotent seed_demo_data.js script resolve the assignee
         sys_id at seed time via:
             var userGr = new GlideRecord('sys_user');
             userGr.addQuery('user_name', 'x_[scope]_demo_agent');
             userGr.query();
             if (userGr.next()) { taskGr.assigned_to = userGr.sys_id; }
         There are NO hard-coded sys_id literals in any seed file
         pointing into this column - all references resolve by the
         human-readable user_name attribute, per AAP Section 0.7.2 "no
         hardcoded sys_id constraint" applied to seed data. AAP Section
         0.7.4's minimum demo-data thresholds require "at least one
         open and one closed task per demo case in 'In Progress' or
         'Pending' state, to exercise the 'all-tasks-closed' gate" -
         all such seed tasks resolve their assigned_to via this lookup
         pattern against the synthetic demo users at
         ../seed-data/users/sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_*.xml.

      6. CASCADE-DELETE BEHAVIOR (DEFAULT - NO CASCADE)
         (this dictionary entry's `<reference_cascade_rule/>` element)
         Per the agent prompt's Phase 3 instruction
         (`<reference_cascade_rule/>` - empty (no cascade behavior on
         user deletion)), the platform's default reference-deletion
         semantics apply: when a sys_user is deleted (a rare global-
         admin operation), tasks retain the orphaned reference rather
         than being auto-deleted. This is the POC-safe default because
         user deletion is gated by global ACLs not modified by this
         scoped application (per AAP Section 0.3.2 "No global ACLs"),
         and silent cascade-deletion of every task assigned to a
         deactivated user would be a destructive action with no audit
         signal. Manual cleanup or reassignment of orphaned tasks is
         acceptable and surfaces operator awareness. The empty element
         (in contrast to the explicit "none" literal used on the
         sibling x_[scope]_case_task.case field) is functionally
         equivalent and is what the agent prompt's Phase 3 specifies
         for THIS field.

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only, NOT byte-for-byte ported):
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-task-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/task/model/AcmTask.java line 75:
            private String assignee;
        ArkCase's AcmTask used a free-form String column to capture the
        assignee. The String value was the LDAP id (a username
        attribute resolvable against the OpenLDAP directory backing
        ArkCase) - NOT a foreign key to a user table. The companion
        getter/setter at lines 252-260
            public String getAssignee()  { return assignee; }
            public void   setAssignee(String assignee) { this.assignee = assignee; }
        materialised the assignee as a free-form String at every
        access; the application layer was responsible for treating it
        as a user identifier and resolving it (when needed) through the
        AcmUser DAO to fetch the user's display name, email, manager,
        etc. This was a known pain point: the LDAP id could be
        misspelled, could refer to a deactivated user, or could fail to
        map to a sys_user-equivalent row entirely - the String field
        was the only authority and was free-form.

        AcmTask.java line 122 documents the runtime semantic of the
        assignee column:
            "When a user claims a task, then the task is assigned to
             that user, and is not part of the group bucket any more."
        The ArkCase pattern combined the `assignee` String column with
        a `candidateGroups` List<String> column (line 125) such that a
        task could be in one of two states: claim-pending (assignee
        empty, candidateGroups populated) or claimed (assignee set,
        candidateGroups irrelevant). The ServiceNow target SIMPLIFIES
        this two-stage pattern into a single mandatory `assigned_to`
        column - per AAP Section 0.3.1's MINIMAL CHANGE CLAUSE the POC
        does not replicate the candidate-group claiming mechanism (it
        is an Activiti BPM feature not enumerated in AAP Section
        0.5.7's six-field target schema), and therefore does not need
        the optional/empty assignee state that arkcase needed for
        unclaimed tasks.

        The ServiceNow target replaces the participants-list-as-source-
        of-truth pattern with a single proper foreign-key Reference
        column on the task row, gaining four critical capabilities:
          * Referential integrity: only existing, active sys_user rows
            may be chosen (the platform's reference picker enforces
            this; no scripted REST or background-script bypass exists
            for case_task creation since AAP Section 0.4.1 specifies no
            anonymous-task-submission portal endpoint).
          * Single source of truth: the same `sys_user` table that
            ServiceNow uses for all OOB authentication, role
            assignment, notification delivery, and dashboard scoping is
            now the canonical user backing task ownership.
          * Dot-walk dereferencing: ACL conditions, form layouts, and
            list views can traverse `current.assigned_to.name`,
            `current.assigned_to.email`, or `current.assigned_to.manager`
            because the column is a typed reference rather than a
            free-form String.
          * Cascade safety: the platform's reference-deletion semantics
            (cascade rule, controlled by the `<reference_cascade_rule/>`
            element below - left empty for default "no cascade"
            behavior) prevent accidental orphaning of tasks when a user
            is deactivated. ArkCase's String-username pattern silently
            broke when LDAP entries were renamed or removed.

      - The field name is `assigned_to` (lowercase, snake_case; NOT
        `assignee`, NOT `assignedTo`, NOT `assigneeLdapId`, NOT
        `assigned_user`, NOT `assigned_agent`) per AAP Section 0.5.7
        verbatim. This is an INTENTIONAL rename from ArkCase's
        `assignee` String column to align with the ServiceNow
        convention used by OOB tables (incident.assigned_to,
        sc_request.assigned_to, change_request.assigned_to all use
        `assigned_to` for the per-record-assignee column). The
        asymmetry with the parent x_[scope]_case table's
        `assigned_agent` field name is intentional: at the case level
        the AAP chose the domain-specific "agent" terminology to evoke
        the case-management persona; at the task level the OOB
        convention is preserved verbatim because tasks are generic
        work items that may be assigned to any user (case_manager,
        case_agent, or case_viewer alike, though case_viewer cannot
        be assigned by ACL since they have no write access).

      - ArkCase's `assignee` String had no explicit length cap
        (defaulting to the database-engine VARCHAR(255) for MySQL
        InnoDB). The ServiceNow target uses the standard 32-character
        Reference-field width to store the sys_id of the chosen
        sys_user row; the platform's auto-generated form picker, list
        view, and report builder all dereference to the user's display
        column (typically `name` or `user_name`) for human-readable
        display via the OOB sys_user dictionary's display=true column.

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.7.1, 0.7.2, 0.7.4):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: `<name>` resolves to
        `x_[scope]_case_task` within the scoped application, and
        `<sys_scope>` / `<sys_package>` bind THIS dictionary record to
        the same scope by `source` attribute lookup. The `<reference>`
        element resolves to OOB `sys_user` by table name (NOT by
        sys_id), preserving zero-hardcoded-sys_id compliance. NO
        global-scope writes - the OOB `sys_user` table is REFERENCED
        but never modified.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_ids: the `<sys_scope>`,
        `<sys_package>`, and `<reference>` text-node values resolve by
        scope source name and table name respectively, not by literal
        sys_id. The `<sys_id>` text-node value is THIS record's own
        deterministic primary key (MD5 of the canonical field
        identifier `x_[scope]_case_task.assigned_to` =
        388df21ea3ca149d70916144f84ecf42) and is NOT a reference to
        any other record. Per AAP Section 0.7.2 this scheme guarantees
        that a fresh PDI re-import of the Update Set produces byte-
        identical sys_id values, which is necessary for round-trip-
        verify (../scripts/round_trip_verify.md) zero-error preview.
      - The literal `[scope]` placeholder is preserved per AAP
        convention; the PDI auto-assigns the actual scope id at App
        Engine Studio creation time and substitutes it into every
        occurrence at export.
      - mandatory=true at the dictionary level: AAP Section 0.5.7
        verbatim declares the `assigned_to` field on x_[scope]_case_task
        as Mandatory with no qualifying suffix (in contrast to
        x_[scope]_case.assigned_group which says "Mandatory on Open
        transition" - a transition-level constraint NOT enforced at
        the dictionary level - and x_[scope]_case.assigned_agent which
        says "Optional" outright). For case_task.assigned_to,
        mandatoriness is absolute: a task without an assignee is
        semantically meaningless (the entire raison d'etre of creating
        a task is to delegate work to a specific user), and the
        platform's mandatory flag enforces the constraint at every
        entry point - manual save in the form, GlideRecord.insert()
        from server-side scripts, and Table API POST. There is NO
        submission path in this scoped application that legitimately
        creates a task without an assignee (no portal-anonymous task
        creation, no bulk-import of headless tasks, etc.), so a hard
        mandatory flag produces zero false-positive rejections.
      - read_only=false: case_manager and the case_agent (when the
        case is "Assigned only" to them) both edit this field directly
        when creating tasks under a case. The auto-generated New Task
        form on the case's Related List leaves `assigned_to` empty by
        default (AAP does not specify a default assignee), prompting
        the creator to explicitly choose a user. Field-level write
        access is governed by the table-level ACLs at
        ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_*.xml (no separate field-level ACL
        is needed for `assigned_to` since AAP Section 0.5.6 enumerates
        the field-level-ACL-required fields as `assigned_group` and
        `assigned_agent` on the case table only - the case_task
        table's per-field protection is delegated to the table-level
        "Assigned only" condition).
      - default_value (empty): no automatic assignee assignment. The
        task creator (case_manager or case_agent) explicitly picks the
        responsible user at insert time. AAP does not specify a
        default assignee.
      - audit=false: per AAP Section 0.3.1 minimal-change clause and
        consistent with the sibling Reference / DateTime / Choice /
        String fields in this same dictionary set (only the `status`
        field on x_[scope]_case carries audit=true since it is the
        most important field for state-machine forensics). Per-task
        assignee changes are logged through the standard
        sys_history_set / sys_audit infrastructure on demand but do
        not trigger the per-field audit overhead by default. The
        agent prompt's Phase 4 explicitly directs `audit=false` for
        this field.
      - max_length=32: the standard ServiceNow Reference-field width.
        The dictionary stores the 32-character lowercase-hex sys_id of
        the referenced sys_user row as the actual column value; the
        platform's auto-generated form picker, list view, and report
        builder all dereference to the user's display column (name)
        for human-readable display via the OOB sys_user dictionary's
        display=true column. The agent prompt's Phase 3 verbatim
        specifies "max_length=32 because reference fields store
        32-char sys_id values internally".
      - choice=0: this is a Reference field, NOT a Choice field. The
        sibling sys_choice_* records under ../choices/ apply only to
        the `type`, `status`, `priority`, `pending_reason`,
        `case_task.type`, `case_task.status`, and `case_party.party_type`
        columns - none are needed here.
      - choice_field, choice_table empty: same reason as choice=0
        above.
      - reference=sys_user: OOB ServiceNow user table. AAP Section
        0.5.7 specifies this exact target table by name. No scoped
        wrapper or facade is needed; tasks reference users directly
        across the scoped/global boundary, which ServiceNow permits
        for OOB tables (the reverse direction - global tables
        referencing scoped tables - would require a Cross-Scope
        Privilege record, but is not needed for this POC).
      - reference_cascade_rule (empty): default platform behavior,
        which is "do nothing on referenced-record deletion." If a
        user is deleted (a rare global-admin operation), tasks retain
        the orphaned reference; this is acceptable for the POC since
        user deletion is gated by global ACLs not modified by this
        scoped application (per AAP Section 0.3.2). AAP does not
        specify a cascade rule. The empty element is functionally
        equivalent to "none" and matches what the agent prompt's
        Phase 3 specifies for THIS field.
      - reference_qual, reference_qual_condition (empty): no filter on
        which users may be selected. ANY active sys_user is eligible
        as an assignee at the picker level. AAP does not require
        filtering by user role, group membership, active status, or
        any other criterion. (One could envision a future-state
        qualifier preventing assignment to inactive users, e.g.,
        `<reference_qual>active=true</reference_qual>`, but that is
        OUT OF SCOPE per AAP Section 0.3.1's MINIMAL CHANGE CLAUSE.
        The agent prompt's Key Insight #5 explicitly notes: "If a
        future enhancement wants to restrict assignment to active
        users only, add `<reference_qual>active=true</reference_qual>`.
        AAP doesn't require this.")
      - use_reference_qualifier=simple: standard ServiceNow setting
        when no advanced (scripted) reference qualifier is in use.
      - dynamic_ref_qual (empty): no dynamic reference qualifier.
      - reference_floor, reference_key, reference_type (empty):
        standard defaults for a basic table-to-table reference; no
        advanced reference semantics (typeahead override, reference
        floor table, document reference, etc.) are needed here.
      - element_reference=false: this is a TABLE reference, not an
        ELEMENT reference (which would point at a specific dictionary
        column on another table). AAP specifies a row-level reference
        target (a user as a whole, not a particular column on that
        user's record).
      - table_reference=false: this is NOT a "Document ID" / "Table"
        polymorphic reference (which is what `glide_var` style fields
        on the OOB task table use to reference any-table-any-row). It
        is a fixed-target reference to sys_user only.
      - text_index=false: Reference fields are not full-text-indexed.
        Searches by user are performed via GlideRecord addJoinQuery
        against sys_user on its sys_id column; full-text indexing of
        the 32-char sys_id has no value.
      - unique=false: a single user is correctly responsible for many
        tasks (that is the entire point of agent-based task routing -
        a case_agent's "My Overdue Tasks" workspace is meant to display
        many tasks with the agent's sys_id in this column), so
        uniqueness on this column would be semantically wrong and
        would break AAP Section 0.7.4's minimum demo-data thresholds
        which require "at least one open and one closed task per demo
        case" - implying many tasks share a single assignee.
      - virtual=false: this is a stored column, not a calculated /
        virtual derivation. The actual sys_id of the chosen sys_user
        row is persisted on every task record (in contrast to
        ArkCase's free-form String pattern that re-resolved the
        assignee at every access).
      - spell_check=false: Reference fields hold a 32-char sys_id and
        the platform renders the dereferenced display value at view
        time; spell-check is meaningless for the persisted value and
        would be misapplied to the dereferenced human-name display.
      - No PII: the field stores a 32-char sys_id pointer to a user
        record; the user record itself stores categorical
        organizational identity (synthetic user_name, fabricated
        display name, fabricated email at the demo seed level only)
        per AAP Section 0.7.2 ("synthetic only"). The seed users at
        ../seed-data/users/sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_*.xml are
        fabricated synthetic accounts (one per role: case_manager,
        case_agent, case_viewer); no real names, real email
        addresses, or PII derived from the source ArkCase database
        are placed in this column at any point in the build.

    Cross-references (AAP Section 0.5.2 dependency ordering):
      - This record MUST load AFTER:
          * ../tables/x_[scope]_case_task.xml (parent table; `<name>`
            here references the scoped task table by name; the
            platform requires the table to exist before its dictionary
            entries can be created)
          * sys_user (OOB; always present on every PDI; never modified
            by this Update Set per AAP Section 0.3.2 "No global ACLs
            ... No global business rules, no global script includes,
            no global UI policies")
      - This record MUST load BEFORE the consumers that read or write
        the `assigned_to` column on x_[scope]_case_task:
          * ../reports/x_[scope]_my_overdue_tasks.xml (the Agent
            Workspace dashboard's overdue-tasks list widget; filters
            by `due_date < javascript:gs.daysAgoStart(0) AND status
            != Closed AND assigned_to = javascript:gs.getUserID()`)
          * ../dashboards/pa_dashboards_x_[scope]_agent_workspace.xml
            (the Agent Workspace dashboard that surfaces the overdue-
            tasks report widget)
          * ../acl/x_[scope]_case_task_*.xml (table-level ACLs on the
            case_task table; the case_agent "Assigned only" condition
            uses `current.assigned_to == gs.getUserID()` as one half
            of the access check, with the other half dot-walking
            `current.case.assigned_agent` / `current.case.assigned_group`
            via the sibling `case` reference field)
          * ../seed-data/users/sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_*.xml (the
            synthetic demo users - one per role - that the demo tasks
            will reference; this dictionary entry must precede the
            seed users for the preview engine to reconcile the field
            schema)
          * ../seed-data/tasks/x_[scope]_case_task_demo_*.xml
            (synthetic demo tasks that populate this field by lookup
            of the demo user's `user_name` attribute via the
            seed_demo_data.js script - never via hard-coded sys_id,
            per AAP Section 0.7.2 the no-hardcoded-sys_id constraint
            applies to flows, ACL conditions, scripts, seed data, UI
            Policies, UI Actions, Business Rules, and client scripts)
          * ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js (the idempotent seed script
            that creates the demo task rows; for each demo task it
            performs:
                var userGr = new GlideRecord('sys_user');
                userGr.addQuery('user_name', '<demo-user-name>');
                userGr.query();
                if (userGr.next()) { taskGr.assigned_to = userGr.sys_id; }
            to resolve the assignee sys_id at seed time, never via
            hard-coded literals)
-->
<record_update table="sys_dictionary">
    <sys_dictionary action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <array>false</array>
        <attributes/>
        <audit>false</audit>
        <calculation/>
        <choice>0</choice>
        <choice_field/>
        <choice_table/>
        <column_label>Assigned To</column_label>
        <comments>Mandatory reference to sys_user - the user responsible for this task. Filter for the My Overdue Tasks report (../reports/x_[scope]_my_overdue_tasks.xml) on the Agent Workspace dashboard, which queries assigned_to = javascript:gs.getUserID() AND due_date &lt; javascript:gs.daysAgoStart(0) AND status != Closed. Used by case_agent "Assigned only" ACL conditions on x_[scope]_case_task as one half of the access check (current.assigned_to == gs.getUserID()), with the other half dot-walking current.case.assigned_agent / current.case.assigned_group. Replaces ArkCase AcmTask.assignee (String username, resolved at runtime via OpenLDAP id; the target uses a proper foreign key to sys_user). Cascade rule is empty (default "no cascade" - deleting a sys_user does NOT auto-cascade-delete tasks; manual cleanup or reassignment of orphaned tasks is acceptable).</comments>
        <create_roles/>
        <default_value/>
        <defaultsort/>
        <delete_roles/>
        <dependent/>
        <dependent_on_field/>
        <display>true</display>
        <dynamic_creation>false</dynamic_creation>
        <dynamic_creation_script/>
        <dynamic_default_value/>
        <dynamic_ref_qual/>
        <element>assigned_to</element>
        <element_reference>false</element_reference>
        <foreign_database/>
        <function_definition/>
        <function_field>false</function_field>
        <internal_type>reference</internal_type>
        <mandatory>true</mandatory>
        <max_length>32</max_length>
        <name>x_[scope]_case_task</name>
        <next_element/>
        <primary>false</primary>
        <read_only>false</read_only>
        <read_roles/>
        <reference>sys_user</reference>
        <reference_cascade_rule/>
        <reference_floor/>
        <reference_key/>
        <reference_qual/>
        <reference_qual_condition/>
        <reference_type/>
        <sizeclass/>
        <spell_check>false</spell_check>
        <staged>false</staged>
        <sys_class_name>sys_dictionary</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>388df21ea3ca149d70916144f84ecf42</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name/>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_[scope]_case_management">x_[scope]_case_management</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_[scope]_case_management</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_dictionary_x_[scope]_case_task_assigned_to</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <table_reference>false</table_reference>
        <text_index>false</text_index>
        <unique>false</unique>
        <use_dependent_field>false</use_dependent_field>
        <use_dynamic_default>false</use_dynamic_default>
        <use_reference_qualifier>simple</use_reference_qualifier>
        <virtual>false</virtual>
        <virtual_type/>
        <widget/>
        <write_roles/>
        <xml_view>false</xml_view>
    </sys_dictionary>
</record_update>
