<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the `sys_dictionary` row that
    declares the `case` Reference field on the `x_casemgmt_case_task` custom
    table inside the scoped application `x_casemgmt`.

    Per AAP Section 0.5.7 (Data-Model Mapping verbatim) for x_casemgmt_case_task:

        Field         Type                          Constraints
        case          Reference -> x_casemgmt_case   Mandatory

    THIS FIELD IS THE PARENT LINKAGE that ties every case-task row back to
    its parent case. It is the single most important field on the entire
    case_task table - without it, a task is an orphan with no semantic
    connection to any case, and the "all tasks must be closed before
    resolving" gate (AAP Section 0.5.5) becomes inoperable. Every other
    field on x_casemgmt_case_task (subject, type, status, assigned_to,
    due_date) describes properties of the task; only `case` describes
    WHICH case the task belongs to.

    Critical behaviors that depend on this field (AAP Sections 0.4.1,
    0.5.5, 0.5.6, 0.5.7):

      1. STATE-MACHINE "ALL TASKS CLOSED" GATE FOR Resolved TRANSITION
         (../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml,
          ../script_includes/x_casemgmt_CaseTransitionValidator.xml)
         Per AAP Section 0.5.5 verbatim:
            From         To        Required condition
            In Progress  Resolved  All linked x_casemgmt_case_task records
                                   have status = Closed
         The validator subflow and Script Include both perform the exact
         GlideRecord query specified in the agent prompt:
            new GlideRecord('x_casemgmt_case_task')
              .addQuery('case', current.sys_id)
              .addQuery('status', '!=', 'Closed')
              .query();
         If even one row is returned, the subflow throws a blocking
         form-level error with the literal text:
            "All tasks must be closed before resolving this case."
         (AAP Section 0.7.4 verbatim "Case-resolution-blocking rule
         wording"). The query above WILL NOT WORK without this dictionary
         entry; the field name `case` declared here is the column the
         GlideRecord query targets, and the reference target
         `x_casemgmt_case` is what makes `addQuery('case', current.sys_id)`
         resolve correctly when the parent case's sys_id is passed as
         the right-hand-side filter value.

      2. RELATED-LIST RENDERING ON THE CASE FORM
         (parent table ../tables/x_casemgmt_case.xml automatic form layout
          per AAP Section 0.4.4 "Internal user UI" requirements)
         When a user opens a case record, ServiceNow's auto-generated
         form layout includes a Related List for x_casemgmt_case_task
         filtered by `case = current.sys_id`. This relationship is
         materialized SOLELY through this dictionary entry's `<reference>`
         element pointing at `x_casemgmt_case` - the platform's reverse-
         relationship engine inspects every reference field on every
         child table and synthesizes an inbound related list on the
         parent. Without `<reference>x_casemgmt_case</reference>` set
         here, the case form would have no Related List of tasks, and
         the AAP Section 0.4.4 internal-UI requirement ("configures
         Related Lists on the case form for both `case_task` (parent =
         current case) and `case_party` (parent = current case)") would
         fail.

      3. ACL "ASSIGNED ONLY" CASCADE FOR CASE_AGENT
         (../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_*.xml)
         Per AAP Section 0.5.6: case_agent has "Assigned only" CRUD
         access. For tasks, "Assigned only" propagates THROUGH this
         field: a case_agent may read/write a task ONLY IF the parent
         case (resolved by `current.case`) satisfies the case-level
         "Assigned only" condition (assigned_agent = current user OR
         assigned_group contains current user). The ACL condition
         scripts on x_casemgmt_case_task therefore traverse this
         reference to evaluate authorization:
            current.case.assigned_agent == gs.getUserID()
              || gs.getUser().isMemberOf(current.case.assigned_group.toString())
         This dot-walk chain (`current.case.assigned_agent`,
         `current.case.assigned_group`) requires that this dictionary
         entry's `<reference>` correctly target `x_casemgmt_case` so the
         platform can dereference the parent case's columns at ACL
         evaluation time.

      4. SEED-DATA POPULATION VIA NUMBER LOOKUP
         (../seed-data/tasks/x_casemgmt_case_task_demo_*.xml,
          ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js)
         Per AAP Section 0.5.2 reference-resolution rules: "Case
         references (e.g., on case_task.case, case_party.case, demo
         task/party seed) -> look up x_casemgmt_case by `number`." The
         seed-data XMLs and the idempotent seed_demo_data.js script
         resolve the parent-case sys_id at seed time via:
            var caseGr = new GlideRecord('x_casemgmt_case');
            caseGr.addQuery('number', 'CASE0000001');
            caseGr.query();
            if (caseGr.next()) { task.case = caseGr.sys_id; }
         There are NO hard-coded sys_id literals in any seed file
         pointing into this column - all references resolve by the
         human-readable case number, per AAP Section 0.7.2 "no
         hardcoded sys_id constraint" applied to seed data.

      5. CASCADE-DELETE BEHAVIOR (INTENTIONALLY DISABLED)
         (this dictionary entry's `<reference_cascade_rule>` element)
         Per the agent prompt's "reference_cascade_rule=none" instruction
         and AAP Section 0.7.4 minimum demo-data thresholds: when a
         parent case is deleted, the platform DOES NOT auto-cascade-
         delete its child tasks. This is the POC-safe default for two
         reasons:
           * In the POC scenario, manual cleanup of orphaned tasks is
             acceptable and surfaces operator awareness; silent cascade
             deletion of dozens of child tasks would be a destructive
             action with no audit signal.
           * AAP Section 0.5.5 makes Closed cases TERMINAL ("Closed
             cases are terminal and cannot be modified") which already
             precludes deletion of cases that have business meaning;
             only Draft cases without tasks would realistically be
             deleted, and those have no children to cascade against.
         The "none" value (synonymous with empty / "no action") matches
         AAP Section 0.3.1's MINIMAL CHANGE CLAUSE - if the AAP wanted
         cascade-delete semantics, it would have said so. Note the
         sibling reference fields x_casemgmt_case.assigned_group and
         x_casemgmt_case.assigned_agent use empty `<reference_cascade_rule/>`
         which is functionally equivalent; this entry uses the explicit
         "none" literal per the agent prompt's explicit-over-implicit
         instruction for THIS field.

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only, NOT byte-for-byte ported):
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-task-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/task/model/AcmTask.java line 72-74:
            private String attachedToObjectType;
            private String attachedToObjectName;
            private Long   attachedToObjectId;
        ArkCase's AcmTask used a POLYMORPHIC PARENT LINKAGE composed of
        three separate columns:
          * attachedToObjectType - String discriminator naming the parent
            object type (e.g., "CASE_FILE", "COMPLAINT", "REQUEST",
            "DOCUMENT_REPOSITORY"). This was a free-form String column
            with no platform-level enum/check constraint.
          * attachedToObjectName - human-readable display name of the
            parent (cached/denormalized to avoid runtime joins).
          * attachedToObjectId - Long sys_id pointer to the parent row,
            interpreted in the context of attachedToObjectType to know
            which physical table to join against.
        This pattern allowed a single `acm_task` row to attach to ANY
        ArkCase entity - a CaseFile, a Complaint matter, a FOIA request,
        a Document Repository folder, etc. The trade-off was that the
        DBMS could not enforce referential integrity (no foreign key was
        possible because the target table varied), and every join
        required the application layer to first read attachedToObjectType
        and then route to the correct DAO.

        The ServiceNow target COLLAPSES this polymorphism into a single
        fixed-target reference for three reasons (AAP Section 0.1.2,
        AAP Section 0.5.7):
          * AAP Section 0.3.2 declares the FOIA portal, the document
            repository, the complaint matters as separate entities, and
            every other ArkCase parent type OUT OF SCOPE. The POC's
            entire universe of "things a task can attach to" is one
            table: x_casemgmt_case. Polymorphism without multiple
            attach-target types is dead weight.
          * Referential integrity: a single fixed-target reference field
            on the ServiceNow platform is enforced by the reference
            picker (only existing rows in the target table are
            selectable) and by the dictionary's `<reference>` element
            (the platform resolves cross-table references at query time
            and rejects writes that point at a deleted target).
          * Dot-walk dereferencing: ACL conditions and form layouts can
            traverse `current.case.assigned_group` only if the column
            type is a reference, not a polymorphic String+Long pair.
        The collapse is therefore a semantic SIMPLIFICATION, not a loss
        of functionality, in the context of this specific POC's scope.
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-task-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/task/model/AcmTask.java line 61:
            implements AcmAssignedObject, Serializable, AcmLegacySystemEntity,
                       AcmParentObjectInfo, AcmNotifiableEntity, AcmStatefulEntity
        The AcmParentObjectInfo interface was the contract that surfaced
        the attachedToObjectType + attachedToObjectId pair to the rest
        of ArkCase's plugin ecosystem. In the ServiceNow target, this
        interface contract has no analogue - the case_task table simply
        carries a `case` reference column, and the platform's reference
        engine handles every consumer use case (related-list rendering,
        form picker, dot-walk ACL conditions, GlideRecord queries) with
        no Java interface needed.
      - The field name is `case` (lowercase, 4 chars, no underscore;
        NOT `case_id`, NOT `parent_case`, NOT `parent`, NOT
        `attached_to`, NOT `case_file`) per AAP Section 0.5.7 verbatim.
        This deliberately matches the parallel field name on the sibling
        x_casemgmt_case_party table (which also uses `case` as its parent
        linkage, declared in ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_party_case.xml)
        for naming consistency across the three-table data model. The
        single-word `case` is also consistent with how the parent flows
        and Script Includes refer to the column in their inline scripts
        (e.g., `addQuery('case', current.sys_id)`).

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.7.1, 0.7.2):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: `<name>` resolves to
        `x_casemgmt_case_task` within the scoped application, and
        `<sys_scope>` / `<sys_package>` bind THIS dictionary record to
        the same scope by `source` attribute lookup. The `<reference>`
        element resolves to the SCOPED `x_casemgmt_case` table by name
        (NOT by sys_id), preserving zero-hardcoded-sys_id compliance and
        keeping the entire parent-child relationship inside the scope
        boundary. NO global-scope writes occur.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_ids: the `<sys_scope>`,
        `<sys_package>`, and `<reference>` text-node values resolve by
        scope source name and table name respectively, not by literal
        sys_id. The `<sys_id>` text-node value is THIS record's own
        deterministic primary key (MD5 of the canonical field identifier
        `x_casemgmt_case_task.case` = 25cae07ed16e95fd89a4c8013152ecc2)
        and is NOT a reference to any other record. Per AAP Section
        0.7.2 this scheme guarantees that a fresh PDI re-import of the
        Update Set produces byte-identical sys_id values, which is
        necessary for round-trip-verify
        (../scripts/round_trip_verify.md) zero-error preview.
      - The concrete scope identifier `casemgmt` is used per AAP convention. ServiceNow Update Set imports use a standard XML parser, so the scope id must be concrete in the XML before export.
      - mandatory=true at the dictionary level: AAP Section 0.5.7
        verbatim declares the `case` field on x_casemgmt_case_task as
        Mandatory with no qualifying suffix (in contrast to
        x_casemgmt_case.assigned_group which says "Mandatory on Open
        transition" - a transition-level constraint NOT enforced at the
        dictionary level). For case_task.case, mandatoriness is
        absolute: a task without a parent case is semantically
        meaningless (the entire raison d'etre of the case_task table
        is to subdivide work on a case), and the platform's mandatory
        flag enforces the constraint at every entry point - manual
        save in the form, GlideRecord.insert() from server-side
        scripts, and Table API POST. There is NO submission path in
        this scoped application that legitimately creates a task
        without a parent case (no portal-anonymous task creation, no
        bulk-import of headless tasks, etc.), so a hard mandatory flag
        produces zero false-positive rejections.
      - read_only=false: case_manager and case_agent both edit this
        field directly when creating tasks under a case. The
        auto-generated New Task form on the case's Related List
        pre-populates the `case` reference with the parent case's
        sys_id, but the field remains user-editable in case the user
        opens the standalone task list and chooses to associate the
        new task with a different case. Field-level write access is
        governed by the table-level ACLs at
        ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_*.xml (no separate field-level ACL
        is needed for `case` since AAP Section 0.5.6 enumerates the
        field-level-ACL-required fields as `assigned_group` and
        `assigned_agent` on the case table only).
      - default_value (empty): no automatic parent-case assignment.
        The platform's Related-List "New" button provides a contextual
        default at form-creation time (it pre-populates `case` with the
        parent case's sys_id), but that is a UX-layer convenience, not
        a dictionary-level default. AAP does not specify a default.
      - audit=false: per AAP Section 0.3.1 minimal-change clause and
        consistent with the sibling Reference / DateTime / Choice
        / String fields in this same dictionary set. The `case` field's
        value is set once at task creation and almost never changes
        thereafter (in the POC scenario, you do not "move" a task from
        one case to another; you close it and create a new one). Audit
        on this field would inflate sys_audit storage with low-value
        entries.
      - max_length=32: the standard ServiceNow Reference-field width.
        The dictionary stores the 32-character lowercase-hex sys_id of
        the referenced x_casemgmt_case row as the actual column value;
        the platform's auto-generated form picker, list view, and
        report builder all dereference to the case's display column
        (which is x_casemgmt_case.number per the AAP-prescribed
        CASE0000001 auto-numbering format) for human-readable display.
      - choice=0: this is a Reference field, NOT a Choice field. The
        sibling sys_choice_* records under ../choices/ apply only to
        the `type`, `status`, `priority`, `pending_reason`,
        `case_task.type`, `case_task.status`, and `case_party.party_type`
        columns - none are needed here.
      - choice_field, choice_table empty: same reason as choice=0
        above.
      - reference=x_casemgmt_case: the SCOPED parent table (NOT an OOB
        ServiceNow table; NOT the OOB `task` table even though the AcmTask
        source has the word "task" in it - see the parent table comment
        block at ../tables/x_casemgmt_case_task.xml for the rationale).
        AAP Section 0.5.7 specifies this exact target table by name.
      - reference_cascade_rule=none: per the agent prompt's explicit
        "reference_cascade_rule=none" instruction. Functionally
        equivalent to empty / no_action; means deleting a parent case
        does NOT auto-cascade-delete its child tasks. The POC default
        prefers explicit "none" over the implicit empty value to
        document the intent inside the Update Set XML for any future
        maintainer who reads it. AAP does not specify a cascade rule
        but the POC-safe default is "do nothing on referenced-record
        deletion" - manual cleanup of orphaned tasks is acceptable and
        surfaces operator awareness rather than silent destructive
        cascade.
      - reference_qual, reference_qual_condition (empty): no filter
        on which cases may be selected as the parent. Any active
        x_casemgmt_case row is eligible. AAP does not require filtering
        by case status, type, priority, or any other criterion. (One
        could envision a future-state qualifier preventing tasks from
        being attached to Closed cases, but that is OUT OF SCOPE per
        AAP Section 0.3.1's MINIMAL CHANGE CLAUSE - the AAP-specified
        ../business_rules/x_casemgmt_block_terminal_closed.xml already
        prevents Closed-case modification, which transitively prevents
        new tasks from being added.)
      - use_reference_qualifier=simple: standard ServiceNow setting
        when no advanced (scripted) reference qualifier is in use.
      - dynamic_ref_qual (empty): no dynamic reference qualifier.
      - reference_floor, reference_key, reference_type (empty):
        standard defaults for a basic table-to-table reference; no
        advanced reference semantics (typeahead override, reference
        floor table, document reference, etc.) are needed here.
      - element_reference=false: this is a TABLE reference, not an
        ELEMENT reference (which would point at a specific dictionary
        column on another table). AAP specifies a row-level reference
        target (a parent case as a whole, not a particular column on
        that case).
      - table_reference=false: this is NOT a "Document ID" / "Table"
        polymorphic reference (which is what the OOB `task` table uses
        for its reference field that can point at any table). It is a
        FIXED-TARGET reference to x_casemgmt_case only. This is
        precisely the simplification being applied: ArkCase's AcmTask
        had a polymorphic parent linkage (attachedToObjectType +
        attachedToObjectId) - the ServiceNow target's case_task.case is
        a fixed-target reference, eliminating the polymorphism per AAP
        Section 0.1.2 ("the polymorphism is collapsed").
      - text_index=false: Reference fields are not full-text-indexed.
        Searches by parent case are performed via GlideRecord
        addJoinQuery against x_casemgmt_case on its sys_id column; full-
        text indexing of the 32-char sys_id has no value.
      - unique=false: a single case is correctly the parent of MANY
        tasks (that is the entire point of the parent-child relationship -
        a case is decomposed into tasks for resolution). AAP Section
        0.7.4 minimum demo-data thresholds explicitly require "at least
        one open and one closed task per demo case in 'In Progress' or
        'Pending' state, to exercise the 'all-tasks-closed' gate" -
        which mandates non-uniqueness. Uniqueness on this column would
        be semantically wrong and would break AAP's seed-data plan.
      - virtual=false: this is a stored column, not a calculated /
        virtual derivation. The actual sys_id of the chosen
        x_casemgmt_case row is persisted on every task record.
      - spell_check=false: Reference fields hold a 32-char sys_id and
        the platform renders the dereferenced display value at view
        time; spell-check is meaningless for the persisted value and
        would be misapplied to the dereferenced human-readable case
        number (CASE0000001) display.
      - No PII: the field stores a 32-char sys_id pointer to a
        x_casemgmt_case row; the case row itself stores synthetic
        requester data (per AAP Section 0.7.2 "synthetic only"). The
        seed cases at ../seed-data/cases/x_casemgmt_case_demo_*.xml are
        fabricated - no real names, no real email addresses, no real
        case content - so no PII is present in any case sys_id pointed
        at by any task's `case` column.

    Cross-references (AAP Section 0.5.2 dependency ordering):
      - This record MUST load AFTER:
          * ../tables/x_casemgmt_case_task.xml (parent table; `<name>`
            here references the scoped task table by name; the platform
            requires the table to exist before its dictionary entries
            can be created)
          * ../tables/x_casemgmt_case.xml (target of the reference;
            `<reference>` resolves to the scoped case table by name; the
            platform requires the referenced table to exist before a
            reference field can be declared against it; AAP Section
            0.5.2 explicitly states "Reference fields before referencing
            tables" - paraphrased: the referenced TABLE must exist
            before the reference FIELD)
      - This record MUST load BEFORE the consumers that read or write
        the `case` column on x_casemgmt_case_task:
          * ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_task_subject.xml,
            ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_task_type.xml,
            ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_task_status.xml,
            ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_task_assigned_to.xml,
            ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_task_due_date.xml (the other
            five fields on the case_task table; ordering among the
            six dictionary entries is not strictly required by the
            platform but for clarity this entry should be among the
            first since it is the parent linkage)
          * ../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml (the
            "all tasks closed" gate; the subflow performs:
                addQuery('case', current.sys_id)
                  .addQuery('status', '!=', 'Closed')
            and throws "All tasks must be closed before resolving this
            case." if any rows are returned)
          * ../flows/general_inquiry_state_machine.xml (the parent flow
            for type=General Inquiry that calls
            validate_resolved_transition)
          * ../flows/complaint_state_machine.xml (the parent flow for
            type=Complaint that calls validate_resolved_transition)
          * ../script_includes/x_casemgmt_CaseTransitionValidator.xml
            (canTransitionToResolved static method that queries
            x_casemgmt_case_task on this field; called by both the flows
            and any business rules that need the same gate)
          * ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_task_*.xml (table-level ACLs on the
            case_task table; the case_agent "Assigned only" condition
            dot-walks current.case.assigned_agent and
            current.case.assigned_group via this reference field)
          * ../seed-data/tasks/x_casemgmt_case_task_demo_*.xml (synthetic
            demo tasks that populate this field by lookup of the parent
            case's `number` attribute via the seed_demo_data.js script -
            never via hard-coded sys_id, per AAP Section 0.7.2 the
            no-hardcoded-sys_id constraint applies to flows, ACL
            conditions, scripts, seed data, UI Policies, UI Actions,
            Business Rules, and client scripts)
          * ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js (the idempotent seed script
            that creates the demo task rows; for each demo task it
            performs:
                var caseGr = new GlideRecord('x_casemgmt_case');
                caseGr.addQuery('number', '<demo-case-number>');
                caseGr.query();
                if (caseGr.next()) { taskGr.case = caseGr.sys_id; }
            to resolve the parent-case sys_id at seed time, never via
            hard-coded literals)
-->
<record_update table="sys_dictionary">
    <sys_dictionary action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <array>false</array>
        <attributes/>
        <audit>false</audit>
        <calculation/>
        <choice>0</choice>
        <choice_field/>
        <choice_table/>
        <column_label>Case</column_label>
        <comments>Mandatory reference to the parent case (x_casemgmt_case). Queried by the case state-machine flow's "all tasks closed" guard for the In Progress -&gt; Resolved transition (../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml, ../script_includes/x_casemgmt_CaseTransitionValidator.xml) via addQuery('case', current.sys_id).addQuery('status', '!=', 'Closed') - if any rows are returned the flow throws the literal blocking error "All tasks must be closed before resolving this case." (AAP Section 0.7.4 verbatim). Replaces ArkCase AcmTask.attachedToObjectId/attachedToObjectType polymorphic parent linkage; in this POC the parent is always a x_casemgmt_case row, so the polymorphism is collapsed into a single fixed-target reference. Used by case_agent "Assigned only" ACL conditions on x_casemgmt_case_task via dot-walk current.case.assigned_agent / current.case.assigned_group. Cascade rule is "none" - deleting a parent case does NOT auto-cascade-delete its child tasks (POC-safe default; manual cleanup required).</comments>
        <create_roles/>
        <default_value/>
        <defaultsort/>
        <delete_roles/>
        <dependent/>
        <dependent_on_field/>
        <display>true</display>
        <dynamic_creation>false</dynamic_creation>
        <dynamic_creation_script/>
        <dynamic_default_value/>
        <dynamic_ref_qual/>
        <element>case</element>
        <element_reference>false</element_reference>
        <foreign_database/>
        <function_definition/>
        <function_field>false</function_field>
        <internal_type>reference</internal_type>
        <mandatory>true</mandatory>
        <max_length>32</max_length>
        <name>x_casemgmt_case_task</name>
        <next_element/>
        <primary>false</primary>
        <read_only>false</read_only>
        <read_roles/>
        <reference>x_casemgmt_case</reference>
        <reference_cascade_rule>none</reference_cascade_rule>
        <reference_floor/>
        <reference_key/>
        <reference_qual/>
        <reference_qual_condition/>
        <reference_type/>
        <sizeclass/>
        <spell_check>false</spell_check>
        <staged>false</staged>
        <sys_class_name>sys_dictionary</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>25cae07ed16e95fd89a4c8013152ecc2</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name/>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_casemgmt">x_casemgmt</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_casemgmt</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_dictionary_x_casemgmt_case_task_case</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <table_reference>false</table_reference>
        <text_index>false</text_index>
        <unique>false</unique>
        <use_dependent_field>false</use_dependent_field>
        <use_dynamic_default>false</use_dynamic_default>
        <use_reference_qualifier>simple</use_reference_qualifier>
        <virtual>false</virtual>
        <virtual_type/>
        <widget/>
        <write_roles/>
        <xml_view>false</xml_view>
    </sys_dictionary>
</record_update>
