<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the `sys_dictionary` row that
    declares the `case` Reference field on the `x_casemgmt_case_party` custom
    table inside the scoped application `x_casemgmt`.

    Per AAP Section 0.5.7 (Data-Model Mapping verbatim) for x_casemgmt_case_party:

        Field     Type                          Constraints
        case      Reference -> x_casemgmt_case   Mandatory

    THIS FIELD IS THE PARENT LINKAGE that ties every case-party row back to
    its parent case. It is the cornerstone of the AAP's "Polymorphic
    association via single-table choice + UI Policy" pattern (AAP Section
    0.4.3) - without it, a party row is a free-floating Person+Organization
    association with no semantic anchor to any case, and the polymorphic
    party-table model collapses into meaningless data. Every other field on
    x_casemgmt_case_party (party_type, person, organization, role_label)
    describes WHAT KIND of party association exists; only `case` describes
    WHICH case the party is associated to.

    Critical behaviors that depend on this field (AAP Sections 0.4.3, 0.4.4,
    0.5.6, 0.5.7):

      1. RELATED-LIST RENDERING ON THE CASE FORM
         (parent table ../tables/x_casemgmt_case.xml automatic form layout
          per AAP Section 0.4.4 "Internal user UI" requirements)
         When a user opens a case record, ServiceNow's auto-generated form
         layout includes a Related List for x_casemgmt_case_party filtered
         by `case = current.sys_id`. AAP Section 0.4.4 explicitly requires:
         "configures Related Lists on the case form for both `case_task`
         (parent = current case) and `case_party` (parent = current case)".
         This relationship is materialized SOLELY through this dictionary
         entry's `<reference>` element pointing at `x_casemgmt_case` - the
         platform's reverse-relationship engine inspects every reference
         field on every child table and synthesizes an inbound related
         list on the parent. Without `<reference>x_casemgmt_case</reference>`
         set here, the case form would have no Related List of parties,
         and the AAP-mandated case-people / case-organizations rendering
         (semantic-equivalent of ArkCase's Cases.PeopleController and
         Cases.OrganizationsController AngularJS controllers in
         acm-standard-applications/arkcase/src/main/webapp/resources/
         modules/cases/services/) would have no data source.

      2. ACL "ASSIGNED ONLY" CASCADE FOR CASE_AGENT
         (../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_*.xml)
         Per AAP Section 0.5.6: case_agent has "Assigned only" CRUD access.
         For parties, "Assigned only" propagates THROUGH this field: a
         case_agent may read/write a party row ONLY IF the parent case
         (resolved by `current.case`) satisfies the case-level "Assigned
         only" condition (assigned_agent = current user OR assigned_group
         contains current user). The ACL condition scripts on
         x_casemgmt_case_party therefore traverse this reference to evaluate
         authorization:
            current.case.assigned_agent == gs.getUserID()
              || gs.getUser().isMemberOf(current.case.assigned_group.toString())
         This dot-walk chain (`current.case.assigned_agent`,
         `current.case.assigned_group`) requires that this dictionary
         entry's `<reference>` correctly target `x_casemgmt_case` so the
         platform can dereference the parent case's columns at ACL
         evaluation time. The same pattern applies to the sibling
         x_casemgmt_case_task table via ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_task_case.xml.

      3. CONDITIONAL FIELD VISIBILITY VIA party_type CHOICE
         (../ui_policy/x_casemgmt_case_party_conditional_fields.xml)
         The polymorphism collapse pattern (AAP Section 0.4.3) makes
         x_casemgmt_case_party.party_type the discriminator that decides
         whether the `person` field (Reference -> sys_user) or the
         `organization` field (Reference -> core_company) is visible and
         required. The UI Policy at the path above enforces the conditional
         visibility. This `case` field is OUTSIDE the polymorphism - it is
         ALWAYS visible and ALWAYS mandatory, regardless of party_type,
         because the parent-case linkage is universal across both Person
         and Organization parties. AAP Section 0.5.7's constraint column
         is simply "Mandatory" with no qualifier - in contrast to
         x_casemgmt_case_party.person ("Conditional: required if
         party_type = Person") and x_casemgmt_case_party.organization
         ("Conditional: required if party_type = Organization") which DO
         carry conditional qualifiers.

      4. SEED-DATA POPULATION VIA NUMBER LOOKUP
         (../seed-data/parties/x_casemgmt_case_party_demo_*.xml,
          ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js)
         Per AAP Section 0.5.2 reference-resolution rules: "Case
         references (e.g., on case_task.case, case_party.case, demo
         task/party seed) -> look up x_casemgmt_case by `number`." The
         seed-data XMLs and the idempotent seed_demo_data.js script
         resolve the parent-case sys_id at seed time via:
            var caseGr = new GlideRecord('x_casemgmt_case');
            caseGr.addQuery('number', 'CASE0000001');
            caseGr.query();
            if (caseGr.next()) { partyGr.case = caseGr.sys_id; }
         There are NO hard-coded sys_id literals in any seed file
         pointing into this column - all references resolve by the
         human-readable case number, per AAP Section 0.7.2 "no
         hardcoded sys_id constraint" applied to seed data. AAP
         Section 0.7.4 minimum demo-data thresholds explicitly require
         "at least one Person and one Organization party per demo case
         to exercise the polymorphic UI policy" - which mandates that
         multiple party rows resolve to the SAME parent-case sys_id
         via this column.

      5. CASCADE-DELETE BEHAVIOR (INTENTIONALLY DISABLED)
         (this dictionary entry's `<reference_cascade_rule>` element)
         Per the agent prompt's "reference_cascade_rule=none" instruction
         and AAP Section 0.7.4 minimum demo-data thresholds: when a
         parent case is deleted, the platform DOES NOT auto-cascade-
         delete its child parties. This is the POC-safe default for two
         reasons:
           * In the POC scenario, manual cleanup of orphaned parties is
             acceptable and surfaces operator awareness; silent cascade
             deletion of dozens of child parties (especially
             organization-typed ones that might be cross-referenced
             elsewhere in the corporate graph) would be a destructive
             action with no audit signal.
           * AAP Section 0.5.5 makes Closed cases TERMINAL ("Closed
             cases are terminal and cannot be modified") which already
             precludes deletion of cases that have business meaning;
             only Draft cases without parties would realistically be
             deleted, and those have no children to cascade against.
         The "none" value (synonymous with empty / "no action") matches
         AAP Section 0.3.1's MINIMAL CHANGE CLAUSE - if the AAP wanted
         cascade-delete semantics, it would have said so. The sibling
         x_casemgmt_case_task_case.xml also uses "none" for the same
         reason; this consistency simplifies the POC's mental model.

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only, NOT byte-for-byte ported):
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-person-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/person/model/PersonAssociation.java
        lines 90-100:
            @Column(name = "cm_person_assoc_parent_id")
            private Long parentId;

            @Column(name = "cm_person_assoc_person_type", nullable = false)
            private String personType;

            @Column(name = "cm_person_assoc_parent_type")
            private String parentType;

            @Column(name = "cm_person_assoc_parent_title")
            private String parentTitle;
        ArkCase's PersonAssociation used a POLYMORPHIC PARENT LINKAGE
        composed of three separate columns (mirroring AcmTask's pattern):
          * parentId - Long sys_id pointer to the parent row, interpreted
            in the context of parentType to know which physical table to
            join against. No platform-level foreign key constraint was
            possible because the target table varied.
          * parentType - String discriminator naming the parent object
            type (e.g., "CASE_FILE", "COMPLAINT", "DOCUMENT_REPOSITORY").
            Free-form String column with no enum constraint.
          * parentTitle - cached/denormalized human-readable display name
            of the parent (to avoid runtime joins on the parent table for
            list-view rendering).
        This pattern allowed a single `acm_person_assoc` row to attach to
        ANY ArkCase entity - a CaseFile, a Complaint matter, a FOIA
        request, a Document Repository folder, etc. Combined with the
        cm_class_name discriminator at lines 71-72:
            @DiscriminatorColumn(name = "cm_class_name", ...)
            @DiscriminatorValue("com.armedia.acm.plugins.person.model.PersonAssociation")
        the table additionally distinguished PersonAssociation rows from
        PersonOrganizationAssociation rows (the latter being a sibling
        @Entity stored in a separate physical table acm_person_org_assoc
        with its own parentId/parentType - see
        ../tables/x_casemgmt_case_party.xml for the complete two-entity
        collapse rationale).

        The ServiceNow target COLLAPSES this polymorphism into a single
        fixed-target reference for three reasons (AAP Sections 0.1.2,
        0.4.3, 0.5.7):
          * AAP Section 0.3.2 declares the FOIA portal, the document
            repository, the complaint matters as separate entities, and
            every other ArkCase parent type OUT OF SCOPE. The POC's
            entire universe of "things a party can attach to" is one
            table: x_casemgmt_case. Polymorphism without multiple
            attach-target types is dead weight.
          * Referential integrity: a single fixed-target reference field
            on the ServiceNow platform is enforced by the reference
            picker (only existing rows in the target table are
            selectable) and by the dictionary's `<reference>` element
            (the platform resolves cross-table references at query time
            and rejects writes that point at a deleted target).
          * Dot-walk dereferencing: ACL conditions and form layouts can
            traverse `current.case.assigned_group` only if the column
            type is a reference, not a polymorphic String+Long pair.
        The collapse is therefore a semantic SIMPLIFICATION, not a loss
        of functionality, in the context of this specific POC's scope.
        Note that the parentTitle denormalization is also dropped - the
        ServiceNow platform's reference field machinery automatically
        renders the dereferenced display column (x_casemgmt_case.number,
        format CASE0000001) at view time, eliminating the need for a
        cached title column.

      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-person-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/person/model/PersonOrganizationAssociation.java
        is the SIBLING JPA entity that ArkCase used for organization
        associations (mapped to acm_person_org_assoc). Its parent linkage
        followed the same parentId/parentType pattern as PersonAssociation.
        Both entities collapse INTO THIS SINGLE TABLE x_casemgmt_case_party
        per AAP Section 0.4.3 - and BOTH inherit the same `case` reference
        field declared by THIS dictionary entry. The discrimination between
        person-type associations and organization-type associations is now
        carried by the `party_type` Choice field
        (../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_party_party_type.xml), not by
        separate physical tables. This dictionary entry is therefore
        agnostic to party_type - whether the row represents a Person party
        or an Organization party, it always has exactly one `case`
        reference back to its parent case.

      - The field name is `case` (lowercase, 4 chars, no underscore;
        NOT `case_id`, NOT `parent_case`, NOT `parent`, NOT
        `parent_object`, NOT `case_file`) per AAP Section 0.5.7 verbatim.
        This deliberately matches the parallel field name on the sibling
        x_casemgmt_case_task table (which also uses `case` as its parent
        linkage, declared in ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_task_case.xml)
        for naming consistency across the three-table data model. The
        single-word `case` is also consistent with how the parent flows
        and Script Includes refer to the column in their inline scripts
        (e.g., `addQuery('case', current.sys_id)`).

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.7.1, 0.7.2):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: `<name>` resolves to
        `x_casemgmt_case_party` within the scoped application, and
        `<sys_scope>` / `<sys_package>` bind THIS dictionary record to
        the same scope by `source` attribute lookup. The `<reference>`
        element resolves to the SCOPED `x_casemgmt_case` table by name
        (NOT by sys_id), preserving zero-hardcoded-sys_id compliance and
        keeping the entire parent-child relationship inside the scope
        boundary. NO global-scope writes occur.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_ids: the `<sys_scope>`,
        `<sys_package>`, and `<reference>` text-node values resolve by
        scope source name and table name respectively, not by literal
        sys_id. The `<sys_id>` text-node value is THIS record's own
        deterministic primary key (MD5 of the canonical field identifier
        `x_casemgmt_case_party.case` = fbd5378ac5055b3db843042ff20777b5)
        and is NOT a reference to any other record. Per AAP Section
        0.7.2 this scheme guarantees that a fresh PDI re-import of the
        Update Set produces byte-identical sys_id values, which is
        necessary for round-trip-verify
        (../scripts/round_trip_verify.md) zero-error preview.
      - The concrete scope identifier `casemgmt` is used per AAP convention. ServiceNow Update Set imports use a standard XML parser, so the scope id must be concrete in the XML before export.
      - mandatory=true at the dictionary level: AAP Section 0.5.7
        verbatim declares the `case` field on x_casemgmt_case_party as
        Mandatory with no qualifying suffix (in contrast to
        x_casemgmt_case_party.person which says "Conditional: required
        if party_type = Person" - a polymorphism-level constraint
        enforced via UI Policy, not at the dictionary level). For
        case_party.case, mandatoriness is absolute: a party without a
        parent case is semantically meaningless (the entire raison
        d'etre of the case_party table is to enumerate the people and
        organizations associated with a case), and the platform's
        mandatory flag enforces the constraint at every entry point -
        manual save in the form, GlideRecord.insert() from server-side
        scripts, and Table API POST. There is NO submission path in
        this scoped application that legitimately creates a party
        without a parent case (no portal-anonymous party creation, no
        bulk-import of headless parties, etc.), so a hard mandatory
        flag produces zero false-positive rejections.
      - read_only=false: case_manager and case_agent both edit this
        field directly when associating parties to a case. The
        auto-generated New Party form on the case's Related List
        pre-populates the `case` reference with the parent case's
        sys_id, but the field remains user-editable in case the user
        opens the standalone party list and chooses to associate the
        new party with a different case. Field-level write access is
        governed by the table-level ACLs at
        ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_*.xml (no separate field-level ACL
        is needed for `case` since AAP Section 0.5.6 enumerates the
        field-level-ACL-required fields as `assigned_group` and
        `assigned_agent` on the case table only).
      - default_value (empty): no automatic parent-case assignment.
        The platform's Related-List "New" button provides a contextual
        default at form-creation time (it pre-populates `case` with the
        parent case's sys_id), but that is a UX-layer convenience, not
        a dictionary-level default. AAP does not specify a default.
      - audit=false: per AAP Section 0.3.1 minimal-change clause and
        consistent with the sibling Reference / DateTime / Choice
        / String fields in this same dictionary set. The `case` field's
        value is set once at party creation and almost never changes
        thereafter (in the POC scenario, you do not "move" a party
        from one case to another; you delete it and create a new
        association under the correct case). Audit on this field would
        inflate sys_audit storage with low-value entries.
      - max_length=32: the standard ServiceNow Reference-field width.
        The dictionary stores the 32-character lowercase-hex sys_id of
        the referenced x_casemgmt_case row as the actual column value;
        the platform's auto-generated form picker, list view, and
        report builder all dereference to the case's display column
        (which is x_casemgmt_case.number per the AAP-prescribed
        CASE0000001 auto-numbering format) for human-readable display.
      - choice=0: this is a Reference field, NOT a Choice field. The
        sibling sys_choice_* records under ../choices/ apply only to
        the `type`, `status`, `priority`, `pending_reason`,
        `case_task.type`, `case_task.status`, and `case_party.party_type`
        columns - none are needed here. Note that `case_party.party_type`
        IS a Choice field (Person / Organization) but THIS field
        (`case_party.case`) is a Reference, not a Choice.
      - choice_field, choice_table empty: same reason as choice=0
        above.
      - reference=x_casemgmt_case: the SCOPED parent table (NOT an OOB
        ServiceNow table; NOT the OOB `task` table; NOT the OOB
        `incident` table). AAP Section 0.5.7 specifies this exact
        target table by name. The platform resolves the table-name
        cross-reference at Update Set import time by querying
        sys_db_object.name, which is why ../tables/x_casemgmt_case.xml
        MUST be loaded BEFORE this dictionary entry per AAP Section
        0.5.2 ("Reference fields before referencing tables").
      - reference_cascade_rule=none: per the agent prompt's explicit
        "reference_cascade_rule=none" instruction. Functionally
        equivalent to empty / no_action; means deleting a parent case
        does NOT auto-cascade-delete its child parties. The POC default
        prefers explicit "none" over the implicit empty value to
        document the intent inside the Update Set XML for any future
        maintainer who reads it. AAP does not specify a cascade rule
        but the POC-safe default is "do nothing on referenced-record
        deletion" - manual cleanup of orphaned parties is acceptable
        and surfaces operator awareness rather than silent destructive
        cascade. The sibling x_casemgmt_case_task_case.xml uses the
        same "none" value for consistency across the three-table data
        model.
      - reference_qual, reference_qual_condition (empty): no filter
        on which cases may be selected as the parent. Any active
        x_casemgmt_case row is eligible. AAP does not require filtering
        by case status, type, priority, or any other criterion. (One
        could envision a future-state qualifier preventing parties
        from being attached to Closed cases, but that is OUT OF SCOPE
        per AAP Section 0.3.1's MINIMAL CHANGE CLAUSE - the AAP-specified
        ../business_rules/x_casemgmt_block_terminal_closed.xml already
        prevents Closed-case modification, which transitively prevents
        new parties from being added.)
      - use_reference_qualifier=simple: standard ServiceNow setting
        when no advanced (scripted) reference qualifier is in use.
      - dynamic_ref_qual (empty): no dynamic reference qualifier.
      - reference_floor, reference_key, reference_type (empty):
        standard defaults for a basic table-to-table reference; no
        advanced reference semantics (typeahead override, reference
        floor table, document reference, etc.) are needed here.
      - element_reference=false: this is a TABLE reference, not an
        ELEMENT reference (which would point at a specific dictionary
        column on another table). AAP specifies a row-level reference
        target (a parent case as a whole, not a particular column on
        that case).
      - table_reference=false: this is NOT a "Document ID" / "Table"
        polymorphic reference (which is what the OOB `task` table uses
        for its reference field that can point at any table). It is a
        FIXED-TARGET reference to x_casemgmt_case only. This is
        precisely the simplification being applied: ArkCase's
        PersonAssociation had a polymorphic parent linkage
        (parentId + parentType + cm_class_name discriminator) - the
        ServiceNow target's case_party.case is a fixed-target
        reference, eliminating the polymorphism per AAP Section 0.1.2
        ("the polymorphism is collapsed").
      - text_index=false: Reference fields are not full-text-indexed.
        Searches by parent case are performed via GlideRecord
        addJoinQuery against x_casemgmt_case on its sys_id column;
        full-text indexing of the 32-char sys_id has no value.
      - unique=false: a single case is correctly the parent of MANY
        parties (that is the entire point of the parent-child
        relationship - a case can have multiple Persons AND multiple
        Organizations associated, each in different roles such as
        Requester, Respondent, Witness per AAP Section 0.5.7's
        role_label example). AAP Section 0.7.4 minimum demo-data
        thresholds explicitly require "at least one Person and one
        Organization party per demo case to exercise the polymorphic
        UI policy" - which mandates non-uniqueness on the `case`
        column (multiple party rows must be allowed to point at the
        same case). Uniqueness on this column would be semantically
        wrong and would break AAP's seed-data plan.
      - virtual=false: this is a stored column, not a calculated /
        virtual derivation. The actual sys_id of the chosen
        x_casemgmt_case row is persisted on every party record.
      - spell_check=false: Reference fields hold a 32-char sys_id and
        the platform renders the dereferenced display value at view
        time; spell-check is meaningless for the persisted value and
        would be misapplied to the dereferenced human-readable case
        number (CASE0000001) display.
      - No PII: the field stores a 32-char sys_id pointer to a
        x_casemgmt_case row; the case row itself stores synthetic
        requester data (per AAP Section 0.7.2 "synthetic only"). The
        seed cases at ../seed-data/cases/x_casemgmt_case_demo_*.xml
        are fabricated - no real names, no real email addresses, no
        real case content - so no PII is present in any case sys_id
        pointed at by any party's `case` column.

    Cross-references (AAP Section 0.5.2 dependency ordering):
      - This record MUST load AFTER:
          * ../tables/x_casemgmt_case_party.xml (parent table; `<name>`
            here references the scoped party table by name; the platform
            requires the table to exist before its dictionary entries
            can be created)
          * ../tables/x_casemgmt_case.xml (target of the reference;
            `<reference>` resolves to the scoped case table by name; the
            platform requires the referenced table to exist before a
            reference field can be declared against it; AAP Section
            0.5.2 explicitly states "Reference fields before referencing
            tables" - paraphrased: the referenced TABLE must exist
            before the reference FIELD)
      - This record MUST load BEFORE the consumers that read or write
        the `case` column on x_casemgmt_case_party:
          * ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_party_party_type.xml,
            ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_party_person.xml,
            ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_party_organization.xml,
            ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_party_role_label.xml (the
            other four fields on the case_party table; ordering among
            the five dictionary entries is not strictly required by the
            platform but for clarity this entry should be among the
            first since it is the parent linkage)
          * ../ui_policy/x_casemgmt_case_party_conditional_fields.xml
            (the polymorphism UI Policy that enforces conditional
            visibility/requiredness of the `person` and `organization`
            fields based on `party_type`; the policy's condition
            scripts reference fields on this table including `case`,
            though the conditional logic itself targets party_type)
          * ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_*.xml (table-level ACLs on the
            case_party table; the case_agent "Assigned only" condition
            dot-walks current.case.assigned_agent and
            current.case.assigned_group via this reference field)
          * ../seed-data/parties/x_casemgmt_case_party_demo_*.xml
            (synthetic demo parties that populate this field by lookup
            of the parent case's `number` attribute via the
            seed_demo_data.js script - never via hard-coded sys_id, per
            AAP Section 0.7.2 the no-hardcoded-sys_id constraint
            applies to flows, ACL conditions, scripts, seed data, UI
            Policies, UI Actions, Business Rules, and client scripts)
          * ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js (the idempotent seed script
            that creates the demo party rows; for each demo party it
            performs:
                var caseGr = new GlideRecord('x_casemgmt_case');
                caseGr.addQuery('number', '<demo-case-number>');
                caseGr.query();
                if (caseGr.next()) { partyGr.case = caseGr.sys_id; }
            to resolve the parent-case sys_id at seed time, never via
            hard-coded literals)
-->
<record_update table="sys_dictionary">
    <sys_dictionary action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <array>false</array>
        <attributes/>
        <audit>false</audit>
        <calculation/>
        <choice>0</choice>
        <choice_field/>
        <choice_table/>
        <column_label>Case</column_label>
        <comments>Mandatory reference to the parent case (x_casemgmt_case). The single most important field on the x_casemgmt_case_party table - it ties every party row (Person or Organization) back to its parent case. Replaces ArkCase PersonAssociation.parentId/parentType/parentTitle polymorphic parent linkage (and the equivalent on PersonOrganizationAssociation); in this POC the parent is always a x_casemgmt_case row, so the polymorphism is collapsed into a single fixed-target reference. Powers the case-form Related List rendering (AAP Section 0.4.4) so that case parties show under the case form. Used by case_agent "Assigned only" ACL conditions on x_casemgmt_case_party via dot-walk current.case.assigned_agent / current.case.assigned_group (AAP Section 0.5.6). Cascade rule is "none" - deleting a parent case does NOT auto-cascade-delete its child parties (POC-safe default; manual cleanup required). Seed data resolves the parent-case sys_id by lookup of x_casemgmt_case.number via ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js (no hardcoded sys_ids, per AAP Section 0.7.2).</comments>
        <create_roles/>
        <default_value/>
        <defaultsort/>
        <delete_roles/>
        <dependent/>
        <dependent_on_field/>
        <display>true</display>
        <dynamic_creation>false</dynamic_creation>
        <dynamic_creation_script/>
        <dynamic_default_value/>
        <dynamic_ref_qual/>
        <element>case</element>
        <element_reference>false</element_reference>
        <foreign_database/>
        <function_definition/>
        <function_field>false</function_field>
        <internal_type>reference</internal_type>
        <mandatory>true</mandatory>
        <max_length>32</max_length>
        <name>x_casemgmt_case_party</name>
        <next_element/>
        <primary>false</primary>
        <read_only>false</read_only>
        <read_roles/>
        <reference>x_casemgmt_case</reference>
        <reference_cascade_rule>none</reference_cascade_rule>
        <reference_floor/>
        <reference_key/>
        <reference_qual/>
        <reference_qual_condition/>
        <reference_type/>
        <sizeclass/>
        <spell_check>false</spell_check>
        <staged>false</staged>
        <sys_class_name>sys_dictionary</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>fbd5378ac5055b3db843042ff20777b5</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name/>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_casemgmt">x_casemgmt</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_casemgmt</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_dictionary_x_casemgmt_case_party_case</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <table_reference>false</table_reference>
        <text_index>false</text_index>
        <unique>false</unique>
        <use_dependent_field>false</use_dependent_field>
        <use_dynamic_default>false</use_dynamic_default>
        <use_reference_qualifier>simple</use_reference_qualifier>
        <virtual>false</virtual>
        <virtual_type/>
        <widget/>
        <write_roles/>
        <xml_view>false</xml_view>
    </sys_dictionary>
</record_update>
