<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    ServiceNow Update Set record-definition for the `sys_dictionary` row that
    declares the `party_type` Choice field on the `x_casemgmt_case_party`
    custom table inside the scoped application `x_casemgmt`.

    Per AAP Section 0.5.7 (Data-Model Mapping verbatim) for x_casemgmt_case_party:

        Field        Type     Constraints
        party_type   Choice   Person, Organization

    Per AAP Section 0.4.1 (Refactored Structure Planning):
        choices/sys_choice_case_party_party_type.xml -> Person, Organization

    Per AAP Section 0.4.3 (Design Pattern Applications):
        "Polymorphic association via single-table choice + UI Policy -
         case_party collapses ArkCase's two association tables
         (acm_person_assoc, acm_person_org_assoc) into one ServiceNow table
         with a Choice discriminator (party_type) and a UI Policy that
         conditionally shows person (reference -> sys_user) or organization
         (reference -> core_company)."

    THIS DICTIONARY ENTRY ONLY DECLARES THAT THE `party_type` CHOICE FIELD
    EXISTS ON THE PARENT TABLE. The choice values themselves (Person,
    Organization) are authored as separate sys_choice records in
    ../choices/sys_choice_case_party_party_type.xml. This separation is a
    deliberate consequence of the ServiceNow Choice-field design pattern: a
    sys_dictionary row declares the column shape; sibling sys_choice rows
    declare the allowed string-label values keyed by `name` + `element`
    lookup against this entry. The set of two labels (Person, Organization)
    is intentionally minimal and authoritative for the entire POC; per AAP
    Section 0.5.7 verbatim, no third party_type is supported and the field
    explicitly does NOT carry the "extensible" qualifier that some other
    Choice fields (e.g., x_casemgmt_case.type per its "General Inquiry,
    Complaint - extensible" annotation in AAP Section 0.5.7) carry. New
    party types beyond Person and Organization are out of POC scope per AAP
    Section 0.3.2.

    THIS FIELD IS THE DISCRIMINATOR FOR THE POLYMORPHISM COLLAPSE. Per AAP
    Section 0.1.2 verbatim: "The case_party polymorphic conditional fields
    (person shown when party_type = Person; organization shown when
    party_type = Organization) are implemented via UI Policies on the form."
    The conditional visibility logic lives in
    ../ui_policy/x_casemgmt_case_party_conditional_fields.xml - NOT in this
    dictionary entry. THIS entry only DECLARES that party_type is a Choice
    field; the UI Policy READS the chosen value at runtime to drive show/hide
    of the sibling reference fields.

    OPERATIONAL ROLE OF THE `party_type` FIELD ON CASE_PARTY ROWS:
      - Acts as the run-time switch between two mutually exclusive sub-shapes
        of a party row:
          * party_type = Person       -> the `person` reference field
                                         (Reference -> sys_user) is required
                                         and visible; `organization` is
                                         hidden and ignored.
          * party_type = Organization -> the `organization` reference field
                                         (Reference -> core_company) is
                                         required and visible; `person` is
                                         hidden and ignored.
        This conditional pairing is the entire purpose of collapsing
        ArkCase's two physical tables (acm_person_assoc and
        acm_person_org_assoc) into ONE ServiceNow table - and party_type
        is the sole field that makes the collapse semantically lossless.
      - Surfaces on the auto-generated x_casemgmt_case_party list view per
        AAP Section 0.4.4 ("Internal user UI" requires "ServiceNow's
        automatic native list and form views for the three custom tables")
        as a categorical column letting an operator scan parties by type
        at-a-glance ("Person" vs "Organization") without dereferencing
        each row.
      - Surfaces on the auto-generated form layout when a user opens an
        individual party record. The user picks Person or Organization
        FIRST, and the UI Policy then reveals exactly one of the two
        reference fields beneath it. Without an explicit choice the form
        cannot finish rendering its conditional sub-section, which is why
        mandatory=true is enforced at the dictionary level.
      - Surfaces in the parent case's Related List of parties (rendered
        via the `case` reference field declared in
        ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_party_case.xml). The Party Type
        column appears beside the role_label so that an internal user
        reviewing a case sees what KIND of association each row
        represents (Person vs Organization) without opening each party
        individually. AAP Section 0.7.4 minimum demo-data thresholds
        explicitly require "at least one Person and one Organization
        party per demo case to exercise the polymorphic UI policy" -
        which, by definition, exercises this column on every demo case.
      - Powers the seed-data scripts at
        ../seed-data/parties/x_casemgmt_case_party_demo_*.xml and
        ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js: every fabricated party row sets
        party_type to either "Person" or "Organization" via
        GlideRecord.setValue('party_type', ...) and then sets either
        person or organization (but NEVER both) accordingly. The seed
        data thus exercises both polymorphism branches and the UI Policy
        rendering on every demo case.
      - Is INTENTIONALLY a Choice (controlled vocabulary), not a free-form
        String. Free-form String values would defeat the discriminator
        intent: a typo like "person" (lowercase) or "Persons" (plural) or
        "Organisation" (British spelling) would break the UI Policy's
        equality test and leave both reference fields hidden. The
        Choice-field configuration (`<choice>3</choice>`) plus the sibling
        sys_choice records guarantee exact-match semantics for the two
        supported labels.

    Semantic source-side reference (read-only, NOT byte-for-byte ported):
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-person-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/person/model/PersonAssociation.java
        lines 69-72:
            @Entity
            @Table(name = "acm_person_assoc")
            @Inheritance(strategy = InheritanceType.SINGLE_TABLE)
            @DiscriminatorColumn(name = "cm_class_name",
                                 discriminatorType = DiscriminatorType.STRING)
            @DiscriminatorValue("com.armedia.acm.plugins.person.model.PersonAssociation")
        ArkCase used JPA single-table inheritance with a string-typed
        discriminator column `cm_class_name` carrying the fully-qualified
        Java class name of the row's runtime type. PersonAssociation rows
        carried discriminator value
        "com.armedia.acm.plugins.person.model.PersonAssociation"; sibling
        Person subtypes carried their own class names. The discriminator
        was a class-name string that was NEVER exposed to end users; it
        was a JPA persistence concern only.
      - acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-person-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/person/model/PersonOrganizationAssociation.java
        lines 64-68 used the SAME @DiscriminatorColumn(name = "cm_class_name")
        annotation but on a DIFFERENT physical table (acm_person_org_assoc)
        with its own row population. So ArkCase actually had TWO tables
        each with internal sub-typing, not one table with a
        person-vs-organization discriminator.
      - The ServiceNow target REPLACES this ArkCase pattern with a HUMAN-
        READABLE DISCRIMINATOR per AAP Section 0.1.2 ("Transformation rule
        for inheritance and polymorphism. ArkCase's JPA single-table
        inheritance with discriminator (cm_class_name) on PersonAssociation
        / OrganizationAssociation is collapsed into one table
        (x_casemgmt_case_party) with a Choice field (party_type) plus
        conditional reference fields (person -> sys_user, organization ->
        core_company)."). The transformation is two-fold:
          * cm_class_name (Java FQN string) -> party_type (human Choice
            "Person" / "Organization"). The end-user sees the chosen value;
            it drives both the form-layer UI Policy and the user's mental
            model.
          * Two physical tables (acm_person_assoc, acm_person_org_assoc) ->
            ONE physical table (x_casemgmt_case_party) per AAP Section 0.4.3
            collapse pattern. The two are no longer distinguished by table
            identity; they are distinguished by THIS field's value.
        This is a deliberate DOWNGRADE of ArkCase's polymorphic richness in
        exchange for ServiceNow-native clarity: there are no plugin sub-
        types, no class-name discriminators, no separate physical tables -
        just one column with two allowed string labels. AAP Section 0.3.2
        marks every other ArkCase party-type variant (e.g., the ZyLAB
        matter-witness association, the FOIA portal-requester association)
        as out of scope, so the collapse is functionally complete for the
        POC's universe.
      - The field name is `party_type` (lowercase, snake_case, two words
        joined by underscore; NOT `partyType`, NOT `type`, NOT
        `party_kind`, NOT `class_name`, NOT `discriminator`) per AAP
        Section 0.5.7 verbatim. The intentional naming difference from
        x_casemgmt_case.type and x_casemgmt_case_task.type (which both use
        bare `type`) is to make absolutely clear that this column is the
        polymorphism discriminator, NOT a categorical descriptor in the
        same sense as case.type or case_task.type. AAP Section 0.5.7
        spells it `party_type` precisely to emphasize the semantic
        difference.
      - The label "Party Type" (Title Case, two words separated by space)
        per the agent prompt's Phase 2 verbatim. The two-word label
        matches the two-word internal name and reads naturally as a form
        field label and list column header.

    Constraints honored (AAP Sections 0.5.7, 0.7.1, 0.7.2, 0.7.4):
      - Scope-namespace exclusivity: `<name>` resolves to
        `x_casemgmt_case_party` within the scoped application, and
        `<sys_scope>` / `<sys_package>` bind THIS dictionary record to
        the same scope by `source` attribute lookup. NO global-scope
        writes - the OOB tables `task`, `incident`, `sys_user`, etc.
        are never modified by this dictionary entry or any other
        artifact in the Update Set. The concrete scope identifier `casemgmt` is used per AAP convention; ServiceNow Update Set imports use a standard XML parser, so the scope id is concrete in the XML before export.
      - Zero hardcoded cross-reference sys_ids: the `<sys_scope>` and
        `<sys_package>` text-node values resolve by scope source name
        (`x_casemgmt`), not by literal sys_id. The
        `<sys_id>` text-node value is THIS record's own deterministic
        primary key (MD5 of the canonical field identifier
        `x_casemgmt_case_party.party_type`) and is NOT a reference to any
        other record. The MD5 derivation guarantees that re-generation
        of this Update Set on any agent run produces a byte-identical
        `<sys_id>` (no random UUIDs), which is required for clean
        Update-Set re-import on a fresh PDI without creating duplicate
        sys_dictionary rows. The same derivation pattern is used by
        every sys_dictionary record in this Update Set (e.g.,
        x_casemgmt_case_party.case      -> fbd5378ac5055b3db843042ff20777b5,
        x_casemgmt_case_task.type       -> 180d00dda06c4b93e4c2c106b621d153,
        x_casemgmt_case_task.status     -> af19c46ec8457885c75512edec980172,
        x_casemgmt_case.type            -> 9a49190f6a6b8f2b4100073c53631168,
        x_casemgmt_case.status          -> 5f0be2eaed29d45b1d63d64e876d22c4,
        x_casemgmt_case.priority        -> 7584a06a06745f24e42efb27f0ae5975).
      - mandatory=true at the dictionary level. AAP Section 0.5.7 verbatim
        marks party_type as Mandatory (the "Choice | Person, Organization"
        constraint column carries no qualifier - it is unconditionally
        required for every row). The polymorphism strategy in AAP Section
        0.4.3 makes this requirement absolute: a row with party_type=null
        cannot drive the UI Policy correctly (the UI Policy condition
        `party_type == 'Person'` evaluates false on null, and the parallel
        condition `party_type == 'Organization'` also evaluates false on
        null - so BOTH reference fields would be hidden, leaving the row
        in an indeterminate state with no visible content). The platform's
        mandatory-flag enforcement runs at every entry point: the
        auto-generated form (where the user sees a red asterisk and
        cannot save without choosing), the Table API (which rejects
        POST/PATCH bodies that omit party_type), the GlideRecord.insert()
        path used by ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js (which throws if the
        field is unset), and the scripted REST endpoints (none of which
        touch case_party in this POC, but the same enforcement would
        apply if they did).
      - read_only=false: case_manager and case_agent (the latter only
        within their "Assigned only" cases per AAP Section 0.5.6) MAY
        edit party_type after initial creation - for example, to correct
        a row erroneously created as "Person" when the actual associate
        is an organization. The read_only=false setting permits the
        write through the standard form, the Table API, and the seed
        scripts. Note that changing party_type after creation will
        ALSO require clearing the no-longer-applicable reference field
        (e.g., changing Person -> Organization requires clearing the
        person reference and setting the organization reference) - the
        UI Policy at ../ui_policy/x_casemgmt_case_party_conditional_fields.xml
        handles this by hiding (and on save, optionally clearing) the
        non-applicable reference field. Field-level write authorization
        is governed by the table-level ACLs in
        ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_*.xml; AAP Section 0.5.6 does NOT
        list party_type among the field-level-ACL-required fields (only
        case.assigned_group and case.assigned_agent carry field-level
        ACLs).
      - default_value is EMPTY (no implicit default). Even though
        "Person" might seem like a sensible default (most case parties
        are likely individuals), AAP Section 0.5.7 does NOT specify a
        default, and forcing the user to choose makes the polymorphic
        intent EXPLICIT. A silent default to Person would silently
        commit type-misclassified rows when an operator forgot to
        consider whether the associate was actually an organization;
        making the user pick prevents that class of data-quality bug.
        This is intentionally STRICTER than x_casemgmt_case.status (which
        defaults to "Draft" per AAP Section 0.4.1) and
        x_casemgmt_case_task.status (which defaults to "Open" per AAP
        Section 0.4.1) - those defaults reflect status-machine starting
        states, whereas party_type is a polymorphism discriminator with
        no semantic "starting state".
      - audit=false per AAP Section 0.3.1 minimal-change clause and the
        agent prompt's Phase 4. Party-type changes are descriptive
        metadata corrections, not regulated lifecycle events. The
        standard sys_* audit columns at the table level (sys_created_on,
        sys_created_by, sys_updated_on, sys_updated_by) capture record-
        level changes; per-field audit on party_type is unnecessary
        overhead for a POC.
      - max_length=40 per the agent prompt's Phase 3 verbatim. The
        longest defined label is "Organization" (12 characters) and the
        shortest is "Person" (6 characters). The 40-character ceiling
        accommodates extensible future labels without a schema migration
        even though no extension is currently planned per AAP Section
        0.3.2 ("any modules, workflows, portal pages, tables, or
        integrations beyond the defined scope" are out of scope - which
        includes new party types). The same 40-character ceiling is
        used on every Choice field in this Update Set (case.type,
        case.status, case.priority, case.pending_reason,
        case_task.type, case_task.status) for consistency.
      - choice=3 = "Choice list, no description column" per the agent
        prompt's Phase 3 verbatim. This is the standard Choice-field
        configuration when a sibling sys_choice record set defines the
        allowed values; the form renderer presents the field as a
        select dropdown sourced from the matching sys_choice rows.
        choice=0 (free-form String) would defeat the purpose of
        constraining the field to a controlled vocabulary; choice=1
        (Choice list with description) would impose a description
        column that AAP Section 0.5.7 does not specify; choice=2
        (Suggestion list) would let users input arbitrary strings
        adjacent to the suggested ones, contradicting the intent and
        breaking the UI Policy's equality tests for "Person" / "Organization".
      - internal_type=string: ServiceNow Choice fields are STORED as
        their underlying type (string for label-based choices, integer
        for integer-keyed choices). The "Choice" semantics come from
        `<choice>3</choice>`, NOT from internal_type. Setting
        internal_type=choice would be incorrect - that internal type
        does not exist in the platform's dictionary type registry. The
        actual value persisted in the column is the string label
        ("Person" or "Organization") chosen by the user.
      - choice_field, choice_table empty: the choice values are sourced
        from sibling sys_choice rows keyed by `name`+`element` lookup,
        not by an alternate field-level override (choice_field) and not
        by lookup against another table (choice_table). Same pattern as
        the other Choice fields in this Update Set.
      - unique=false: multiple parties with the same party_type are
        explicitly permitted, both within a single case (per AAP
        Section 0.7.4 "at least one Person and one Organization party
        per demo case" - which means each demo case has at least one
        party_type=Person row AND at least one party_type=Organization
        row, but a real case might have multiple Person parties such
        as a Requester, a Witness, and a Respondent simultaneously) and
        across cases. Uniqueness is not a meaningful concept for a
        polymorphism-discriminator Choice field.
      - text_index=false per the agent prompt's Phase 6 verbatim. A
        Choice field with two labels does not benefit from a text
        index; users navigate party_type via the Choice dropdown and
        list-view filters, not free-form full-text search.
      - spell_check=false per the agent prompt's Phase 6 verbatim. A
        controlled Choice vocabulary is by definition correctly spelled;
        spell_check on a Choice field would produce false positives on
        label tokens that the platform dictionary might not recognize
        (e.g., the word "Organization" with American spelling vs the
        platform's potentially British-flavored dictionary).
      - No reference target: this is a String-backed Choice field, NOT
        a Reference field. All `<reference*>` elements are empty and
        `<table_reference>false</table_reference>`. The field does NOT
        reference an external lookup table; the choice values live as
        sys_choice rows keyed by element name. (Note that the SIBLING
        fields person and organization, declared in
        ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_party_person.xml and
        ../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_party_organization.xml respectively,
        ARE Reference fields - but party_type itself is not.)
      - element_reference=false: this is not an element-level reference
        either. AAP specifies a Choice column at the row level, not a
        column-level reference into another dictionary entry's choices.
      - dependent (empty): the platform's "Dependent" mechanism is for
        cascading Choice fields (where the available values of field B
        depend on the chosen value of field A in the same record). For
        case_party, the polymorphism-conditional behavior is implemented
        via UI Policy (../ui_policy/x_casemgmt_case_party_conditional_fields.xml),
        NOT via Dependent Choice. UI Policies operate at the form-render
        layer (showing/hiding fields, marking required) whereas Dependent
        Choice operates at the data layer (filtering available choices).
        AAP Section 0.4.3 explicitly designates "UI Policies on the form"
        as the polymorphism implementation mechanism - so dependent /
        dependent_on_field are EMPTY here. The UI Policy reads party_type
        and toggles person and organization independently; party_type
        itself is not dependent on any other field.
      - virtual=false: this is a stored column, not a calculated /
        virtual derivation. The actual chosen string label ("Person" or
        "Organization") is persisted on every party record and queried
        directly by the UI Policy and by reports.
      - No PII: the field stores only categorical labels chosen from a
        controlled two-element vocabulary; no real names, email
        addresses, organizational identifiers, or any source-side
        ArkCase production data are derived from or stored in this
        column at any point in the build (per AAP Section 0.3.2
        synthetic-data-only constraint). The vocabulary itself
        ("Person", "Organization") contains no PII either - they are
        generic English nouns.

    Cross-references (AAP Section 0.5.2 dependency ordering):
      - This record MUST load AFTER:
          * ../tables/x_casemgmt_case_party.xml (parent table; the
            `<name>x_casemgmt_case_party</name>` element below references
            the table by name, and the table must exist before any of
            its dictionary entries can be attached)
          * ../app/sys_app/x_casemgmt_case_management.xml and
            ../app/sys_scope/x_casemgmt.xml (scoped application records;
            <sys_scope> and <sys_package> resolve against them by source
            name)
      - This record MUST load BEFORE:
          * ../choices/sys_choice_case_party_party_type.xml (the choice
            values Person, Organization which reference this dictionary
            entry by `name` + `element` lookup against the strings
            `x_casemgmt_case_party` and `party_type`. The two sys_choice
            rows would fail to install if this dictionary entry were
            absent because their name/element foreign-keys would resolve
            to nothing.)
          * ../ui_policy/x_casemgmt_case_party_conditional_fields.xml
            (the UI Policy that drives conditional visibility of the
            person and organization fields based on the value of
            party_type. The UI Policy's condition uses the column name
            `party_type` and would be undefined without this dictionary
            entry. The UI Policy's actions read THIS field's chosen
            value at every form render.)
          * ../seed-data/parties/x_casemgmt_case_party_demo_*.xml (every
            demo party row must specify party_type; the seed data
            would fail to insert if this dictionary record were absent
            because GlideRecord.setValue('party_type', ...) would have
            no target column. AAP Section 0.7.4 mandates "at least one
            Person and one Organization party per demo case" - which by
            definition exercises this column on every demo case.)
          * ../scripts/seed_demo_data.js (the idempotent server-side
            seed script writes synthetic party_type labels via
            GlideRecord.setValue('party_type', ...) for both branches
            of the polymorphism)
          * ../acl/x_casemgmt_case_party_*.xml (table-level ACLs on the
            case_party table; the ACLs reference this column indirectly
            via list-view filters rendered in the auto-generated UI,
            though the table-level ACL conditions themselves do not
            dot-walk through party_type)

    Source for the deterministic sys_id derivation:
        echo -n "x_casemgmt_case_party.party_type" | md5sum
        => 5e02afdbd2f05f407e986015e93d1238

    The MD5 input is the canonical field identifier <name>.<element>,
    matching the same derivation pattern used across all other
    sys_dictionary records in this Update Set.

    Critical naming notes carried forward to
    ../choices/sys_choice_case_party_party_type.xml:
        The two labels are EXACTLY "Person" (capitalized P, 6 chars) and
        "Organization" (capitalized O, American spelling, 12 chars). NOT
        "person" (lowercase), NOT "Persons" (plural), NOT "Organisation"
        (British spelling), NOT "Org" (abbreviated). AAP Section 0.5.7
        verbatim spells the labels "Person, Organization". The Update Set
        re-import gate per AAP Section 0.7.3 will detect any deviation as
        a preview error because the sys_choice rows must reference this
        dictionary entry exactly, AND the UI Policy's condition strings
        ('party_type == "Person"' and 'party_type == "Organization"')
        must match the persisted label exactly.
-->
<record_update table="sys_dictionary">
    <sys_dictionary action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <active>true</active>
        <array>false</array>
        <attributes/>
        <audit>false</audit>
        <calculation/>
        <choice>3</choice>
        <choice_field/>
        <choice_table/>
        <column_label>Party Type</column_label>
        <comments>Mandatory Choice discriminator field for polymorphic case_party rows. Values: Person, Organization. Authored as separate sys_choice rows in ../choices/sys_choice_case_party_party_type.xml. Drives conditional visibility and requiredness of the sibling person (Reference -&gt; sys_user) and organization (Reference -&gt; core_company) fields via the UI Policy at ../ui_policy/x_casemgmt_case_party_conditional_fields.xml. Replaces ArkCase's cm_class_name JPA discriminator on acm_person_assoc / acm_person_org_assoc with a human-readable Choice; collapses the two ArkCase association tables (PersonAssociation, PersonOrganizationAssociation) into a single ServiceNow polymorphic table per AAP Section 0.4.3. No default value - user MUST explicitly choose Person or Organization, ensuring the polymorphic intent is always explicit.</comments>
        <create_roles/>
        <default_value/>
        <defaultsort/>
        <delete_roles/>
        <dependent/>
        <dependent_on_field/>
        <display>true</display>
        <dynamic_creation>false</dynamic_creation>
        <dynamic_creation_script/>
        <dynamic_default_value/>
        <dynamic_ref_qual/>
        <element>party_type</element>
        <element_reference>false</element_reference>
        <foreign_database/>
        <function_definition/>
        <function_field>false</function_field>
        <internal_type>string</internal_type>
        <mandatory>true</mandatory>
        <max_length>40</max_length>
        <name>x_casemgmt_case_party</name>
        <next_element/>
        <primary>false</primary>
        <read_only>false</read_only>
        <read_roles/>
        <reference/>
        <reference_cascade_rule/>
        <reference_floor/>
        <reference_key/>
        <reference_qual/>
        <reference_qual_condition/>
        <reference_type/>
        <sizeclass/>
        <spell_check>false</spell_check>
        <staged>false</staged>
        <sys_class_name>sys_dictionary</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>5e02afdbd2f05f407e986015e93d1238</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name/>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_casemgmt">x_casemgmt</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_casemgmt</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_dictionary_x_casemgmt_case_party_party_type</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>admin</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2025-01-01 00:00:00</sys_updated_on>
        <table_reference>false</table_reference>
        <text_index>false</text_index>
        <unique>false</unique>
        <use_dependent_field>false</use_dependent_field>
        <use_dynamic_default>false</use_dynamic_default>
        <use_reference_qualifier>simple</use_reference_qualifier>
        <virtual>false</virtual>
        <virtual_type/>
        <widget/>
        <write_roles/>
        <xml_view>false</xml_view>
    </sys_dictionary>
</record_update>
