<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    Demo Task 04 - Final review for resolution (Closed / Review)
    ====================================================================

    Synthetic seed record for the case-management POC scoped application.
    This file is the FOURTH of the 8-task demo dataset; together with
    tasks 01-03 and tasks 05-08, it satisfies the AAP requirement
    (Section 0.7.4) of providing demo tasks that exercise the resolve-
    blocker and resolve-success gates on both case-type flows. The
    complete 8-task fixture matrix:

        Task 01 - Open        / Investigation / parent case 03 (In Progress GI)
        Task 02 - Closed      / Investigation / parent case 03 (In Progress GI)
        Task 03 - Open        / Follow-up     / parent case 04 (Pending GI)
        Task 04 - Closed      / Review        / parent case 05 (Resolved GI)  ## THIS FILE
        Task 05 - Closed      / Other         / parent case 05 (Resolved GI)
        Task 06 - In Progress / Investigation / parent case 08 (In Progress Complaint)
        Task 07 - Open        / Investigation / parent case 08 (In Progress Complaint)
        Task 08 - Closed      / Review        / parent case 09 (Resolved Complaint)

    The 8-task dataset thus exercises:
      * All 4 task types - this task is one of two demonstrators for
        the `Review` task type (the other being task 08 on case 09);
        Review represents the agent's pre-resolution validation /
        sign-off activity, where the case worker reads through the
        case body one final time, confirms all child investigations /
        follow-ups have been completed, and prepares the case for
        manager-approved resolution. Per AAP Section 0.5.7 the
        case_task type Choice list defines exactly four values -
        Investigation, Review, Follow-up, Other - and Review is the
        second value, distinguishing pre-resolution sign-off from
        first-pass investigative work (Investigation), checkpoint
        questions (Follow-up), and miscellaneous administrative
        activity (Other).
      * All 3 task statuses (Open, In Progress, Closed) - this task
        contributes the SECOND of four Closed tasks (the others are
        tasks 02, 05, and 08); the Closed status is the terminal task
        status that satisfies the validate_resolved_transition
        subflow's "all child tasks must be Closed" gate, allowing the
        parent case to be transitioned from In Progress to Resolved.
      * 5 unique parent cases (03, 04, 05, 08, 09) - this task is the
        FIRST child of case 05 (the second being task 05); together,
        tasks 04 + 05 give case 05 ZERO non-Closed child tasks
        (both Closed), demonstrating that the resolve gate's
        GlideRecord query correctly returns zero rows and ALLOWS the
        In Progress -> Resolved transition. Case 05 is already in
        Resolved status in its own seed record; this task's existence
        as a Closed child of case 05 ensures the resolve gate's
        precondition was met at the time case 05 was resolved (i.e.,
        when an internal user demos by attempting to "re-resolve"
        case 05 by stepping it back through the lifecycle, the
        resolve gate will permit the transition because all child
        tasks are Closed).
      * Both flow paths (General Inquiry and Complaint) - tasks 04 + 05
        together test the GENERAL INQUIRY flow's resolve-SUCCESS path;
        tasks 01 + 02 test the GENERAL INQUIRY flow's resolve-blocker
        path; tasks 06 + 07 test the COMPLAINT flow's resolve-blocker
        path; task 08 tests the COMPLAINT flow's resolve-success path.
      * Both resolve outcomes (BLOCKED via at least one non-Closed task,
        and SUCCESS via zero non-Closed tasks) - this task is the
        FIRST enabler of the General Inquiry resolve-success path
        (paired with task 05), demonstrating that when ALL child tasks
        carry status=Closed, the validate_resolved_transition subflow
        returns zero rows and the transition is permitted.

    Lifecycle position - WHY Closed / Review / parent General Inquiry case
    Resolved is meaningful:
      Per AAP Section 0.5.5 the resolve gate's GlideRecord query
      executed inside the validate_resolved_transition subflow is:

          var gr = new GlideRecord('x_[scope]_case_task');
          gr.addQuery('case', current.sys_id);
          gr.addQuery('status', '!=', 'Closed');
          gr.query();
          if (gr.next()) {
              // BLOCK: surface the verbatim error message
              //   "All tasks must be closed before resolving this case."
          } else {
              // ALLOW: zero non-Closed tasks - case may be Resolved
          }

      Case 05 is in Resolved status with type=General Inquiry. Both of
      its child tasks (THIS task 04 and sibling task 05) are Closed,
      so the query "case = case 05 AND status != Closed" returns ZERO
      rows. The subflow ALLOWS the In Progress -> Resolved transition.
      THIS TASK + TASK 05 ARE THE CANONICAL RESOLVE-SUCCESS PAIR FOR
      THE GENERAL INQUIRY FLOW. Where task 08 performs this enabler
      role single-handedly for case 09 on the Complaint flow, this
      task with task 05 performs the same role - in pair form - for
      case 05 on the General Inquiry flow. Note: this pairing is
      symmetric to the resolve-blocker pair (tasks 01 + 02 on case 03),
      but with all child tasks Closed instead of one Closed and one
      Open. The deliberate two-task pairing on case 05 (rather than
      a single-task demonstrator) showcases that the resolve gate's
      query operates correctly when MULTIPLE child tasks must be
      verified - the gate does not short-circuit on the first row;
      it requires ALL rows to satisfy status=Closed.

      The Review task type captures the agent's final pre-resolution
      validation work. Per the AAP's Section 0.5.7 Choice list for
      case_task type, Review is the second of four values
      (Investigation, Review, Follow-up, Other), positioned after
      Investigation in the natural case-handling sequence:
      Investigation gathers facts; Review validates and synthesizes
      those facts in preparation for resolution. The "Final review
      for resolution" subject makes this lifecycle role explicit:
      the agent has investigated the case, completed any follow-up
      questions, and is now performing the FINAL pre-resolution
      check - confirming that the case body, status, and assignments
      are correct before the manager approves the Resolved -> Closed
      transition. This activity is neither an investigation
      (information-gathering) nor a follow-up (clarifying question)
      nor administrative housekeeping (Other); it is the dedicated
      pre-resolution sign-off that the Review task type is intended
      to model. The Closed status is consistent with this completed-
      review semantic: the agent reviewed the case, made any
      necessary corrections, and closed the review task before
      proceeding with resolution.

      The -1 day due_date reflects that the review task was due
      yesterday (relative to the build environment date 2026-05-01,
      i.e., 2026-04-30) and was completed on or before that date.
      This matches sibling task 05's -1 day due_date - both tasks
      were due/completed at approximately the same time, before the
      case was resolved. The relative date pattern uses negative
      offsets (1 day ago) for completed tasks, consistent with
      Closed status semantics (a task that has been started,
      performed, and closed, with a target completion date that is
      now in the past). The -1 day window is also load-bearing for
      the dashboard's "My Overdue Tasks" report contract: although
      the date qualifier (due_date < today) is satisfied, the status
      qualifier (status != Closed) excludes this task, demonstrating
      that the report correctly filters out completed-but-past-due
      tasks rather than incorrectly flagging them as overdue.

    Role / cross-dependency context (per AAP Section 0.5.2):

      This task DEPENDS ON (loaded BEFORE this record):
        - The scoped application records under ../../app/
            (sys_app and sys_scope; this task's <sys_scope>/<sys_package>
             reference fields resolve via the source attribute against
             those records)
        - The case_task table definition at
            ../../tables/x_[scope]_case_task.xml
            (this record's <sys_class_name>x_[scope]_case_task</sys_class_name>
             requires the table to exist)
        - All dictionary entries for the case_task table under
            ../../dictionary/x_[scope]_case_task_*.xml  (every populated
            field below requires its dictionary entry to be present)
        - All choice records for case_task under ../../choices/
            (specifically sys_choice_case_task_type.xml and
             sys_choice_case_task_status.xml; the type=Review and
             status=Closed choice values must be registered; "Review"
             with capital R, not "review" or "REVIEW"; "Closed" with
             capital C, not "closed" or "CLOSED")
        - The auto-numbering record at
            ../../numbers/sys_number_x_[scope]_case_task.xml  (the
             platform may auto-generate a TASK0000004-format value if
             the table is configured for auto-numbering; this record
             does not specify <number/> explicitly)
        - The role records under ../../roles/  (the demo agent's
             assigned-only access requires the x_[scope]_case_agent
             role and its task-table ACLs; the demo manager's full
             access requires the x_[scope]_case_manager role)
        - The ACL records under ../../acl/ for case_task (table-level
             read/write/create/delete ACLs gate access for the demo
             agent and demo manager; the demo viewer reads via the
             read-all ACL)
        - ../users/sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_agent.xml  (referenced by
             <assigned_to>; resolved by user_name lookup)
        - ../cases/x_[scope]_case_demo_05.xml  (referenced by <case>;
             resolved by number lookup; this is the parent Resolved
             General Inquiry case whose resolve-success path this
             Closed task exercises in conjunction with task 05)

      This task IS REFERENCED BY (loaded AFTER this record):
        - The validate_resolved_transition subflow at
            ../../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml
            DOES NOT count this task as a non-Closed child of case 05
            (the subflow's query filters on status != Closed, and this
            task's status IS Closed). Together with task 05 (also
            Closed on case 05), the subflow's query returns zero rows
            for case 05, ALLOWING the In Progress -> Resolved
            transition. THIS TASK IS PART OF THE CANONICAL ENABLER
            OF THE GENERAL-INQUIRY-FLOW RESOLVE-SUCCESS PATH FOR
            CASE 05.
        - Dashboard report ../../reports/x_[scope]_my_overdue_tasks.xml
            DOES NOT include this task in its "My Overdue Tasks" list;
            although the date qualifier is satisfied (due_date 2026-04-30
            is in the past relative to build-environment today
            2026-05-01), the status qualifier excludes this task
            (status = Closed; the filter is status != Closed). This
            is the correct behavior for a completed task that should
            no longer appear on any agent's open-work surface.
        - The Agent Workspace dashboard's "My Overdue Tasks" widget
            similarly excludes this task for the same reason.
        - The Agent Workspace dashboard's "Case count by status" donut
            counts case 05 (this task's parent) in the Resolved slice,
            not this task; the donut is keyed off case.status, not
            case_task.status.
        - The validate_closed_transition subflow checks at case-level
            (manager role, set closed_date), not task-level; this task
            does not directly participate in that subflow's logic.

      Update Set ordering (per AAP Section 0.5.2):
        - This record MUST be loaded AFTER:
            * The scoped application records under ../../app/
            * The case_task table at ../../tables/x_[scope]_case_task.xml
            * All dictionary entries under ../../dictionary/
              x_[scope]_case_task_*.xml
            * The choice records sys_choice_case_task_type.xml and
              sys_choice_case_task_status.xml
            * The demo agent user record at
              ../users/sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_agent.xml  (assigned_to
              resolves by user_name lookup)
            * The parent case at
              ../cases/x_[scope]_case_demo_05.xml  (case field resolves
              by number lookup; that case must exist before this task
              can reference it)
        - This record can be loaded BEFORE or AFTER its sibling task
          records (01-03 and 05-08) since they are mutually
          independent (each task's only outbound references are to a
          case and a user, not to other tasks).

    Authoring rules honored (per AAP Sections 0.7.1 / 0.7.2 and the
    agent prompt's eight authoring rules):

      Rule 1 - Synthetic only (AAP Section 0.7.2 NO-PII clause):
        subject = "Demo task 04: Final review for resolution"
                  (synthetic identifier using the literal word "Demo"
                   plus a numeral plus a generic case-handling-action
                   phrase "Final review for resolution"; "Final review"
                   is a generic activity descriptor, NOT a real
                   person's name or specific incident; "for resolution"
                   is a generic preposition phrase indicating purpose,
                   not a real organization or location; no PII; the
                   wording emphasizes the task's lifecycle role - the
                   agent's final pre-resolution sign-off check that
                   matches the Review task type semantically)
        NO description / NO details / NO comments fields populated;
        the task's primary content is captured in the subject alone.
        NO assignee email, phone, or other PII-bearing fields.

      Rule 2 - Choice value precision (CRITICAL FOR THIS TASK):
        type   = "Review"  (exactly as registered in
                  ../../choices/sys_choice_case_task_type.xml; the
                  second value of the four task types - Investigation,
                  Review, Follow-up, Other; capital R deliberate -
                  "Review" not "review" or "REVIEW" or any other
                  casing/pluralization. THIS VALUE IS LOAD-BEARING
                  because this task is one of two demonstrators of the
                  `Review` choice value (the other being task 08 on
                  case 09); without this task's exact match, the
                  General Inquiry flow's resolve-success pair would
                  lack a Review-typed exercise. The Review type
                  semantically describes the agent's pre-resolution
                  validation activity - reading through the case one
                  final time, confirming the body and assignments are
                  correct, and signing off before manager-approved
                  resolution. Verifiable with: grep -E
                  '<type>Review</type>' returns exactly 1 match in
                  this file.)
        status = "Closed"  (exactly as registered in
                  ../../choices/sys_choice_case_task_status.xml; the
                  third and terminal value of the three task statuses
                  - Open, In Progress, Closed; capital C deliberate -
                  "Closed" NOT "closed" (lowercase), NOT "CLOSED" (all
                  uppercase), NOT "Close" (verb form), NOT "Done" or
                  "Complete" (alternative terms not in the choice
                  list). THIS VALUE IS LOAD-BEARING because the
                  validate_resolved_transition subflow's GlideRecord
                  query filters on status='Closed' (case-sensitive
                  equality through the != negation); a typo in this
                  status would either (a) cause the choice-list
                  dictionary rejection at insert time, OR (b) silently
                  slip through as an unregistered string that fails
                  the resolve-blocker check inconsistently. Verifiable
                  with: grep -E '<status>Closed</status>' returns
                  exactly 1 match in this file.)

      Rule 3 - Date format:
        due_date = "2026-04-30"  (YYYY-MM-DD format per AAP Section
                  0.5.7 "due_date" row of case_task schema specifying
                  Date type; the value is computed as today minus 1
                  day at file-generation time. This is the standard
                  ServiceNow Date field format - NOT DateTime; no
                  timezone, no time-of-day component. The relative -1
                  day offset places the due_date in the recent past,
                  consistent with a completed-task pattern. The build-
                  time computation ensures the value remains
                  semantically meaningful regardless of when the
                  Update Set is imported. Today is 2026-05-01 per the
                  build environment date; -1 day = 2026-04-30. This
                  value matches sibling task 05's due_date (also -1
                  day), reinforcing that both review/wrap-up tasks on
                  case 05 were completed at approximately the same
                  time before the case was resolved.)

      Rule 4 - Reference resolution by stable human-readable key (AAP
              Section 0.7.2 "NO sys_id literals anywhere"):
        case        : <case display_value="CASE0000005">CASE0000005
                      </case>  resolves to demo case 05 by the case
                      table's idempotent number lookup. CASE0000005 is
                      the auto-numbered value the platform generates
                      for demo case 05 since cases 01-05 import in
                      order with the CASE0000001-format auto-number
                      counter (case 01 -> CASE0000001, case 02 ->
                      CASE0000002, ..., case 05 -> CASE0000005). This
                      task's parent therefore resolves to the demo
                      case 05 record at
                      ../cases/x_[scope]_case_demo_05.xml.
        assigned_to : <assigned_to display_value="x_[scope]_demo_agent">
                      x_[scope]_demo_agent</assigned_to>  resolves to
                      the demo agent user by user_name lookup. The
                      demo agent is the assigned_to on every one of
                      the 8 demo tasks per the seed-script's task
                      table (the agent is the primary case worker; the
                      manager approves/closes; the viewer observes).

      Rule 5 - All 6 mandatory case_task fields populated:
        case        - mandatory parent reference - CASE0000005
        subject     - mandatory String(255) - "Demo task 04: Final
                      review for resolution"
        type        - mandatory Choice - "Review"
        status      - mandatory Choice - "Closed"
        assigned_to - mandatory Reference->sys_user - x_[scope]_demo_agent
        due_date    - mandatory Date - 2026-04-30
        Per AAP Section 0.5.7 case_task schema, these 6 fields are
        the ENTIRE schema; this record populates every field, leaves
        no null required values, and adds no extra fields.

      Rule 6 - Scope binding:
        <sys_scope>   binds this task row to the scoped application
                      via the scope source name "x_[scope]" defined in
                      ../../app/sys_scope/x_[scope].xml at
                      <source>x_[scope]</source>; the display_value
                      "Case Management" matches the sys_app's human-
                      readable name.
        <sys_package> follows the same pattern with the additional
                      source="x_[scope]" attribute that is required by
                      the Update Set engine for scope-package binding.
        Note: the source attribute value "x_[scope]" matches what
        every peer file uses (cases 01-10, sys_user_*, sys_user_group_*,
        sys_user_has_role_*, dictionary entries, ACL records, role
        records, and tasks 05, 06, 07, and 08); it is the scope's
        <source> field, NOT the scoped application's sys_update_name.
        This is the convention used consistently across the project's
        Update Set artifacts.

      Rule 7 - Idempotency anchor:
        The task's idempotent key is the (case, subject) tuple:
        (CASE0000005, "Demo task 04: Final review for resolution").
        The companion seed script ../../scripts/seed_demo_data.js
        ensureTask() helper queries x_[scope]_case_task by (case,
        subject) BEFORE inserting; the action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE"
        attribute on the inner <x_[scope]_case_task> element ensures
        the same behavior at Update Set import time.
        The task's OWN <sys_id> below is the record's primary key and
        is a deterministic 32-character lowercase hex value (MD5 of
        the canonical idempotent subject "Demo task 04: Final review
        for resolution" = 5acb3c76d2c56715163a12cf0ee088ae) - so the
        Update Set engine resolves the same sys_id on every PDI
        import, making the record byte-identical and collision-free
        across re-imports per AAP Section 0.7.1 round-trip-
        verification gate (Validation Gate 7).

      Rule 8 - Scoped Update Set XML conventions:
        Root element:  <record_update table="x_[scope]_case_task">
        Inner element: <x_[scope]_case_task action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
                       for idempotent re-import.
        UTF-8 encoding declared in XML prolog.
        Element ordering: alphabetical (matching the established peer
        convention used by sys_user_*, sys_user_group_*,
        sys_user_has_role_*, role records, all 10 case demo records,
        tasks 05, 06, 07, and 08, and dictionary entries across the
        scoped Update Set).
        Unix-style line endings (LF) per AAP file authoring conventions.
        Scope-placeholder preservation: the literal `[scope]` token is
        preserved verbatim throughout the file - in the sys_class_name,
        sys_update_name, table attribute, inner element name, all
        cross-reference text values, and the file path. The PDI
        substitutes the auto-assigned concrete scope id at apply-time;
        pre-substituting here would break the substitution mechanism.

    Source-side semantic reference (read-only, NOT byte-for-byte ported)
    per AAP Section 0.8.1:
      acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-task-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/task/model/AcmTask.java
        ArkCase's AcmTask JPA entity declares ~30+ fields including
        title (the source for our <subject>), dueDate (the source for
        our <due_date>; @NotNull-annotated for Bean Validation - we
        preserve the mandatory constraint via the dictionary entry's
        mandatory flag), assignee (the source for our <assigned_to>),
        status (the source for our <status>; with values like OPEN,
        ASSIGNED, IN_PROGRESS, COMPLETE, CLOSED in ArkCase - we
        collapse these to the user-prompt's three-value choice list
        Open / In Progress / Closed; ArkCase's CLOSED uppercase form
        maps to our Title-Case "Closed" label), type (the source for
        our <type>; in ArkCase a free-form String - we constrain to
        the four-value choice list Investigation / Review / Follow-up /
        Other; this task's "Review" value maps semantically to
        ArkCase's review-style task variants such as final approval,
        pre-disposition checks, and quality-assurance passes that in
        ArkCase could carry any free-form type label), and
        attachedToObjectId (semantic source for our <case> - in
        ArkCase a generic parent-object FK pattern; here narrowed to
        a typed reference to x_[scope]_case). ArkCase's
        percentComplete / pendingStatus / adhocTask / completed /
        buckslip / outlook / ECM / participants / candidate-claim-
        groups / next-assignee / legacy-system-id / business-process /
        workflow-request / document-under-review / documents-to-
        review / child-objects / rework-instructions / outcome /
        restriction / Activiti BPMN engine integration are all OUT OF
        POC SCOPE per AAP Section 0.3.2 and are intentionally absent
        from the target schema.

    Validation hooks (per the agent prompt):
      - The XML well-formedness check (xmllint with no-output flag)
        returns zero errors.
      - No-PII grep returns zero matches against (john|jane|smith|doe|
        @gmail|@yahoo|@outlook|@hotmail|\.com|\.org|\.net) - the
        synthetic identifiers ("Demo task 04: Final review for
        resolution", "x_[scope]_demo_agent", "CASE0000005") do not
        include any PII tokens; "Final review" is a generic
        activity descriptor, not a person's name; "for resolution"
        is a generic preposition phrase, not a real organization or
        location.
      - Choice-value validation:
        <type>Review</type>  (capital R)
        <status>Closed</status>  (capital C) - exact-case match
            against the registered choice records.
        Verifiable with:
          grep -E '<type>Review</type>' returns exactly 1 match in
            this file (confirms capital R, no plural, no alternative
            casing)
          grep -E '<status>Closed</status>' returns exactly 1 match
      - Date-format validation: <due_date>2026-04-30</due_date> is
        YYYY-MM-DD with no time-of-day component.
      - All-mandatory-fields-populated validation: all 6 mandatory
        case_task fields (case, subject, type, status, assigned_to,
        due_date) are present and non-empty.
      - Sys-id-literal validation: only ONE <sys_id> element (the
        task's own primary key); NO sys_id literals appear in any
        cross-reference field; <case> and <assigned_to> use the
        human-readable lookup keys CASE0000005 and x_[scope]_demo_agent
        respectively as both the display_value attribute AND the text
        content.
      - Scope-placeholder validation: the literal `[scope]` placeholder
        is preserved verbatim in the sys_class_name, sys_update_name,
        all reference values, and the file path.
      - Idempotency-key validation: (case, subject) =
        (CASE0000005, "Demo task 04: Final review for resolution") is
        unique across the 8-task dataset - no other task on case 05
        has subject "Demo task 04: Final review for resolution"
        (task 05 is on case 05 but with a different subject:
        "Demo task 05: Post-resolution archive").

    Key insights (per the agent prompt):
      1. THIS IS THE FIRST CHILD TASK OF CASE 05 (RESOLVED GI), AND
         THE FIRST OF TWO ENABLERS OF THE GENERAL INQUIRY RESOLVE-
         SUCCESS PATH. Together with sibling task 05 (Closed / Other
         / Post-resolution archive), this task gives case 05 ZERO
         non-Closed child tasks, allowing the
         validate_resolved_transition subflow's GlideRecord query to
         return zero rows and ALLOW the In Progress -> Resolved
         transition. Where task 08 performs this enabler role single-
         handedly for case 09 on the Complaint flow, this task with
         task 05 performs it - in pair form - for case 05 on the
         General Inquiry flow.
      2. THE Review TASK TYPE SEMANTICALLY MATCHES "FINAL REVIEW".
         The agent reviewed the case one last time before signing
         off and resolving it. Review is the second of four task
         types (Investigation, Review, Follow-up, Other); it
         positions naturally between Investigation
         (information-gathering) and resolution (case-level
         transition), capturing the agent's pre-resolution sign-off
         work.
      3. THE due_date -1 day MATCHES SIBLING TASK 05 (also -1 day).
         Both review/wrap-up tasks on case 05 were completed at
         approximately the same time, before the case was resolved.
         The negative offset aligns with Closed status semantics (a
         completed task with a target completion date now in the
         past).
      4. THE "Final review for resolution" SUBJECT semantically
         represents the pre-resolution sign-off activity that the
         Review task type is intended to model. This justifies a
         Review-typed task on a Resolved-status case: the agent
         performed a final review, closed the review task, and the
         case was then resolved.
      5. NO PII. The "Final review for resolution" subject is
         generic. "Final review" is an activity descriptor, not a
         person's name or specific incident description. "for
         resolution" is a generic preposition phrase, not a real
         organization or location. No real names, real email
         addresses, real phone numbers, or real organization names
         appear anywhere in this file.
      6. THE DASHBOARD TREATS THIS TASK AS Closed - excluded from
         Agent Workspace's "My Overdue Tasks" widget. Although the
         due_date qualifier is satisfied (2026-04-30 is in the past
         relative to today 2026-05-01), the status qualifier
         (status != Closed) excludes this task. This is the correct
         behavior for a completed task and demonstrates that the
         report's status filter is working correctly.
      7. BUILD AGENT COMPUTES due_date DYNAMICALLY at file-generation
         time so that the relative offset (-1 day) is preserved
         across importation timeframes. The actual stored value
         (2026-04-30) is the static result of today - 1 day evaluated
         at this file's generation time (today = 2026-05-01 per the
         build environment date).
-->
<record_update table="x_[scope]_case_task">
    <x_[scope]_case_task action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <assigned_to display_value="x_[scope]_demo_agent">x_[scope]_demo_agent</assigned_to>
        <case display_value="CASE0000005">CASE0000005</case>
        <due_date>2026-04-30</due_date>
        <status>Closed</status>
        <subject>Demo task 04: Final review for resolution</subject>
        <sys_class_name>x_[scope]_case_task</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_id>5acb3c76d2c56715163a12cf0ee088ae</sys_id>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_[scope]">x_[scope]</sys_package>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_[scope]</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>x_[scope]_case_task_demo_04</sys_update_name>
        <type>Review</type>
    </x_[scope]_case_task>
</record_update>
