<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    Demo Task 03 - Follow up with requester (Open / Follow-up)
    ====================================================================

    Synthetic seed record for the case-management POC scoped application.
    This file is the THIRD of the 8-task demo dataset; together with
    tasks 01-02 and tasks 04-08, it satisfies the AAP requirement
    (Section 0.7.4) of providing demo tasks that exercise the resolve-
    blocker and resolve-success gates on both case-type flows. The
    complete 8-task fixture matrix:

        Task 01 - Open        / Investigation / parent case 03 (In Progress GI)
        Task 02 - Closed      / Investigation / parent case 03 (In Progress GI)
        Task 03 - Open        / Follow-up     / parent case 04 (Pending GI)        ## THIS FILE
        Task 04 - Closed      / Review        / parent case 05 (Resolved GI)
        Task 05 - Closed      / Other         / parent case 05 (Resolved GI)
        Task 06 - In Progress / Investigation / parent case 08 (In Progress Complaint)
        Task 07 - Open        / Investigation / parent case 08 (In Progress Complaint)
        Task 08 - Closed      / Review        / parent case 09 (Resolved Complaint)

    The 8-task dataset thus exercises:
      * All 4 task types - this task is THE ONE AND ONLY canonical
        demonstrator for the `Follow-up` task type (Investigation
        appears on tasks 01, 02, 06, 07; Review appears on tasks 04
        and 08; Other appears on task 05; Follow-up appears only
        here). Per AAP Section 0.5.7 the case_task type Choice list
        defines exactly four values - Investigation, Review,
        Follow-up, Other - and Follow-up is the THIRD value, with a
        deliberate HYPHEN between "Follow" and "up" (NOT a space, NOT
        an underscore, NOT a single word). This task is the
        LOAD-BEARING PROOF that the `Follow-up` choice value with
        its exact hyphenated spelling is registered in
        ../../choices/sys_choice_case_task_type.xml, accepted by the
        case_task table's type-field dictionary entry, and surfaces
        correctly on the form. Follow-up represents the agent's
        outbound clarifying question to the requester or to a third
        party - the activity that distinguishes a stalled case
        (waiting on the agent) from a Pending case (waiting on
        external input). Pairing the Follow-up task type with the
        Pending parent case status creates the canonical
        information-gap demonstration: case 04 is Pending awaiting
        external info, and this Follow-up task is the agent's
        actionable item to obtain that info.
      * All 3 task statuses (Open, In Progress, Closed) - this task
        contributes the FIRST of two Open tasks (the other being
        task 07 on case 08); the Open status is the initial,
        not-yet-started status that contrasts with both terminal
        Closed and active In Progress, demonstrating that all three
        registered status values are surfaced in the demo dataset.
        The Open status on this task ALSO gates any future attempt
        to resolve case 04: although case 04 is currently Pending
        (not directly resolvable), if it were transitioned through
        Pending -> In Progress -> Resolved the validate_resolved_
        transition subflow would query non-Closed children of case 04
        and find this Open task, returning the verbatim blocking
        error "All tasks must be closed before resolving this case."
        per AAP Section 0.5.5. This task is NOT load-bearing for any
        immediate resolve-success path, but it IS load-bearing for
        the demonstration that Pending cases retain Open child tasks
        until the requested information is received.
      * 5 unique parent cases (03, 04, 05, 08, 09) - this task is
        the SOLE child of case 04 (Pending General Inquiry); no
        other demo task references CASE0000004, making this task
        the canonical exercise of the case-04-task association.
        Pairing case 04 (Pending status) with this Open Follow-up
        task is intentional: the Pending status by AAP Section 0.5.7
        choice list semantically means "waiting on something
        external," and the Follow-up task type semantically means
        "agent's outbound clarifying question". Together they tell
        the operational story: the agent has placed the case on
        hold (Pending = Awaiting Info per case 04's pending_reason)
        and has scheduled a follow-up call/email (this task) to
        retrieve the missing input. The agent will execute the
        follow-up activity, close THIS task, and then transition
        case 04 from Pending to In Progress (which will clear the
        pending_reason via the clear_pending_reason_on_inprogress
        business rule). The case 04 -> In Progress -> Resolved path
        is the ultimate goal, but at this moment the case is
        deliberately stalled with this Open follow-up task as the
        single gating action.
      * Both flow paths (General Inquiry and Complaint) - this task
        sits on a General Inquiry case (case 04). The General Inquiry
        flow's resolve-blocker path is exercised by tasks 01 + 02 on
        case 03; the General Inquiry flow's resolve-success path is
        exercised by tasks 04 + 05 on case 05. THIS task does not
        directly exercise a resolve gate (case 04 is in Pending
        status, not In Progress), but its Open status would block
        any hypothetical resolve attempt on case 04, demonstrating
        that the resolve-blocker query is independent of where the
        case currently sits in the lifecycle.

    Lifecycle position - WHY Open / Follow-up / parent General Inquiry
    case Pending is meaningful:
      Per AAP Section 0.5.5 the canonical Pending semantics are: a
      Pending case is one where the agent has placed it on hold
      pending external input (see case 04's pending_reason =
      "Awaiting Info" choice value). Per AAP Section 0.5.7 the
      Pending case status accepts a pending_reason qualifier with
      values "Awaiting Info", "Awaiting Third Party", "Other". The
      Pending state is operator-initiated (not auto-triggered), and
      transitioning OUT of Pending requires an operator-initiated
      Pending -> In Progress transition that clears pending_reason
      via the x_[scope]_clear_pending_reason_on_inprogress business
      rule (see ../../business_rules/x_[scope]_clear_pending_reason_
      on_inprogress.xml).

      During the Pending interval the case-management workflow does
      NOT prevent task creation/modification - tasks remain a
      first-class child entity of the case and continue to be the
      operator's tool for tracking outstanding work. THIS task is
      the canonical demonstration of that interval's workflow:
      while case 04 is Pending awaiting external info, the agent
      has created a Follow-up task (with a +2 day due_date) to
      track the outbound clarifying contact. When the agent
      successfully obtains the requested information, two things
      happen in the demo workflow:
        (a) The agent closes this Open task by setting its status
            to Closed (an operator-driven activity surfaced via the
            case-form's related-list edit affordance).
        (b) The agent operator-initiates the case 04 Pending ->
            In Progress transition. The clear_pending_reason_on_
            inprogress business rule fires, removing the
            "Awaiting Info" pending_reason. Case 04 is now active
            again.
      Note that step (a) does NOT auto-trigger step (b) - per AAP
      Section 0.5.5 there is no implicit Pending-clear-on-task-
      closure flow logic. The two activities are operationally
      sequential but technically independent.

      The Follow-up task type captures the agent's outbound
      clarifying contact activity. Per the AAP's Section 0.5.7
      Choice list for case_task type, Follow-up is the third of
      four values (Investigation, Review, Follow-up, Other),
      positioned to capture work that is neither initial fact-
      gathering (Investigation), nor final pre-resolution sign-off
      (Review), nor miscellaneous administrative housekeeping
      (Other), but specifically the agent's outbound clarifying
      question or status check. The "Follow up with requester"
      subject makes this lifecycle role explicit: the agent is
      reaching out to the requester (the external party who
      submitted case 04 via the Experience Portal or whose
      synthetic requester_name is captured on the case) to obtain
      the missing input that is keeping case 04 Pending. The Open
      status is consistent with this not-yet-executed semantic:
      the agent has scheduled the follow-up but has not yet
      performed the outreach.

      The +2 day due_date reflects that the follow-up is scheduled
      for two days from now (relative to the build environment date
      2026-05-01, i.e., 2026-05-03) - a near-term, time-sensitive
      action that is NOT yet overdue. The relative date pattern
      uses positive offsets (2 days hence) for active, scheduled
      tasks, consistent with Open status semantics (a task that has
      been scheduled but not yet started, with a target completion
      date in the near future). The +2 day window is also load-
      bearing for the dashboard's "My Overdue Tasks" report
      contract: the date qualifier (due_date < today) is NOT
      satisfied (2026-05-03 is in the future relative to today
      2026-05-01), so this task correctly does NOT appear on the
      Agent Workspace's "My Overdue Tasks" widget. This
      demonstrates that the report's date filter correctly excludes
      future-dated active tasks rather than incorrectly flagging
      them as overdue. By contrast, sibling task 01 has a -3 day
      due_date and IS overdue (and Open), making task 01 the
      positive-test fixture for the My Overdue Tasks widget; this
      task is the negative-test fixture (Open but not yet overdue).

    Role / cross-dependency context (per AAP Section 0.5.2):

      This task DEPENDS ON (loaded BEFORE this record):
        - The scoped application records under ../../app/
            (sys_app and sys_scope; this task's <sys_scope>/<sys_package>
             reference fields resolve via the source attribute against
             those records)
        - The case_task table definition at
            ../../tables/x_[scope]_case_task.xml
            (this record's <sys_class_name>x_[scope]_case_task</sys_class_name>
             requires the table to exist)
        - All dictionary entries for the case_task table under
            ../../dictionary/x_[scope]_case_task_*.xml  (every populated
            field below requires its dictionary entry to be present)
        - All choice records for case_task under ../../choices/
            (specifically sys_choice_case_task_type.xml and
             sys_choice_case_task_status.xml; the type=Follow-up and
             status=Open choice values must be registered; "Follow-up"
             with a single hyphen between "Follow" and "up", Title
             Case "Follow", lowercase "up", NOT "Follow up" with a
             space, NOT "Followup" without a separator, NOT "Follow_up"
             with an underscore, NOT "FOLLOW-UP" all uppercase; "Open"
             with capital O, not "open" or "OPEN")
        - The auto-numbering record at
            ../../numbers/sys_number_x_[scope]_case_task.xml  (the
             platform may auto-generate a TASK0000003-format value if
             the table is configured for auto-numbering; this record
             does not specify <number/> explicitly)
        - The role records under ../../roles/  (the demo agent's
             assigned-only access requires the x_[scope]_case_agent
             role and its task-table ACLs; the demo manager's full
             access requires the x_[scope]_case_manager role)
        - The ACL records under ../../acl/ for case_task (table-level
             read/write/create/delete ACLs gate access for the demo
             agent and demo manager; the demo viewer reads via the
             read-all ACL)
        - ../users/sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_agent.xml  (referenced by
             <assigned_to>; resolved by user_name lookup)
        - ../cases/x_[scope]_case_demo_04.xml  (referenced by <case>;
             resolved by number lookup; this is the parent Pending
             General Inquiry case for which this task is the SOLE
             child task in the demo dataset)

      This task IS REFERENCED BY (loaded AFTER this record):
        - The validate_resolved_transition subflow at
            ../../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml
            DOES count this task as a non-Closed child of case 04
            (the subflow's query filters on status != Closed, and
            this task's status IS Open, which != Closed). However,
            case 04 is currently in Pending status, not In Progress,
            so the resolve gate (which only fires on In Progress ->
            Resolved attempts) does not currently apply. If case 04
            were operator-transitioned Pending -> In Progress -> the
            validate_resolved_transition subflow would query non-
            Closed children of case 04 and find THIS Open task,
            returning the verbatim blocking error "All tasks must
            be closed before resolving this case." Although this is
            not the immediate workflow path for case 04, it
            demonstrates that the resolve gate's logic is robust
            against Open child tasks regardless of the parent case's
            current status.
        - Dashboard report ../../reports/x_[scope]_my_overdue_tasks.xml
            does NOT include this task in its "My Overdue Tasks"
            list. The report's filter is "due_date < today AND
            status != Closed AND assigned_to = current user". This
            task's status (Open) and assigned_to (demo agent)
            satisfy two of the three qualifiers, but the date
            qualifier is NOT satisfied: due_date 2026-05-03 is in
            the FUTURE relative to today 2026-05-01. Correctly
            excluded - this is a not-yet-overdue active task. By
            contrast, task 01's due_date is -3 days (in the past)
            and IS in the report.
        - The Agent Workspace dashboard's "My Overdue Tasks" widget
            similarly excludes this task for the same reason.
        - The Agent Workspace dashboard's "Case count by status"
            donut counts case 04 (this task's parent) in the
            Pending slice, not this task; the donut is keyed off
            case.status, not case_task.status.
        - The clear_pending_reason_on_inprogress business rule at
            ../../business_rules/x_[scope]_clear_pending_reason_on_
            inprogress.xml fires on the case 04 Pending -> In
            Progress transition (an operator-driven future activity
            in the demo workflow), but does NOT directly act on
            this task. The closure of THIS task is a SEPARATE
            operator-driven activity that precedes (or in the demo
            scenario, is operationally paired with) the Pending ->
            In Progress transition.
        - The validate_closed_transition subflow checks at case-
            level (manager role, set closed_date), not task-level;
            this task does not directly participate in that
            subflow's logic.

      Update Set ordering (per AAP Section 0.5.2):
        - This record MUST be loaded AFTER:
            * The scoped application records under ../../app/
            * The case_task table at ../../tables/x_[scope]_case_task.xml
            * All dictionary entries under ../../dictionary/
              x_[scope]_case_task_*.xml
            * The choice records sys_choice_case_task_type.xml and
              sys_choice_case_task_status.xml
            * The demo agent user record at
              ../users/sys_user_x_[scope]_demo_agent.xml  (assigned_to
              resolves by user_name lookup)
            * The parent case at
              ../cases/x_[scope]_case_demo_04.xml  (case field
              resolves by number lookup; that case must exist before
              this task can reference it)
        - This record can be loaded BEFORE or AFTER its sibling task
          records (01-02 and 04-08) since they are mutually
          independent (each task's only outbound references are to
          a case and a user, not to other tasks).

    Authoring rules honored (per AAP Sections 0.7.1 / 0.7.2 and the
    agent prompt's eight authoring rules):

      Rule 1 - Synthetic only (AAP Section 0.7.2 NO-PII clause):
        subject = "Demo task 03: Follow up with requester"
                  (synthetic identifier using the literal word "Demo"
                   plus a numeral plus a generic case-handling-action
                   phrase "Follow up with requester"; "Follow up" is
                   a generic agent-activity descriptor written as the
                   English phrase with a SPACE between "Follow" and
                   "up" - this is the natural English phrase, NOT
                   the typed Choice value `Follow-up` (which uses a
                   hyphen). The CHOICE value `Follow-up` for the
                   <type> element is a separate distinct string that
                   appears in <type>Follow-up</type> below; the two
                   strings are intentionally different - the subject
                   uses natural English orthography, the type uses
                   the registered Choice key with its hyphenated
                   spelling. "with requester" is a generic
                   preposition+role phrase indicating the recipient
                   role of the follow-up activity, not a real
                   person's name; "requester" is a role label, not a
                   PII identifier; no PII; the wording emphasizes
                   the task's lifecycle role - the agent's outbound
                   clarifying contact to the case's requester to
                   obtain the missing information that is keeping
                   case 04 Pending)
        NO description / NO details / NO comments fields populated;
        the task's primary content is captured in the subject alone.
        NO assignee email, phone, or other PII-bearing fields.

      Rule 2 - Choice value precision (CRITICAL FOR THIS TASK):
        type   = "Follow-up"  (exactly as registered in
                  ../../choices/sys_choice_case_task_type.xml; the
                  third value of the four task types - Investigation,
                  Review, Follow-up, Other; spelling is HYPHENATED -
                  "Follow-up" with a single hyphen between "Follow"
                  and "up", Title Case "Follow", lowercase "up". This
                  is the SINGLE MOST COMMON ERROR POINT for this
                  file because the natural English phrase "Follow up
                  with requester" appearing in the <subject> element
                  uses a SPACE between "Follow" and "up", but the
                  typed Choice key uses a HYPHEN. Anti-patterns:
                    - "Follow up"   (space; this is the English
                                     phrase, NOT the choice key)
                    - "Followup"    (no separator)
                    - "Follow_up"   (underscore)
                    - "FOLLOW-UP"   (uppercase)
                    - "follow-up"   (lowercase F)
                    - "Follow-Up"   (uppercase U)
                  CORRECT: exactly "Follow-up" - single hyphen,
                  Title Case "Follow", lowercase "up". THIS VALUE IS
                  LOAD-BEARING because this task is THE SOLE
                  demonstrator of the `Follow-up` choice value in
                  the demo dataset; without this task's exact match,
                  no fixture in the dataset would exercise the
                  third of four task types. Verifiable with: grep
                  -E '<type>Follow-up</type>' returns exactly 1
                  match in this file. grep -E '<type>Follow up</type>'
                  returns exactly 0 matches (verifies the HYPHEN
                  form is used, not the SPACE form).
        status = "Open"  (exactly as registered in
                  ../../choices/sys_choice_case_task_status.xml; the
                  first value of the three task statuses - Open, In
                  Progress, Closed; capital O deliberate - "Open"
                  NOT "open" (lowercase), NOT "OPEN" (all
                  uppercase), NOT "New" or "Pending" (alternative
                  terms not in the choice list; specifically NOT
                  "Pending" - the Pending status applies to the
                  parent case, NOT to child tasks. case_task.status
                  has only Open / In Progress / Closed; case.status
                  is the one with Pending). THIS VALUE IS
                  LOAD-BEARING because Open is the canonical
                  initial-task status that pairs naturally with the
                  +2 day future-dated due_date, demonstrating the
                  scheduled-but-not-yet-started workflow state.
                  Verifiable with: grep -E '<status>Open</status>'
                  returns exactly 1 match in this file.)

      Rule 3 - Date format:
        due_date = "2026-05-03"  (YYYY-MM-DD format per AAP Section
                  0.5.7 "due_date" row of case_task schema specifying
                  Date type; the value is computed as today plus 2
                  days at file-generation time. This is the standard
                  ServiceNow Date field format - NOT DateTime; no
                  timezone, no time-of-day component. The relative
                  +2 day offset places the due_date in the near
                  future, consistent with an Open task pattern. The
                  build-time computation ensures the value remains
                  semantically meaningful regardless of when the
                  Update Set is imported. Today is 2026-05-01 per
                  the build environment date; +2 days = 2026-05-03.
                  This value contrasts with sibling tasks 04 and 05
                  (-1 day each, completed yesterday) and tasks 06
                  (+7 days), 07 (+3 days), 08 (-2 days), and 01
                  (-3 days), demonstrating that the demo dataset
                  spans both past-due and future-due time windows
                  to exercise the My Overdue Tasks report's date
                  filter.)

      Rule 4 - Reference resolution by stable human-readable key
              (AAP Section 0.7.2 "NO sys_id literals anywhere"):
        case        : <case display_value="CASE0000004">CASE0000004
                      </case>  resolves to demo case 04 by the case
                      table's idempotent number lookup. CASE0000004
                      is the auto-numbered value the platform
                      generates for demo case 04 since cases 01-04
                      import in order with the CASE0000001-format
                      auto-number counter (case 01 -> CASE0000001,
                      case 02 -> CASE0000002, case 03 -> CASE0000003,
                      case 04 -> CASE0000004). This task's parent
                      therefore resolves to the demo case 04 record
                      at ../cases/x_[scope]_case_demo_04.xml, which
                      is the Pending General Inquiry case awaiting
                      external information per its pending_reason =
                      "Awaiting Info".
        assigned_to : <assigned_to display_value="x_[scope]_demo_agent">
                      x_[scope]_demo_agent</assigned_to>  resolves
                      to the demo agent user by user_name lookup.
                      The demo agent is the assigned_to on every
                      one of the 8 demo tasks per the seed-script's
                      task table (the agent is the primary case
                      worker; the manager approves/closes; the
                      viewer observes).

      Rule 5 - All 6 mandatory case_task fields populated:
        case        - mandatory parent reference - CASE0000004
        subject     - mandatory String(255) - "Demo task 03: Follow
                      up with requester"
        type        - mandatory Choice - "Follow-up"
        status      - mandatory Choice - "Open"
        assigned_to - mandatory Reference->sys_user - x_[scope]_demo_agent
        due_date    - mandatory Date - 2026-05-03
        Per AAP Section 0.5.7 case_task schema, these 6 fields are
        the ENTIRE schema; this record populates every field, leaves
        no null required values, and adds no extra fields.

      Rule 6 - Scope binding:
        <sys_scope>   binds this task row to the scoped application
                      via the scope source name "x_[scope]" defined
                      in ../../app/sys_scope/x_[scope].xml at
                      <source>x_[scope]</source>; the display_value
                      "Case Management" matches the sys_app's human-
                      readable name.
        <sys_package> follows the same pattern with the additional
                      source="x_[scope]" attribute that is required
                      by the Update Set engine for scope-package
                      binding.
        Note: the source attribute value "x_[scope]" matches what
        every peer file uses (cases 01-10, sys_user_*,
        sys_user_group_*, sys_user_has_role_*, dictionary entries,
        ACL records, role records, and tasks 04, 05, 06, 07, and
        08); it is the scope's <source> field, NOT the scoped
        application's sys_update_name. This is the convention used
        consistently across the project's Update Set artifacts.

      Rule 7 - Idempotency anchor:
        The task's idempotent key is the (case, subject) tuple:
        (CASE0000004, "Demo task 03: Follow up with requester").
        The companion seed script ../../scripts/seed_demo_data.js
        ensureTask() helper queries x_[scope]_case_task by (case,
        subject) BEFORE inserting; the action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE"
        attribute on the inner <x_[scope]_case_task> element
        ensures the same behavior at Update Set import time.
        The task's OWN <sys_id> below is the record's primary key
        and is a deterministic 32-character lowercase hex value
        (MD5 of the canonical idempotent subject "Demo task 03:
        Follow up with requester" =
        922ef8bd877c160b4468ddfe919d8a52) - so the Update Set
        engine resolves the same sys_id on every PDI import, making
        the record byte-identical and collision-free across
        re-imports per AAP Section 0.7.1 round-trip-verification
        gate (Validation Gate 7).

      Rule 8 - Scoped Update Set XML conventions:
        Root element:  <record_update table="x_[scope]_case_task">
        Inner element: <x_[scope]_case_task action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
                       for idempotent re-import.
        UTF-8 encoding declared in XML prolog.
        Element ordering: alphabetical (matching the established
        peer convention used by sys_user_*, sys_user_group_*,
        sys_user_has_role_*, role records, all 10 case demo
        records, tasks 04, 05, 06, 07, and 08, and dictionary
        entries across the scoped Update Set).
        Unix-style line endings (LF) per AAP file authoring
        conventions.
        Scope-placeholder preservation: the literal `[scope]` token
        is preserved verbatim throughout the file - in the
        sys_class_name, sys_update_name, table attribute, inner
        element name, all cross-reference text values, and the
        file path. The PDI substitutes the auto-assigned concrete
        scope id at apply-time; pre-substituting here would break
        the substitution mechanism.

    Source-side semantic reference (read-only, NOT byte-for-byte
    ported) per AAP Section 0.8.1:
      acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-task-plugin/src/main/java/
        com/armedia/acm/plugins/task/model/AcmTask.java
        ArkCase's AcmTask JPA entity declares ~30+ fields including
        title (the source for our <subject>), dueDate (the source
        for our <due_date>; @NotNull-annotated for Bean Validation
        - we preserve the mandatory constraint via the dictionary
        entry's mandatory flag), assignee (the source for our
        <assigned_to>), status (the source for our <status>; with
        values like OPEN, ASSIGNED, IN_PROGRESS, COMPLETE, CLOSED
        in ArkCase - we collapse these to the user-prompt's
        three-value choice list Open / In Progress / Closed;
        ArkCase's OPEN uppercase form maps to our Title-Case "Open"
        label), type (the source for our <type>; in ArkCase a
        free-form String - we constrain to the four-value choice
        list Investigation / Review / Follow-up / Other; this
        task's "Follow-up" value maps semantically to ArkCase's
        clarification-style task variants such as request-info,
        await-response, and contact-requester that in ArkCase
        could carry any free-form type label. The hyphenated
        "Follow-up" form is a target-defined typographic choice
        with no direct ArkCase analog), and attachedToObjectId
        (semantic source for our <case> - in ArkCase a generic
        parent-object FK pattern; here narrowed to a typed
        reference to x_[scope]_case). ArkCase's percentComplete /
        pendingStatus / adhocTask / completed / buckslip / outlook
        / ECM / participants / candidate-claim-groups /
        next-assignee / legacy-system-id / business-process /
        workflow-request / document-under-review / documents-to-
        review / child-objects / rework-instructions / outcome /
        restriction / Activiti BPMN engine integration are all OUT
        OF POC SCOPE per AAP Section 0.3.2 and are intentionally
        absent from the target schema.

    Validation hooks (per the agent prompt):
      - The XML well-formedness check (xmllint with no-output
        flag) returns zero errors.
      - No-PII grep returns zero matches against (john|jane|smith|
        doe|@gmail|@yahoo|@outlook|@hotmail|\.com|\.org|\.net) -
        the synthetic identifiers ("Demo task 03: Follow up with
        requester", "x_[scope]_demo_agent", "CASE0000004") do not
        include any PII tokens; "Follow up" is a generic
        agent-activity descriptor written as the natural English
        phrase, not a person's name; "with requester" is a generic
        preposition+role-label phrase, not a real person or
        organization.
      - Choice-value validation:
        <type>Follow-up</type>  (HYPHEN, single, between "Follow"
            and "up") - exact-case match against the registered
            choice record. Verifiable with:
              grep -E '<type>Follow-up</type>' returns exactly 1
                match in this file (confirms HYPHEN form, Title
                Case "Follow", lowercase "up")
              grep -E '<type>Follow up</type>' returns exactly 0
                matches in this file (confirms the SPACE form is
                NOT used for the typed Choice value)
        <status>Open</status>  (capital O) - exact-case match
            against the registered choice record. Verifiable with:
              grep -E '<status>Open</status>' returns exactly 1
                match in this file
      - Date-format validation: <due_date>2026-05-03</due_date>
        is YYYY-MM-DD with no time-of-day component.
      - All-mandatory-fields-populated validation: all 6 mandatory
        case_task fields (case, subject, type, status,
        assigned_to, due_date) are present and non-empty.
      - Sys-id-literal validation: only ONE <sys_id> element (the
        task's own primary key); NO sys_id literals appear in any
        cross-reference field; <case> and <assigned_to> use the
        human-readable lookup keys CASE0000004 and
        x_[scope]_demo_agent respectively as both the
        display_value attribute AND the text content.
      - Scope-placeholder validation: the literal `[scope]`
        placeholder is preserved verbatim in the sys_class_name,
        sys_update_name, all reference values, and the file path.
      - Idempotency-key validation: (case, subject) =
        (CASE0000004, "Demo task 03: Follow up with requester") is
        unique across the 8-task dataset - no other task on case
        04 exists in the demo dataset (this task is the SOLE child
        of case 04) and no other task has subject "Demo task 03:
        Follow up with requester".

    Key insights (per the agent prompt):
      1. THE `Follow-up` HYPHEN IS THE MOST COMMON ERROR POINT.
         AAP Section 0.5.7 explicitly defines this with a hyphen.
         The natural English phrase "Follow up with requester" in
         the <subject> element uses a SPACE between "Follow" and
         "up", but the typed Choice value `Follow-up` for the
         <type> element uses a HYPHEN. They are intentionally
         DIFFERENT strings serving different purposes: the subject
         is human-readable English; the type is a typed key in the
         choice list. Validate after authoring with:
           grep -E '<type>Follow-up</type>'  -> 1 match
           grep -E '<type>Follow up</type>'  -> 0 matches
      2. THE SUBJECT "Follow up with requester" USES A SPACE
         (English phrase), but the type CHOICE value is `Follow-up`
         (HYPHEN, typed concept). They are intentionally different
         strings - this is by design, not by mistake. The subject
         describes what the agent will DO ("follow up" as a verb
         phrase); the type categorizes the task into a registered
         workflow class ("Follow-up" as a noun keyword).
      3. THIS TASK IS ON A PENDING CASE. Case 04 is in Pending
         status (`pending_reason=Awaiting Info`). The follow-up
         task tracks the agent's outbound call/email to the
         requester to obtain the missing information. The pairing
         of Pending case status + Follow-up task type is the
         canonical information-gap demonstration pattern.
      4. THE due_date IS +2 DAYS (NEAR-TERM, NOT YET OVERDUE).
         This makes the task time-sensitive but NOT yet overdue,
         demonstrating realistic operational urgency. The +2 day
         offset specifically:
           - Creates a not-yet-overdue Open task (correctly
             EXCLUDED from My Overdue Tasks report)
           - Contrasts with task 01's -3 day overdue Open task
             (correctly INCLUDED in My Overdue Tasks report)
         Together, tasks 01 and 03 demonstrate that the date
         filter on the My Overdue Tasks report correctly partitions
         Open tasks into overdue (past-due) and not-yet-overdue
         (future-due) buckets.
      5. TASK TYPE `Follow-up` IS ONE OF FOUR AAP-MANDATED VALUES:
         Investigation, Review, Follow-up, Other. This task is the
         CANONICAL DEMONSTRATOR for the Follow-up type - the SOLE
         exercise of this choice value in the entire 8-task demo
         dataset. Without this task, the dataset would lack any
         Follow-up exercise, leaving the third of four task types
         untested.
      6. NO AUTOMATIC TRANSITION FROM PENDING TO IN PROGRESS WHEN
         THIS TASK IS CLOSED. Per AAP Section 0.5.5, Pending -> In
         Progress transitions are operator-initiated, not
         auto-triggered by task closure. The seed data correctly
         demonstrates a Pending case with an Open task, but
         resolving the task does NOT automatically change the case
         status. The clear_pending_reason_on_inprogress business
         rule fires on the OPERATOR-INITIATED Pending -> In
         Progress transition, not on task-closure events.
      7. BUILD AGENT COMPUTES due_date DYNAMICALLY at file-
         generation time so that the relative offset (+2 days) is
         preserved across importation timeframes. The actual
         stored value (2026-05-03) is the static result of today
         + 2 days evaluated at this file's generation time
         (today = 2026-05-01 per the build environment date).
      8. NO PII. The "Follow up with requester" subject is
         generic. "Follow up" is an agent-activity descriptor,
         not a person's name. "with requester" is a generic
         preposition+role-label phrase, not a real person or
         organization. No real names, real email addresses, real
         phone numbers, or real organization names appear
         anywhere in this file. The synthetic identifiers
         ("x_[scope]_demo_agent", "CASE0000004") are scoped
         placeholders or auto-numbered identifiers with no
         real-world correspondence.
      9. ELEMENT ORDERING IS STRICTLY ALPHABETICAL. The element
         ordering in this file (within the inner
         <x_[scope]_case_task> element) is: assigned_to, case,
         due_date, status, subject, sys_class_name,
         sys_created_by, sys_id, sys_package, sys_scope,
         sys_update_name, type. This matches the strict
         alphabetical convention used by every peer task file
         (04, 05, 06, 07, 08) and every other peer record file
         in the scoped Update Set artifacts.
     10. THIS TASK IS THE SOLE CHILD OF CASE 04. No other demo
         task references CASE0000004. This makes the task-04
         pairing the definitive exercise of the case-04-task
         association in the demo dataset. Sibling cases 03, 05,
         and 08 each have multiple child tasks (case 03: tasks
         01, 02; case 05: tasks 04, 05; case 08: tasks 06, 07);
         case 09 has one task (task 08); case 04 has one task
         (this task). Cases 01, 02, 06, 07, and 10 have zero
         demo tasks (those cases exercise non-task-related
         lifecycle points: Draft, Open, Open Complaint, Resolved
         Complaint, Closed Complaint).
-->
<record_update table="x_[scope]_case_task">
    <x_[scope]_case_task action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <assigned_to display_value="x_[scope]_demo_agent">x_[scope]_demo_agent</assigned_to>
        <case display_value="CASE0000004">CASE0000004</case>
        <due_date>2026-05-03</due_date>
        <status>Open</status>
        <subject>Demo task 03: Follow up with requester</subject>
        <sys_class_name>x_[scope]_case_task</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_id>922ef8bd877c160b4468ddfe919d8a52</sys_id>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_[scope]">x_[scope]</sys_package>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_[scope]</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>x_[scope]_case_task_demo_03</sys_update_name>
        <type>Follow-up</type>
    </x_[scope]_case_task>
</record_update>
