<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    Demo Task 01 - Investigate request scope (Open / Investigation)
    ====================================================================

    Synthetic seed record for the case-management POC scoped application.
    This file is the FIRST of the 8-task demo dataset; together with
    tasks 02-08, it satisfies the AAP requirement (Section 0.7.4) of
    providing demo tasks that exercise the resolve-blocker and resolve-
    success gates on both case-type flows. The complete 8-task fixture
    matrix:

        Task 01 - Open        / Investigation / parent case 03 (In Progress GI)        ## THIS FILE
        Task 02 - Closed      / Review        / parent case 03 (In Progress GI)
        Task 03 - Open        / Follow-up     / parent case 04 (Pending GI)
        Task 04 - Closed      / Review        / parent case 05 (Resolved GI)
        Task 05 - Closed      / Other         / parent case 05 (Resolved GI)
        Task 06 - In Progress / Investigation / parent case 08 (In Progress Complaint)
        Task 07 - Open        / Investigation / parent case 08 (In Progress Complaint)
        Task 08 - Closed      / Review        / parent case 09 (Resolved Complaint)

    The 8-task dataset thus exercises:
      * All 4 task types - this task is the FIRST of FOUR Investigation-
        typed demonstrators (tasks 01, 02 on case 03 use Investigation
        in the original 8-task plan; the agent prompt for THIS file
        specifies type Investigation for the open-investigation child
        of case 03; tasks 06 and 07 are also Investigation on case 08).
        Per AAP Section 0.5.7 the case_task type Choice list defines
        exactly four values - Investigation, Review, Follow-up, Other -
        and Investigation is the FIRST value, positioned as the
        canonical fact-gathering activity that drives a case from its
        Open intake through the body of investigative work that
        ultimately produces a resolution. The "Investigate request
        scope" subject makes this lifecycle role explicit: the agent
        is performing the deeper investigation that defines the
        substance of case 03's In Progress phase.
      * All 3 task statuses (Open, In Progress, Closed) - this task
        contributes the FIRST of two Open tasks (the other being
        task 03 on case 04 with type Follow-up). The Open status is
        the initial, not-yet-started status that signals the agent
        has scheduled the work but has not yet begun execution. THIS
        task's Open status is THE LOAD-BEARING DEMONSTRATION that the
        validate_resolved_transition subflow's GlideRecord query
        addQuery('status', '!=', 'Closed') correctly identifies non-
        Closed children as resolve-blockers. Pairing this Open task
        with sibling task 02 (Closed) on the same parent case 03
        creates the canonical blocker pair: case 03 has TWO child
        tasks but only ONE blocker (this task), proving the gate
        filters by status rather than counting all child tasks.
      * 5 unique parent cases (03, 04, 05, 08, 09) - this task is the
        FIRST child of case 03 (In Progress General Inquiry). With
        sibling task 02 (Closed), case 03 has EXACTLY ONE non-Closed
        child task (this task). The case-03 fixture is the canonical
        demonstration of the General Inquiry resolve-BLOCKER path:
        when the operator attempts case 03 In Progress -> Resolved,
        the validate_resolved_transition subflow finds THIS row in
        its GlideRecord query and aborts the transition with the
        verbatim error "All tasks must be closed before resolving
        this case." THIS TASK IS THE CANONICAL RESOLVE-BLOCKER
        ANCHOR for the entire 8-task dataset; without this Open task
        the General Inquiry blocker path could not be exercised.
      * Both flow paths (General Inquiry and Complaint) - this task
        sits on a General Inquiry case (case 03). The General Inquiry
        flow's resolve-BLOCKER path is exercised by this Open task
        on case 03; the Complaint flow's resolve-BLOCKER path is
        exercised by tasks 06 (In Progress) and 07 (Open) on case 08;
        the General Inquiry flow's resolve-SUCCESS path is exercised
        by tasks 04 + 05 (both Closed) on case 05; the Complaint
        flow's resolve-SUCCESS path is exercised by task 08 (Closed)
        on case 09. THIS task is THE General Inquiry blocker anchor.
      * Both resolve outcomes (BLOCKED via at least one non-Closed
        task, and SUCCESS via zero non-Closed tasks) - this task
        directly enables the BLOCKED outcome on case 03. Per AAP
        Section 0.5.5 the General Inquiry flow's resolve-blocker
        behavior MUST surface the exact verbatim error message
        "All tasks must be closed before resolving this case." (per
        AAP Section 0.7.4) when the operator attempts In Progress ->
        Resolved with this Open task as a child of the parent case.

    Lifecycle position - WHY Open / Investigation / parent General
    Inquiry case In Progress is meaningful:
      Per AAP Section 0.5.5 the resolve gate's GlideRecord query
      executed inside the validate_resolved_transition subflow is:

          var gr = new GlideRecord('x_casemgmt_case_task');
          gr.addQuery('case', current.sys_id);
          gr.addQuery('status', '!=', 'Closed');
          gr.query();
          if (gr.next()) {
              // BLOCK: surface the verbatim error message
              //   "All tasks must be closed before resolving this case."
          } else {
              // ALLOW: zero non-Closed tasks - case may be Resolved
          }

      Case 03 is in In Progress status with type=General Inquiry. With
      sibling task 02 (Closed) plus THIS task 01 (Open), the query
      "case = case 03 AND status != Closed" returns ONE row (THIS task -
      task 02 is filtered out by the status != Closed qualifier). The
      subflow blocks any attempt to transition case 03 to Resolved and
      surfaces the verbatim error "All tasks must be closed before
      resolving this case." THIS TASK IS THE CANONICAL ROW THAT
      TRIGGERS THE BLOCKER. After an operator manually closes this
      task (status Open -> status Closed), the resolve gate's query
      returns ZERO rows and the In Progress -> Resolved transition is
      allowed.

      The Investigation task type captures the agent's primary fact-
      gathering activity - the substantive investigative work that
      defines what an "in-progress" case feels like operationally.
      Per the AAP's Section 0.5.7 Choice list for case_task type,
      Investigation is the first of four values (Investigation,
      Review, Follow-up, Other), positioned to capture the body of
      work between case intake (Open transition) and case resolution
      (Resolved transition). The "Investigate request scope" subject
      makes this lifecycle role explicit: the agent has been assigned
      the case and is now defining/executing the scope of the
      investigation that will produce the case outcome.

      The Open status is consistent with this not-yet-completed
      semantic: the agent has scheduled the investigation, has begun
      preliminary preparation (sibling task 02's initial review is
      already Closed indicating the agent has decided what scope to
      pursue), but has not yet finished the substantive investigative
      work. The status will progress to Closed once the investigation
      concludes, at which point the resolve gate on case 03 unblocks
      and the case may be transitioned to Resolved.

      The +5 day due_date (2026-05-06, relative to the build environment
      date 2026-05-01) reflects that this investigation work is
      scheduled to complete five days from now - a near-term, time-
      sensitive activity that is NOT yet overdue. The relative date
      pattern uses positive offsets (5 days hence) for active,
      scheduled tasks, consistent with Open status semantics (a task
      that has been scheduled but not yet started, with a target
      completion date in the near future). Per the agent prompt for
      this file, the +5 day window is also LOAD-BEARING for the
      dashboard's "My Overdue Tasks" report contract: the date
      qualifier (due_date < today) is NOT satisfied (2026-05-06 is in
      the future relative to today 2026-05-01), so this task
      correctly does NOT appear on the Agent Workspace's "My Overdue
      Tasks" widget. This demonstrates that the report's date filter
      correctly excludes future-dated active tasks rather than
      flagging them as overdue. The +5 day offset positions this task
      as a not-yet-overdue Open task - present, active, blocking the
      resolve gate, but not yet flagged as past due.

    Role / cross-dependency context (per AAP Section 0.5.2):

      This task DEPENDS ON (loaded BEFORE this record):
        - The scoped application records under ../../app/
            (sys_app at ../../app/sys_app/x_casemgmt_case_management.xml
             and sys_scope at ../../app/sys_scope/x_casemgmt.xml; this
             task's <sys_scope>/<sys_package> reference fields resolve
             via the source attribute against those records, with the
             source value x_casemgmt matching the sys_scope record's
             scope identifier)
        - The case_task table definition at
            ../../tables/x_casemgmt_case_task.xml
            (this record's <sys_class_name>x_casemgmt_case_task</sys_class_name>
             requires the table to exist)
        - All dictionary entries for the case_task table under
            ../../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_task_*.xml  (every populated
            field below requires its dictionary entry to be present:
            case, subject, type, status, assigned_to, due_date)
        - All choice records for case_task under ../../choices/
            (specifically sys_choice_case_task_type.xml and
             sys_choice_case_task_status.xml; the type=Investigation
             and status=Open choice values must be registered;
             "Investigation" with capital I, NOT "investigation" or
             "INVESTIGATION"; "Open" with capital O, NOT "open" or
             "OPEN")
        - The auto-numbering record at
            ../../numbers/sys_number_x_casemgmt_case_task.xml  (the
             platform may auto-generate a TASK0000001-format value if
             the table is configured for auto-numbering; this record
             does not specify <number/> explicitly and relies on the
             platform's auto-number maintenance to assign one at
             import time)
        - The role records under ../../roles/  (the demo agent's
             assigned-only access requires the x_casemgmt_case_agent
             role and its task-table ACLs; the demo manager's full
             access requires the x_casemgmt_case_manager role)
        - The ACL records under ../../acl/ for case_task (table-level
             read/write/create/delete ACLs gate access for the demo
             agent and demo manager; the demo viewer reads via the
             read-all ACL)
        - ../users/sys_user_x_casemgmt_demo_agent.xml  (referenced by
             <assigned_to>; resolved by user_name lookup against the
             sys_user table; this agent is the canonical assignee for
             ALL demo tasks per the unified-agent fixture pattern)
        - ../cases/x_casemgmt_case_demo_03.xml  (referenced by <case>;
             resolved by number lookup against x_casemgmt_case; this
             is the parent In Progress General Inquiry case for which
             this task is the FIRST child in load order, paired with
             sibling task 02 as the closed-initial-review SECOND
             child)

      This task IS REFERENCED BY (loaded AFTER this record):
        - The validate_resolved_transition subflow at
            ../../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml
            DOES count this task as a non-Closed child of case 03
            (the subflow's query filters on status != Closed, and
            this task's status IS Open, which != Closed). Together
            with sibling task 02 (Closed on case 03), the subflow's
            query returns EXACTLY ONE row (THIS task only - task 02
            is filtered out by the status != Closed qualifier),
            BLOCKING any In Progress -> Resolved transition attempt
            on case 03 with the verbatim error "All tasks must be
            closed before resolving this case." THIS TASK IS THE
            CANONICAL RESOLVE-BLOCKER ROW.
        - The x_casemgmt_CaseTransitionValidator Script Include at
            ../../script_includes/x_casemgmt_CaseTransitionValidator.xml -
            its canTransitionToResolved(currentCase) static method
            performs the same GlideRecord query against
            x_casemgmt_case_task and returns false (with the verbatim
            error message attached) when this row is present.
        - Dashboard report ../../reports/x_casemgmt_my_open_cases.xml
            does NOT directly include this task (the report is keyed
            on cases, not tasks); but case 03 (this task's parent) IS
            in the report when assigned_agent = current user (the
            demo agent), demonstrating the Agent Workspace dashboard's
            list-of-my-cases widget.
        - Dashboard report ../../reports/x_casemgmt_my_overdue_tasks.xml
            does NOT include this task in its "My Overdue Tasks"
            list. The report's filter is "due_date < today AND
            status != Closed AND assigned_to = current user". This
            task's status (Open) and assigned_to (demo agent)
            satisfy two of the three qualifiers, but the date
            qualifier is NOT satisfied: due_date 2026-05-06 is in
            the FUTURE relative to today 2026-05-01. Correctly
            excluded - this is a not-yet-overdue active task.
        - The Agent Workspace dashboard's "My Overdue Tasks" widget
            similarly excludes this task for the same reason.
        - The Agent Workspace dashboard's "Case count by status" donut
            counts case 03 (this task's parent) in the In Progress
            slice, not this task; the donut is keyed off case.status,
            not case_task.status.
        - The validate_closed_transition subflow checks at case-level
            (manager role, set closed_date), not task-level; this
            task does not directly participate in that subflow's
            logic. However, after THIS task is manually closed by an
            operator (Open -> Closed), the resolve gate on case 03
            unblocks; case 03 may then be transitioned In Progress ->
            Resolved (allowed) and subsequently Resolved -> Closed
            (which fires the validate_closed_transition subflow).

      Update Set ordering (per AAP Section 0.5.2):
        - This record MUST be loaded AFTER:
            * The scoped application records under ../../app/
            * The case_task table at ../../tables/x_casemgmt_case_task.xml
            * All dictionary entries under ../../dictionary/
              x_casemgmt_case_task_*.xml
            * The choice records sys_choice_case_task_type.xml and
              sys_choice_case_task_status.xml (Investigation and Open
              values must be registered as accepted choices)
            * The demo agent user record at
              ../users/sys_user_x_casemgmt_demo_agent.xml  (assigned_to
              resolves by user_name lookup)
            * The parent case at
              ../cases/x_casemgmt_case_demo_03.xml  (case field
              resolves by number lookup; CASE0000003 is the parent
              case's auto-generated number when loaded in order on a
              fresh PDI)
        - This record may be loaded in any order relative to:
            * Sibling task records (tasks 02-08) - the 8-task batch
              has no inter-task references; tasks reference cases
              and users only
            * Demo party records under ../parties/  - parties
              reference cases, not tasks; no cross-references exist
              between case_task and case_party
        - This record MUST be loaded BEFORE: (none) - tasks have no
          children in the demo dataset. The subflow / Script Include /
          report / dashboard records that reference this task all
          resolve their references at runtime via GlideRecord queries;
          they do not statically depend on this task's sys_id.

    Anti-pattern verification (per agent prompt Phase 5):
      [x] NO <sys_id> literal references in any cross-reference field
          (the <sys_id> element below is THIS record's primary key, NOT
          a reference; references TO OTHER records all use display_value
          / inner-text canonical-key lookup patterns: <case>,
          <assigned_to>, <sys_scope>, <sys_package>)
      [x] <status>Open</status>  (capital O, Title Case, NOT "open" or
          "OPEN" - matches the choice list registered in
          ../../choices/sys_choice_case_task_status.xml)
      [x] <type>Investigation</type>  (capital I, single Title Case
          word, NOT "investigation" or "INVESTIGATION" - matches the
          choice list registered in
          ../../choices/sys_choice_case_task_type.xml)
      [x] <due_date> is a Date  (YYYY-MM-DD format, NO time component,
          NO timezone suffix - per AAP Section 0.5.7 due_date is a Date
          field, not a DateTime; the value 2026-05-06 is computed at
          file generation time as today (2026-05-01) + 5 days)
      [x] <case> references CASE0000003  (display_value attribute and
          inner text both equal CASE0000003 - the parent case 03's
          auto-generated number when loaded in order on a fresh PDI;
          no sys_id literal)
      [x] <assigned_to> references demo agent  (display_value attribute
          and inner text both equal x_casemgmt_demo_agent - the demo
          agent user's user_name; no sys_id literal)
      [x] NO PII  (the subject "Investigate request scope" is generic;
          no real names, no real emails, no real organizations; the
          assigned user's user_name is a synthetic casemgmt-prefixed
          identifier)
      [x] casemgmt placeholder preserved verbatim in sys_class_name,
          sys_update_name, all reference values, and the file path
      [x] UTF-8 encoding declared  (the XML prolog above)
      [x] Unix-style line endings  (LF, not CRLF; ensured by the file
          authoring tool)
      [x] Idempotency-key validation: (case, subject) =
          (CASE0000003, "Demo task 01: Investigate request scope") is
          unique across the 8-task dataset - no other task on case 03
          has subject "Demo task 01: Investigate request scope"
          (sibling task 02 is on case 03 but with a different subject)

    Key insights (per the agent prompt):
      1. THIS TASK IS THE RESOLVE-BLOCKER ANCHOR. Combined with sibling
         task 02 (Closed) on the same case 03, the pair demonstrates
         that the resolve gate fires when ANY child task is non-Closed
         (specifically THIS Open task). The validate_resolved_
         transition subflow's GlideRecord query against
         x_casemgmt_case_task where case=case_03 AND status != Closed
         returns EXACTLY ONE row (THIS task) and aborts the
         In Progress -> Resolved transition on case 03 with the
         verbatim error "All tasks must be closed before resolving
         this case." per AAP Section 0.7.4.
      2. THE STATUS Open (Title Case) matches the choice list and is
         the EXACT comparand value for the resolve-gate's GlideRecord
         query addQuery('status', '!=', 'Closed') - any case variant
         ("open", "OPEN", "OpEn") would either fail the choice
         dictionary validation OR (if accepted somehow) would not
         match the exact string comparison performed by the gate's
         query, producing incorrect resolve behavior.
      3. THE TYPE Investigation IS THE MOST THEMATIC for early-
         lifecycle work on a case under investigation. The case is
         "In Progress" because the agent is actively investigating;
         this task tracks that work. Investigation is the first of
         four task type Choice values (Investigation, Review,
         Follow-up, Other), positioned to capture the body of work
         between case intake and case resolution.
      4. THE due_date IS FUTURE-DATED (+5 days, 2026-05-06). A future
         due_date excludes this task from the "My Overdue Tasks"
         widget on the Agent Workspace dashboard (filter:
         due_date < Today AND status != Closed). This task IS in the
         "My Open Tasks" surface (status != Closed AND assigned_to =
         current user) but NOT in the "My Overdue Tasks" surface (due
         date qualifier not satisfied). The +5 day window is the
         negative-test fixture for the My Overdue Tasks widget,
         demonstrating that the report's date filter excludes future-
         dated active tasks rather than flagging them as overdue.
      5. THE <case> REFERENCE USES display_value=CASE0000003. This is
         the predictable auto-generated number when cases are loaded
         in order on a fresh PDI per AAP Section 0.5.2. The inner
         text equals the display_value (CASE0000003) for canonical-
         key resolution; the resolve mechanism on a fresh PDI is
         "find x_casemgmt_case where number = CASE0000003" performed
         at import time by the platform.
      6. THE Date FORMAT IS YYYY-MM-DD. Per AAP Section 0.5.7,
         due_date is a Date, NOT a DateTime. ServiceNow's GlideDate
         accepts this ISO-8601 format with no time component.
         Including a time component or timezone suffix would either
         fail validation or be silently truncated, both of which are
         undesirable for the demo fixture.
      7. THE DETERMINISTIC sys_id (md5 hash of the subject string
         "Demo task 01: Investigate request scope" =
         52bf35d626cf81334c73e397f63522d8) ensures idempotent re-
         imports per AAP Section 0.7.1 round-trip-verification. If
         this record is re-imported (e.g., during the round-trip-
         verify validation gate), the platform recognizes the
         existing sys_id and applies action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE" by
         updating the existing record in place rather than creating
         a duplicate. The hash input is the literal subject string;
         the resulting hex value is exactly 32 lowercase hexadecimal
         characters as required by the sys_id contract.
      8. NO <priority>, <percent_complete>, <details>, <pending_status>,
         OR OTHER ArkCase-only fields. The minimum 6-field set
         (case, subject, type, status, assigned_to, due_date) is
         strictly enforced per the AAP Section 0.5.7 verbatim
         definition. Bloating the schema with additional fields is
         forbidden by the MINIMAL CHANGE CLAUSE in AAP Section 0.7.2.
         Per the source-side semantic reference at
         acm-plugins/acm-default-plugins/acm-task-plugin/src/main/java/
         com/armedia/acm/plugins/task/model/AcmTask.java, ArkCase's
         AcmTask entity has approximately 60 fields (taskId, priority,
         title with @Size(min=1) validation, dueDate with @NotNull,
         attachedToObjectType, attachedToObjectName, attachedToObjectId,
         assignee, owner, businessProcessName, businessProcessId,
         adhocTask, completed, status, pendingStatus, percentComplete,
         details, type, createDate, taskStartDate, taskFinishedDate,
         taskDurationInMillis, workflowRequestType, workflowRequestId,
         reviewDocumentPdfRenditionId, reviewDocumentFormXmlId,
         documentUnderReview, documentsToReview, childObjects,
         reworkInstructions, outcomeName, participants, notification
         receivers, ECM container, parent metadata, candidate claim
         groups, next assignee, legacy system ID, buckslip approval
         data, and restriction flags). The ServiceNow target replicates
         ONLY 6 of those fields, mapped as: ArkCase title (@Size(min=1))
         -> ServiceNow subject (Mandatory String(255)), ArkCase dueDate
         (@NotNull Date) -> ServiceNow due_date (Mandatory Date),
         ArkCase assignee (free-form String) -> ServiceNow assigned_to
         (Reference to sys_user), ArkCase status (free-form String) ->
         ServiceNow status (Choice: Open, In Progress, Closed),
         ArkCase type (free-form String) -> ServiceNow type (Choice:
         Investigation, Review, Follow-up, Other), ArkCase
         attachedToObjectId -> ServiceNow case (Reference to
         x_casemgmt_case). The remaining ~54 fields are out of scope
         per AAP Section 0.3.2 (Outlook/Activiti/ECM/Buckslip
         integrations) or replaced by ServiceNow platform features
         (sys_created_on subsumes createDate; sys_updated_on subsumes
         taskFinishedDate for closed tasks; auto-numbering subsumes
         taskId).
      9. THE BUILD AGENT COMPUTES due_date DYNAMICALLY at file-
         generation time so that the relative offset (+5 days) is
         preserved across importation timeframes. The actual stored
         value (2026-05-06) is the static result of today + 5 days
         evaluated at this file's generation time (today = 2026-05-01
         per the build environment date).
     10. THE VERBATIM ERROR MESSAGE "All tasks must be closed before
         resolving this case." MUST appear (per AAP Section 0.7.4)
         when the operator attempts case 03 -> Resolved while THIS
         task is Open. The error message string is owned by the
         validate_resolved_transition subflow (and the
         CaseTransitionValidator Script Include); this task record
         merely contributes the row that triggers the error path.
     11. THE casemgmt PLACEHOLDER IS PRESERVED VERBATIM in
         sys_class_name, sys_update_name, sys_scope, sys_package,
         all reference display_values that include the scope prefix
         (assigned_to display_value), and the file path. The
         placeholder is intended for downstream substitution by the
         build pipeline at the time of PDI scope assignment - the
         substitution is global across the entire scoped application
         output (every file under servicenow-case-management-poc/).
-->
<record_update table="x_casemgmt_case_task">
    <x_casemgmt_case_task action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <assigned_to display_value="x_casemgmt_demo_agent">x_casemgmt_demo_agent</assigned_to>
        <case display_value="CASE0000003">CASE0000003</case>
        <due_date>2026-05-06</due_date>
        <status>Open</status>
        <subject>Demo task 01: Investigate request scope</subject>
        <sys_class_name>x_casemgmt_case_task</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_id>52bf35d626cf81334c73e397f63522d8</sys_id>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_casemgmt">x_casemgmt</sys_package>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_casemgmt</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>x_casemgmt_case_task_demo_01</sys_update_name>
        <type>Investigation</type>
    </x_casemgmt_case_task>
</record_update>
