<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    Demo Task 02 - Initial review complete (Closed / Review)
    ====================================================================

    Synthetic seed record for the case-management POC scoped application.
    This file is the SECOND of the 8-task demo dataset; together with
    tasks 01 and 03 through 08, it satisfies the AAP requirement
    (Section 0.7.4) of providing demo tasks that exercise the resolve-
    blocker and resolve-success gates on both case-type flows. The
    complete 8-task fixture matrix:

        Task 01 - Open        / Investigation / parent case 03 (In Progress GI)
        Task 02 - Closed      / Review        / parent case 03 (In Progress GI)  ## THIS FILE
        Task 03 - Open        / Follow-up     / parent case 04 (Pending GI)
        Task 04 - Closed      / Review        / parent case 05 (Resolved GI)
        Task 05 - Closed      / Other         / parent case 05 (Resolved GI)
        Task 06 - In Progress / Investigation / parent case 08 (In Progress Complaint)
        Task 07 - Open        / Investigation / parent case 08 (In Progress Complaint)
        Task 08 - Closed      / Review        / parent case 09 (Resolved Complaint)

    The 8-task dataset thus exercises:
      * All 4 task types - this task is one of three Review-typed
        demonstrators (the others being task 04 on case 05 and task 08
        on case 09); Review represents the agent's pre-resolution or
        intermediate validation / sign-off activity, where the case
        worker reads through the case body, confirms a milestone has
        been reached, and either advances or pauses the case lifecycle.
        Per AAP Section 0.5.7 the case_task type Choice list defines
        exactly four values - Investigation, Review, Follow-up, Other -
        and Review is the second value. This task ALSO carries
        operational significance distinct from the other two Review
        tasks: where tasks 04 and 08 are FINAL pre-resolution reviews
        (paired with Resolved-status parent cases), THIS task is an
        INITIAL scope-review activity that occurred BEFORE the deeper
        investigation work tracked by sibling task 01 began. The agent
        first performed an initial review of the request to determine
        the appropriate next steps (this task), closed that review
        task, then opened the deeper investigation task (task 01,
        currently Open).
      * All 3 task statuses (Open, In Progress, Closed) - this task
        contributes the FIRST of four Closed tasks (the others are
        tasks 04, 05, and 08); the Closed status is the terminal task
        status that satisfies the validate_resolved_transition
        subflow's "all child tasks must be Closed" gate. THIS task's
        Closed status is THE LOAD-BEARING DEMONSTRATION that the
        resolve gate's GlideRecord query (status != Closed) filters
        OUT closed tasks rather than counting them - meaning this task
        does NOT contribute to the resolve-blocker count for case 03
        even though it IS a child of case 03. The resolve blocker for
        case 03 comes from sibling task 01 (Open), not from this task.
      * 5 unique parent cases (03, 04, 05, 08, 09) - this task is the
        SECOND child of case 03 (the first being task 01); together,
        tasks 01 + 02 give case 03 EXACTLY ONE non-Closed child task
        (task 01 is Open; this task 02 is Closed). The case-03 fixture
        is the canonical demonstration that the resolve gate counts
        ONLY non-Closed tasks - if the gate naively counted all child
        tasks it would block case 03 with a count of 2; if the gate
        correctly filters by status != Closed it identifies task 01 as
        the SOLE blocker (count of 1).
      * Both flow paths (General Inquiry and Complaint) - this task
        sits on a General Inquiry case (case 03). The General Inquiry
        flow's resolve-BLOCKER path is exercised by tasks 01 + 02 on
        case 03; the General Inquiry flow's resolve-SUCCESS path is
        exercised by tasks 04 + 05 on case 05. THIS task is an
        ESSENTIAL HALF of the General Inquiry resolve-blocker
        demonstration: without this Closed sibling, the resolve gate
        could be misinterpreted as "blocks if any child exists"
        rather than "blocks if any non-Closed child exists." This
        task's existence as a Closed sibling of an Open task on the
        same parent case is what proves the gate's status-filtering
        semantics.
      * Both resolve outcomes (BLOCKED via at least one non-Closed task,
        and SUCCESS via zero non-Closed tasks) - this task does NOT
        directly enable a resolve-success path, but it IS the
        canonical FILTERED-OUT task that proves the resolve gate's
        query is selective rather than total. The blocker on case 03
        is task 01 alone; this Closed task is correctly excluded.

    Lifecycle position - WHY Closed / Review / parent General Inquiry case
    In Progress is meaningful:
      Per AAP Section 0.5.5 the resolve gate's GlideRecord query
      executed inside the validate_resolved_transition subflow is:

          var gr = new GlideRecord('x_casemgmt_case_task');
          gr.addQuery('case', current.sys_id);
          gr.addQuery('status', '!=', 'Closed');
          gr.query();
          if (gr.next()) {
              // BLOCK: surface the verbatim error message
              //   "All tasks must be closed before resolving this case."
          } else {
              // ALLOW: zero non-Closed tasks - case may be Resolved
          }

      Case 03 is in In Progress status with type=General Inquiry. With
      sibling task 01 (Open) plus THIS task 02 (Closed), the query
      "case = case 03 AND status != Closed" returns ONE row (task 01
      only - this task is FILTERED OUT by the status != Closed
      qualifier). The subflow blocks any attempt to transition case 03
      to Resolved and surfaces the verbatim error "All tasks must be
      closed before resolving this case." THIS TASK IS THE CANONICAL
      DEMONSTRATION THAT THE RESOLVE GATE'S STATUS-FILTERING WORKS
      CORRECTLY. Where task 01 IS the resolve-blocker for case 03,
      THIS task PROVES the gate does not over-count - it does not
      treat all child tasks as blockers, only the non-Closed ones.

      The Review task type captures the agent's pre-action validation
      work - in this case, the INITIAL scope review the agent
      performed before deciding to launch a deeper investigation. Per
      the AAP's Section 0.5.7 Choice list for case_task type, Review
      is the second of four values (Investigation, Review, Follow-up,
      Other), positioned to capture validation activities that bracket
      either the start or the end of an investigation. The "Initial
      review complete" subject makes this lifecycle role explicit: the
      agent received the case, performed an initial review of its
      scope and severity, determined that further investigation was
      needed, marked the review task Closed, and then created the
      Investigation task (task 01) that remains Open while the deeper
      work proceeds.

      The Closed status is consistent with this completed-review
      semantic: the agent reviewed the case scope, made a decision
      (proceed with investigation), and closed the review task before
      the case progressed from Open into In Progress. The transition
      narrative is therefore: case 03 was created in Draft, was
      assigned to a group/agent (Open transition), the agent performed
      THIS initial review and closed it, the agent then launched task
      01 (Investigation) and transitioned the case to In Progress
      (where it currently sits awaiting completion of task 01).

      The -3 day due_date reflects that the initial-review task was
      due three days ago (relative to the build environment date
      2026-05-01, i.e., 2026-04-28) and was completed on or before
      that date. The -3 day offset is deliberately distant from the
      sibling task 01's -3 day due_date (also -3 days) AND from tasks
      04/05's -1 day due_date - indicating that this initial review
      occurred earlier than the closing reviews on case 05 and at the
      same canonical "task is due/completed" interval as task 01. The
      relative date pattern uses negative offsets (3 days ago) for
      completed tasks, consistent with Closed status semantics (a
      task that has been started, performed, and closed, with a
      target completion date that is now in the past). The -3 day
      window is also load-bearing for the dashboard's "My Overdue
      Tasks" report contract: although the date qualifier
      (due_date < today) is satisfied, the status qualifier
      (status != Closed) excludes this task. THIS DEMONSTRATES THAT
      THE REPORT CORRECTLY FILTERS OUT COMPLETED-BUT-PAST-DUE TASKS
      RATHER THAN INCORRECTLY FLAGGING THEM AS OVERDUE - a critical
      negative-test fixture for the My Overdue Tasks widget. By
      contrast, sibling task 01 has the SAME -3 day due_date but
      Open status, making task 01 the positive-test fixture for the
      My Overdue Tasks widget and this task the negative-test fixture
      proving the status filter excludes the closed-and-past-due
      case.

    Role / cross-dependency context (per AAP Section 0.5.2):

      This task DEPENDS ON (loaded BEFORE this record):
        - The scoped application records under ../../app/
            (sys_app and sys_scope; this task's <sys_scope>/<sys_package>
             reference fields resolve via the source attribute against
             those records)
        - The case_task table definition at
            ../../tables/x_casemgmt_case_task.xml
            (this record's <sys_class_name>x_casemgmt_case_task</sys_class_name>
             requires the table to exist)
        - All dictionary entries for the case_task table under
            ../../dictionary/x_casemgmt_case_task_*.xml  (every populated
            field below requires its dictionary entry to be present:
            case, subject, type, status, assigned_to, due_date)
        - All choice records for case_task under ../../choices/
            (specifically sys_choice_case_task_type.xml and
             sys_choice_case_task_status.xml; the type=Review and
             status=Closed choice values must be registered; "Review"
             with capital R, not "review" or "REVIEW"; "Closed" with
             capital C, not "closed" or "CLOSED")
        - The auto-numbering record at
            ../../numbers/sys_number_x_casemgmt_case_task.xml  (the
             platform may auto-generate a TASK0000002-format value if
             the table is configured for auto-numbering; this record
             does not specify <number/> explicitly and relies on the
             platform's auto-number maintenance to assign one at
             import time)
        - The role records under ../../roles/  (the demo agent's
             assigned-only access requires the x_casemgmt_case_agent
             role and its task-table ACLs; the demo manager's full
             access requires the x_casemgmt_case_manager role)
        - The ACL records under ../../acl/ for case_task (table-level
             read/write/create/delete ACLs gate access for the demo
             agent and demo manager; the demo viewer reads via the
             read-all ACL)
        - ../users/sys_user_x_casemgmt_demo_agent.xml  (referenced by
             <assigned_to>; resolved by user_name lookup against the
             sys_user table; this agent is the canonical assignee for
             ALL demo tasks per the unified-agent fixture pattern)
        - ../cases/x_casemgmt_case_demo_03.xml  (referenced by <case>;
             resolved by number lookup against x_casemgmt_case; this
             is the parent In Progress General Inquiry case for
             which this task is the closed-initial-review SECOND
             child task in the demo dataset, paired with the open-
             investigation FIRST child task 01)

      This task IS REFERENCED BY (loaded AFTER this record):
        - The validate_resolved_transition subflow at
            ../../flows/sub_flows/validate_resolved_transition.xml
            DOES NOT count this task as a non-Closed child of case 03
            (the subflow's query filters on status != Closed, and
            this task's status IS Closed). Together with task 01
            (Open on case 03), the subflow's query returns EXACTLY
            ONE row (task 01 only), BLOCKING any In Progress ->
            Resolved transition attempt on case 03 with the verbatim
            error "All tasks must be closed before resolving this
            case." THIS TASK IS THE CANONICAL FILTERED-OUT TASK
            PROVING THE GATE'S STATUS-FILTERING SEMANTICS.
        - Dashboard report ../../reports/x_casemgmt_my_overdue_tasks.xml
            DOES NOT include this task in its "My Overdue Tasks" list;
            although the date qualifier is satisfied (due_date
            2026-04-28 is in the past relative to build-environment
            today 2026-05-01), the status qualifier excludes this
            task (status = Closed; the filter is status != Closed).
            This is the correct behavior for a completed task that
            should no longer appear on any agent's open-work surface,
            and demonstrates that the report's status filter is
            applied AFTER the date filter is applied.
        - The Agent Workspace dashboard's "My Overdue Tasks" widget
            similarly excludes this task for the same reason.
        - The Agent Workspace dashboard's "Case count by status" donut
            counts case 03 (this task's parent) in the In Progress
            slice, not this task; the donut is keyed off case.status,
            not case_task.status.
        - The validate_closed_transition subflow checks at case-level
            (manager role, set closed_date), not task-level; this
            task does not directly participate in that subflow's
            logic.

      Update Set ordering (per AAP Section 0.5.2):
        - This record MUST be loaded AFTER:
            * The scoped application records under ../../app/
            * The case_task table at ../../tables/x_casemgmt_case_task.xml
            * All dictionary entries under ../../dictionary/
              x_casemgmt_case_task_*.xml
            * The choice records sys_choice_case_task_type.xml and
              sys_choice_case_task_status.xml (Review and Closed
              values must be registered as accepted choices)
            * The demo agent user record at
              ../users/sys_user_x_casemgmt_demo_agent.xml  (assigned_to
              resolves by user_name lookup)
            * The parent case at
              ../cases/x_casemgmt_case_demo_03.xml  (case field
              resolves by number lookup; that case must exist before
              this task can reference it)
        - This record can be loaded BEFORE or AFTER its sibling task
          records (01, 03-08) since they are mutually independent
          (each task's only outbound references are to a case and a
          user, not to other tasks).
        - This record has NO downstream task dependents: tasks have
          no children of their own (no subtasks; the case_task table
          is leaf).

    Authoring rules honored (per AAP Sections 0.7.1 / 0.7.2 and the
    agent prompt's eight authoring rules):

      Rule 1 - Synthetic only (AAP Section 0.7.2 NO-PII clause):
        subject = "Demo task 02: Initial review complete"
                  (synthetic identifier using the literal word "Demo"
                   plus a numeral plus a generic case-handling-action
                   phrase "Initial review complete"; "Initial review"
                   is a generic activity descriptor naming the
                   beginning of the case-handling sequence, NOT a
                   real person's name or specific incident; "complete"
                   is a generic adjective indicating the activity has
                   been finished, not a real organization or location;
                   no PII; the wording emphasizes the task's lifecycle
                   role - the agent's first-pass review of the case
                   scope before deciding to launch a deeper
                   investigation, marked complete because that review
                   has been performed)
        NO description / NO details / NO comments fields populated;
        the task's primary content is captured in the subject alone.
        NO assignee email, phone, or other PII-bearing fields.

      Rule 2 - Choice value precision (CRITICAL FOR THIS TASK):
        type   = "Review"  (exactly as registered in
                  ../../choices/sys_choice_case_task_type.xml; the
                  second value of the four task types - Investigation,
                  Review, Follow-up, Other; capital R deliberate -
                  "Review" not "review" or "REVIEW" or any other
                  case variant; the choice is byte-for-byte
                  identical between <label> and <value> in the
                  choice record)
        status = "Closed"  (exactly as registered in
                  ../../choices/sys_choice_case_task_status.xml; the
                  third value of the three task statuses - Open,
                  In Progress, Closed; capital C deliberate - "Closed"
                  not "closed" or "CLOSED"; the choice is byte-for-
                  byte identical between <label> and <value> in the
                  choice record; "Closed" status is the EXACT string
                  the validate_resolved_transition subflow's query
                  compares against in the addQuery('status', '!=',
                  'Closed') clause)

      Rule 3 - Date format (AAP Section 0.5.7 due_date type Date):
        due_date = "2026-04-28"  (YYYY-MM-DD format, NOT
                  YYYY-MM-DDTHH:MM:SS DateTime format; case_task's
                  due_date dictionary entry is configured as a Date
                  type per AAP Section 0.5.7, which requires
                  YYYY-MM-DD format only; the value 2026-04-28 is
                  the static result of (build environment today
                  2026-05-01) - 3 days, evaluated at this file's
                  generation time)

      Rule 4 - Reference resolution by lookup key (AAP Section 0.5.2,
        no-hard-coded-sys_id constraint, AAP Section 0.7.2):
        <case>          resolves by number lookup against
                        x_casemgmt_case.number; display_value is the
                        canonical number "CASE0000003" of the parent
                        case (case 03); the inner text is the same
                        canonical number, NOT a sys_id literal; the
                        update set engine resolves the reference at
                        import time by querying for x_casemgmt_case
                        records with number = CASE0000003 (the parent
                        case 03 record was loaded earlier in the
                        update set, ensuring the lookup succeeds)
        <assigned_to>   resolves by user_name lookup against
                        sys_user.user_name; display_value is the
                        synthetic user_name "x_casemgmt_demo_agent";
                        the inner text is the same synthetic
                        user_name, NOT a sys_id literal; the update
                        set engine resolves the reference at import
                        time by querying for sys_user records with
                        user_name = x_casemgmt_demo_agent (the demo
                        agent record was loaded earlier in the update
                        set, ensuring the lookup succeeds)
        <sys_scope>     resolves by scope identifier; display_value
                        is the human-readable application name "Case
                        Management"; the inner text is the scope
                        identifier "x_casemgmt" which is the
                        scoped application's canonical scope name
                        (NOT a sys_id literal; the scope identifier
                        is human-readable and stable across PDIs)
        <sys_package>   resolves the same way; the source attribute
                        is "x_casemgmt" indicating the scope from
                        which this package is derived

      Rule 5 - Mandatory fields all populated (AAP Section 0.5.7):
        case          - mandatory; populated with CASE0000003 reference
        subject       - mandatory; populated with synthetic subject
        type          - mandatory; populated with "Review" choice
        status        - mandatory; populated with "Closed" choice
        assigned_to   - mandatory; populated with demo agent reference
        due_date      - mandatory; populated with 2026-04-28
        ALL six AAP-mandatory fields are populated.
        Standard housekeeping fields (sys_class_name, sys_created_by,
        sys_id, sys_package, sys_scope, sys_update_name) are also
        populated per ServiceNow Update Set XML conventions.

      Rule 6 - Scope binding (AAP Section 0.7.2 scoped-namespace-only
        constraint):
        sys_class_name  = "x_casemgmt_case_task"  (the scoped table
                          this record belongs to; literal "casemgmt"
                          placeholder preserved as required by the
                          AAP for downstream substitution by the
                          build pipeline at the time of PDI scope
                          assignment)
        sys_scope       = "x_casemgmt" (display_value "Case Management";
                          the scope identifier of the case-management
                          scoped application)
        sys_package     = "x_casemgmt" (display_value "Case Management",
                          source "x_casemgmt"; the package
                          identifier of the case-management scoped
                          application; matches sibling task records'
                          source attribute pattern for cross-task
                          consistency)
        sys_update_name = "x_casemgmt_case_task_demo_02"  (the
                          canonical update name encoding scope, table,
                          purpose, and ordinal index; matches the
                          file basename for grep-ability)
        File path also encodes scope: under
        servicenow-case-management-poc/seed-data/tasks/ (the seed
        data subdirectory of the scoped application output) and
        named "x_casemgmt_case_task_demo_02.xml" (literal placeholder
        preserved).

      Rule 7 - Idempotency anchor:
        The (case, subject) pair (CASE0000003,
        "Demo task 02: Initial review complete") is the idempotent
        key. No other task in the 8-task dataset shares this pair.
        The deterministic sys_id (md5 of the subject) ensures that
        re-importing this update set will UPDATE rather than
        DUPLICATE this record - the platform recognizes the existing
        sys_id and applies the action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE" semantic
        correctly. (case, subject) idempotency uniqueness check
        across the 8-task dataset:
          - Task 01: (CASE0000003, "Demo task 01: Investigate
            requester history")
          - Task 02: (CASE0000003,
            "Demo task 02: Initial review complete")  ## THIS FILE
          - Task 03: (CASE0000004, "Demo task 03: Follow up with
            requester")
          - Task 04: (CASE0000005, "Demo task 04: Final review for
            resolution")
          - Task 05: (CASE0000005, "Demo task 05: Post-resolution
            archive")
          - Task 06: (CASE0000008, "Demo task 06: Complaint
            investigation")
          - Task 07: (CASE0000008, "Demo task 07: Witness interview
            prep")
          - Task 08: (CASE0000009, "Demo task 08: Final complaint
            review")
        The pair (CASE0000003, "Demo task 02: Initial review
        complete") is unique - tasks 01 and 02 share the same parent
        case (CASE0000003) but have different subjects, ensuring
        idempotency of each within the dataset.

      Rule 8 - Scoped Update Set XML conventions:
        Root element  : <record_update table="x_casemgmt_case_task">
        Inner element : <x_casemgmt_case_task action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        Encoding      : UTF-8 declared in the XML prolog
        Line endings  : Unix (LF only)
        Indentation   : 4 spaces (matching sibling demo task records)
        Action attr   : "INSERT_OR_UPDATE" (allows re-import to
                        update an existing record by sys_id rather
                        than fail; combined with the deterministic
                        sys_id this guarantees idempotent imports)

    Anti-pattern verification (per agent prompt Phase 5):
      [x] <status>Closed</status> uses capital C (not "closed" or
          "CLOSED" or any mixed-case variant)
      [x] <type>Review</type> uses capital R (not "review" or "REVIEW"
          or any mixed-case variant)
      [x] <due_date>2026-04-28</due_date> is past-dated (~3 days ago
          from build env today 2026-05-01) and Date format
          (YYYY-MM-DD, not DateTime YYYY-MM-DDTHH:MM:SS)
      [x] <case display_value="CASE0000003">CASE0000003</case>
          references the parent case 03 by its canonical CASE-prefixed
          number (resolved by number lookup at import time)
      [x] <assigned_to display_value="x_casemgmt_demo_agent">
          x_casemgmt_demo_agent</assigned_to> references the demo
          agent by user_name (resolved by user_name lookup at import
          time)
      [x] NO PII anywhere - all fields use synthetic generic values
          ("Demo task", "Initial review complete", numeric ordinals,
          synthetic user_name "x_casemgmt_demo_agent", synthetic case
          number "CASE0000003")
      [x] NO sys_id literals in reference fields - the only sys_id
          appearing in this record is the deterministic md5-of-
          subject value used as THIS record's own sys_id (which is
          allowed because action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE" requires the
          record to assert its own sys_id; references TO OTHER
          records all use display_value/inner-text canonical-key
          lookup patterns)
      [x] casemgmt placeholder preserved verbatim in
          sys_class_name, sys_update_name, all reference values, and
          the file path
      [x] Idempotency-key validation: (case, subject) =
          (CASE0000003, "Demo task 02: Initial review complete") is
          unique across the 8-task dataset - no other task on case 03
          has subject "Demo task 02: Initial review complete"
          (task 01 is on case 03 but with a different subject).

    Key insights (per the agent prompt):
      1. THIS IS THE COMPLETED INITIAL REVIEW TASK ON CASE 03. It
         demonstrates that even when an agent has done initial work
         (review complete), other tasks can still be open
         (investigation), preventing case resolution. The lifecycle
         narrative: case received -> initial review (this task) ->
         deeper investigation (task 01, still Open) -> case will
         eventually be resolvable when task 01 is also closed.
      2. THIS TASK PROVES THE STATUS-FILTERING IN THE RESOLVE GATE.
         The validate_resolved_transition subflow does NOT just count
         tasks - it counts NON-CLOSED tasks via
         addQuery('status', '!=', 'Closed'). This task's
         status=Closed excludes it from the gate's blocker list. If
         a developer accidentally implemented the gate as
         "any child blocks resolve" (without the status filter),
         this fixture would surface that bug because the gate would
         incorrectly block case 03 with a count of 2 instead of 1.
      3. THE Review TASK TYPE matches "initial review" semantics. The
         agent reviewed the request scope before deciding to launch a
         deeper investigation. Review is the second of four task
         types (Investigation, Review, Follow-up, Other); it captures
         pre-action sign-off work that can occur at the start
         (initial review) or end (final review) of an investigation.
      4. THE due_date IS PAST-DATED (-3 days, 2026-04-28). This is
         consistent with status=Closed - the task was due 3 days ago
         and has been completed. The relative offset preserves the
         lifecycle semantic across importation timeframes (the
         actual stored value is the static result of today - 3 days
         evaluated at this file's generation time).
      5. THE Closed STATUS USES TITLE CASE Closed. This matches the
         choice list and is the EXACT string the resolve-gate's
         GlideRecord query compares against in the addQuery('status',
         '!=', 'Closed') clause. Any case variant ("closed",
         "CLOSED", "ClOsEd") would either fail the choice
         dictionary's value validation OR (if accepted somehow) would
         not match the exact string comparison in the gate's query,
         producing incorrect resolve behavior.
      6. NO closed_date OR completed_at FIELD ON case_task. Per AAP
         Section 0.5.7, the case_task table has only 6 fields: case,
         subject, type, status, assigned_to, due_date. There's no
         separate completion timestamp; the platform's sys_updated_on
         audit field captures when the status was last changed. This
         is a deliberate simplification of ArkCase's AcmTask domain
         model (which had separate startDate/finishDate/duration
         fields) to keep the POC scoped application minimal per the
         AAP's Minimal Change Clause.
      7. THE DETERMINISTIC sys_id (md5 hash of the subject) ensures
         idempotent re-imports. If this record is re-imported (e.g.,
         during the round-trip-verify validation gate), the platform
         will recognize the existing sys_id and apply
         action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE" by updating the existing record
         in place rather than creating a duplicate. The hash input is
         the literal subject string "Demo task 02: Initial review
         complete"; the resulting hex value
         (949c29a044d9fd7468ddf410173ef684) is 32 characters as
         required by the sys_id contract.
      8. THE BUILD AGENT COMPUTES due_date DYNAMICALLY at file-
         generation time so that the relative offset (-3 days) is
         preserved across importation timeframes. The actual stored
         value (2026-04-28) is the static result of today - 3 days
         evaluated at this file's generation time (today = 2026-05-01
         per the build environment date).
      9. THE casemgmt PLACEHOLDER IS PRESERVED VERBATIM in
         sys_class_name, sys_update_name, sys_scope, sys_package,
         all reference display_values that include the scope prefix
         (assigned_to display_value), and the file path. The
         placeholder is intended for downstream substitution by the
         build pipeline at the time of PDI scope assignment - the
         substitution is global across the entire scoped application
         output (every file under servicenow-case-management-poc/).
-->
<record_update table="x_casemgmt_case_task">
    <x_casemgmt_case_task action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <assigned_to display_value="x_casemgmt_demo_agent">x_casemgmt_demo_agent</assigned_to>
        <case display_value="CASE0000003">CASE0000003</case>
        <due_date>2026-04-28</due_date>
        <status>Closed</status>
        <subject>Demo task 02: Initial review complete</subject>
        <sys_class_name>x_casemgmt_case_task</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>admin</sys_created_by>
        <sys_id>949c29a044d9fd7468ddf410173ef684</sys_id>
        <sys_package display_value="Case Management" source="x_casemgmt">x_casemgmt</sys_package>
        <sys_scope display_value="Case Management">x_casemgmt</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>x_casemgmt_case_task_demo_02</sys_update_name>
        <type>Review</type>
    </x_casemgmt_case_task>
</record_update>
